<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Amos on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</title>
    <link>http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/62-amos/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Amos on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/62-amos/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 1</title>
      <link>http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/62-amos/chap001/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/62-amos/chap001/</guid>
      <description>1 The words of Amos, who was among the herdsmen of Thecua: which he saw concerning Israel in the days of Ozias king of Juda, and in the days of Jeroboam the son of Joas king of Israel two years before the earthquake.&#xA;2 And he said: The Lord will roar from Sion, and utter his voice from Jerusalem: and the beautiful places of the shepherds have mourned, and the top of Carmel is withered.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 2</title>
      <link>http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/62-amos/chap002/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/62-amos/chap002/</guid>
      <description>1 Thus saith the Lord: For three crimes of Moab, and for four I will not convert him: because he hath burnt the bones of the king of Edom even to ashes.&#xA;2 And I will send a fire into Moab, and it shall devour the houses of Carioth: and Moab shall die with a noise, with the sound of the trumpet:&#xA;3 And I will cut off the judge from the midst thereof, and will slay all his princes with him, saith the Lord.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 3</title>
      <link>http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/62-amos/chap003/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/62-amos/chap003/</guid>
      <description>1 Hear the word that the Lord hath spoken concerning you, O ye children of Israel: concerning the whole family that I brought up out of the land of Egypt, saying:&#xA;2 You only have I known of all the families of the earth: therefore will I visit upon you all your iniquities.&#xA;3 Shall two walk together except they be agreed?&#xA;4 Will a lion roar in the forest, if he have no prey?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 4</title>
      <link>http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/62-amos/chap004/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/62-amos/chap004/</guid>
      <description>1 Hear this word, ye fat kine that are in the mountains of Samaria: you that oppress the needy, and crush the poor: that say to your masters: Bring, and we will drink.&#xA;2 The Lord God hath sworn by his holiness, that lo, the days shall come upon you, when they shall lift you up on pikes, and what shall remain of you in boiling pots.&#xA;3 And you shall go out at the breaches one over against the other, and you shall be cast forth into Armon, saith the Lord.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 5</title>
      <link>http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/62-amos/chap005/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/62-amos/chap005/</guid>
      <description>1 Hear ye this word, which I take up concerning you for a lamentation. The house of Israel is fallen, and it shall rise no more.&#xA;2 The virgin of Israel is cast down upon her land, there is none to raise her up.&#xA;3 For thus saith the Lord God: The city, out of which came forth a thousand, there shall be left in it a hundred: and out of which there came a hundred, there shall be left in it ten, in the house of Israel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 6</title>
      <link>http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/62-amos/chap006/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/62-amos/chap006/</guid>
      <description>1 Woe to you that are wealthy in Sion, and to you that have confidence in the mountain of Samaria: ye great men, heads of the people, that go in with state into the house of Israel.&#xA;2 Pass ye over to Chalane, and see, and go from thence into Emath the great: and go down into Geth of the Philistines, and to all the best kingdoms of these: if their border be larger than your border.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 7</title>
      <link>http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/62-amos/chap007/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/62-amos/chap007/</guid>
      <description>1 These things the Lord God shewed to me: and behold the locust was formed in the beginning of the shooting up of the latter rain, and lo, it was the latter rain after the king&amp;rsquo;s mowing.&#xA;2 And it came to pass, that when they had made an end of eating the grass of the land, I said: O Lord God, be merciful, I beseech thee: who shall raise up Jacob, for he is very little?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 8</title>
      <link>http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/62-amos/chap008/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/62-amos/chap008/</guid>
      <description>1 These things the Lord shewed to me: and behold a hook to draw down the fruit.&#xA;2 And he said: What seest thou, Amos? And I said: A hook to draw down fruit. And the Lord said to me: The end is come upon my people Israel: I will not again pass by them any more.&#xA;3 And the hinges of the temple shall screak in that day, saith the Lord God: many shall die: silence shall be cast in every place.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 9</title>
      <link>http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/62-amos/chap009/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/62-amos/chap009/</guid>
      <description>1 I saw the Lord standing upon the altar, and he said: Strike the hinges, and let the lintels be shook: for there is covetousness in the head of them all, and I will slay the last of them with the sword: there shall be no flight for them: they shall flee, and he that shall flee of them shall not be delivered.&#xA;2 Though they go down even to hell, thence shall my hand bring them out: and though they climb up to heaven, thence will I bring them down.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
