<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Isaiah on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</title>
    <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Isaiah on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:32 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 10</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap010/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:32 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap010/</guid>
      <description>1 Woe to them that make wicked laws: and when they write, write injustice:&#xA;2 To oppress the poor in judgment, and do violence to the cause of the humble of my people: that widows might be their prey, and that they might rob the fatherless.&#xA;3 What will you do in the day of visitation, and of the calamity which cometh from afar? to whom will ye flee for help?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 11</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap011/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:32 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap011/</guid>
      <description>1 And there shall come forth a rod out of the root of Jesse, and a flower shall rise up out of his root.&#xA;2 And the spirit of the Lord shall rest upon him: the spirit of wisdom, and of understanding, the spirit of counsel, and of fortitude, the spirit of knowledge, and of godliness.&#xA;3 And he shall be filled with the spirit of the fear of the Lord, He shall not judge according to the sight of the eyes, nor reprove according to the hearing of the ears.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 12</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap012/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:32 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap012/</guid>
      <description>1 And thou shalt say in that day: I will give thanks to thee, O Lord, for thou wast angry with me: thy wrath is turned away, and thou hast comforted me.&#xA;2 Behold, God is my saviour, I will deal confidently, and will not fear: because the Lord is my strength, and my praise, and he is become my salvation.&#xA;3 Thou shall draw waters with joy out of the saviour&amp;rsquo;s fountains:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 13</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap013/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:32 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap013/</guid>
      <description>1 The burden of Babylon which Isaiah the son of Amos saw.&#xA;2 Upon the dark mountain lift ye up a banner, exalt the voice, lift up the hand, and let the rulers go into the gates.&#xA;3 I have commanded my sanctified ones, and have called my strong ones in my wrath, them that rejoice in my glory.&#xA;4 The noise of a multitude in the mountains, as it were of many people, the noise of the sound of kings, of nations gathered together: the Lord of hosts hath given charge to the troops of war.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 14</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap014/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:32 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap014/</guid>
      <description>1 Her time is near at hand, and her days shall not be prolonged. For the Lord will have mercy on Jacob, and will yet choose out of Israel, and will make them rest upon their own ground: and the stranger shall be joined with them, and shall adhere to the house of Jacob.&#xA;2 And the people shall take them, and bring them into their place: and the house of Israel shall possess them in the land of the Lord for servants and handmaids: and they shall make them captives that had taken them, and shall subdue their oppressors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 15</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap015/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:32 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap015/</guid>
      <description>1 The burden of Moab. Because in the night Ar of Moab is laid waste, it is silent: because the wall of Moab is destroyed in the night, it is silent.&#xA;2 The house is gone up, and Dibon to the high places to mourn over Nabo, and over Medaba, Moab hath howled: on all their heads shall be baldness, and every beard shall be shaven.&#xA;3 In their streets they are girded with sackcloth: on the tops of their houses, and in their streets all shall howl and come down weeping.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 16</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap016/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:32 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap016/</guid>
      <description>1 Send forth, O Lord, the lamb, the ruler of the earth, from Petra of the desert, to the mount of the daughter of Sion.&#xA;2 And it shall come to pass, that as a bird fleeing away, and as young ones flying out of the nest, so shall the daughters of Moab be in the passage of Arnon.&#xA;3 Take counsel, gather a council: make thy shadow as the night in the midday: hide them that flee, and betray not them that wander about.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 17</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap017/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:32 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap017/</guid>
      <description>1 The burden of Damascus. Behold Damascus shall cease to be a city, and shall be as a ruinous heap of stones.&#xA;2 The cities of Aroer shall be left for flocks, and they shall rest there, and there shall be none to make them afraid.&#xA;3 And aid shall cease from Ephraim, and the kingdom from Damascus: and the remnant of Syria shall be as the glory of the children of Israel: saith the Lord of hosts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 18</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap018/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:32 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap018/</guid>
      <description>1 Woe to the land, the winged cymbal, which is beyond the rivers of Ethiopia,&#xA;2 That sendeth ambassadors by the sea, and in vessels of bulrushes upon the waters. Go, ye swift angels, to a nation rent and torn in pieces: to a terrible people, after which there is no other: to a nation expecting and trodden underfoot, whose land the rivers have spoiled.&#xA;3 All ye inhabitants of the world, who dwell on the earth, when the sign shall be lifted up on the mountains, you shall see, and you shall hear the sound of the trumpet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 19</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap019/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:32 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap019/</guid>
      <description>1 The burden of Egypt. Behold the Lord will ascend upon a swift cloud, and will enter into Egypt, and the idols of Egypt shall be moved at his presence, and the heart of Egypt shall melt in the midst thereof.&#xA;2 And I will set the Egyptians to fight against the Egyptians: and they shall fight brother against brother, and friend against friend, city against city, kingdom against kingdom.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 20</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap020/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:32 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap020/</guid>
      <description>1 In the year that Tharthan entered into Azotus, when Sargon the king of the Assyrians had sent him, and he had fought against Azotus, and had taken it:&#xA;2 At that same time the Lord spoke by the hand of Isaiah the son of Amos, saying Go, and loose the sackcloth from off thy loins, and take off thy shoes from thy feet. And he did so, and went naked, and barefoot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 21</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:32 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap021/</guid>
      <description>1 The burden of the desert of the sea. As whirlwinds come from the south, it cometh from the desert from a terrible land.&#xA;2 A grievous vision is told me: he that is unfaithful dealeth unfaithfully: and he that is a spoiler, spoileth. Go up, O Elam, besiege, O Mede: I have made all the mourning thereof to cease.&#xA;3 Therefore are my loins filled with pain, anguish hath taken hold of me, as the anguish of a woman in labour: I fell down at the hearing of it, I was troubled at the seeing of it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 22</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap022/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:32 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap022/</guid>
      <description>1 The burden of the valley of vision. What aileth thee also, that thou too art wholly gone up to the housetops?&#xA;2 Full of clamour, a populous city, a joyous city: thy slain are not slain by the sword, nor dead in battle.&#xA;3 All the princes are fled together, and are bound hard: all that were found, are bound together, they are fled far off.&#xA;4 Therefore have I said: Depart from me, I will weep bitterly: labour not to comfort me, for the devastation of the daughter of my people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 23</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap023/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:32 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap023/</guid>
      <description>1 The burden of Tyre. Howl, ye ships of the sea, for the house is destroyed, from whence they were wont to come: from the land of Cethim it is revealed to them.&#xA;2 Be silent, you that dwell in the island: the merchants of Sidon passing over the sea, have filled thee.&#xA;3 The seed of the Nile in many waters, the harvest of the river is her revenue: and she is become the mart of the nations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 24</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap024/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:32 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap024/</guid>
      <description>1 Behold the Lord shall lay waste the earth, and shall strip it, and shall afflict the face thereof, and scatter abroad the inhabitants thereof.&#xA;2 And it shall be as with the people, so with the priest: and as with the servant so with his master: as with the handmaid, so with her mistress: as with the buyer, so with the seller: as with the lender, so with the borrower: as with him that calleth for his money, so with him that oweth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 25</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap025/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:32 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap025/</guid>
      <description>1 O Lord, thou art my God, I will exalt O thee, and give glory to thy name: for thou hast done wonderful things, thy designs of old faithful, amen.&#xA;2 For thou hast reduced the city to a heap, the strong city to ruin, the house of strangers, to be no city, and to be no more built up for ever.&#xA;3 Therefore shall a strong people praise thee, the city of mighty nations shall fear thee.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 26</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap026/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:32 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap026/</guid>
      <description>1 In that day shall this canticle be sung in the land of Juda. Sion the city of our strength a saviour, a wall and a bulwark shall be set therein.&#xA;2 Open ye the gates, and let the just nation, that keepeth the truth, enter in.&#xA;3 The old error is passed away: thou wilt keep peace: peace, because we have hoped in thee.&#xA;4 You have hoped in the Lord for evermore, in the Lord God mighty for ever.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 27</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap027/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:32 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap027/</guid>
      <description>1 In that day the Lord with his hard, and great, and strong sword shall visit leviathan the bar serpent, and leviathan the crooked serpent, and shall slay the whale that is in the sea.&#xA;2 In that day there shall be singing to the vineyard of pure wine.&#xA;3 I am the Lord that keep it, I will suddenly give it drink: lest any hurt come to it, I keep it night and day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 28</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap028/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:32 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap028/</guid>
      <description>1 Woe to the crown of pride, to the drunkards of Ephraim, and to the fading flower the glory his joy, who were on the head of the fat valley, staggering with wine.&#xA;2 Behold the Lord is mighty and strong, as a storm of hail: a destroying whirlwind, as the violence of many waters overflowing, and sent forth upon a spacious land.&#xA;3 The crown of pride of the drunkards of Ephraim shall be trodden under feet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 29</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap029/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:32 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap029/</guid>
      <description>1 Woe to Ariel, to Ariel the city which David took: year is added to year. the solemnities are at an end.&#xA;2 And I will make a trench about Ariel, and it shall be in sorrow and mourning, and it shall be to me as Ariel.&#xA;3 And I will make a circle round about thee, and I will cast up a rampart against thee, and raise up bulwarks to besiege thee.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 30</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap030/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:32 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap030/</guid>
      <description>1 Woe to you, apostate children, saith the Lord, that you would take counsel, and not of me: and would begin a web, and not by my spirit, that you might add sin upon sin:&#xA;2 Who walk to go down into Egypt, and have not asked at my mouth, hoping for help in the strength of Pharao, and trusting in the shadow of Egypt.&#xA;3 And the strength of Pharao shall be to your confusion, and the confidence of the shadow of Egypt to your shame.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 31</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap031/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:32 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap031/</guid>
      <description>1 Woe to them that go down to Egypt for help, trusting in horses, and putting their confidence in chariots, because they are many: and in horsemen, because they are very strong: and have not trusted in the Holy One of Israel, and have not sought after the Lord.&#xA;2 But he that is the wise one hath brought evil, and hath not removed his words: and he will rise up against the house of the wicked, and against the aid of them that work iniquity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 32</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap032/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:32 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap032/</guid>
      <description>1 Behold a king shall reign in justice, and princes shall rule in judgment.&#xA;2 And a man shall be as when one is hid from the wind, and hideth himself from a storm, as rivers of waters in drought, and the shadow of a rock that standeth out in a desert land.&#xA;3 The eyes of them that see shall not be dim, and the ears of them that hear shall hearken diligently.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 33</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap033/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:32 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap033/</guid>
      <description>1 Woe to thee that spoilest, shalt not thou thyself also be spoiled? and thou that despisest, shalt not thyself also be despised? when thou shalt have made an end of spoiling, thou shalt be spoiled: when being wearied thou shalt cease to despise, thou shalt be despised.&#xA;2 O Lord, have mercy on us: for we have waited for thee: be thou our arm in the morning, and our salvation in the time of trouble.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 34</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap034/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:32 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap034/</guid>
      <description>1 Come near, ye Gentiles, and hear, and hearken, ye people: let the earth hear, and all that is therein, the world, and every thing that cometh forth of it.&#xA;2 For the indignation of the Lord is upon all nations, and his fury upon all their armies: he hath killed them, and delivered them to slaughter.&#xA;3 Their slain shall be cast forth, and out of their carcasses shall rise a stink: the mountains shall be melted with their blood.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 35</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap035/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:32 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap035/</guid>
      <description>1 The land that was desolate and impassable shall be glad, and the wilderness shall rejoice, and shall flourish like the lily.&#xA;2 It shall bud forth and blossom, and shall rejoice with joy and praise: the glory of Libanus is given to it: the beauty of Carmel, and Saron, they shall see the glory of the Lord, and the beauty of our God.&#xA;3 Strengthen ye the feeble hands, and confirm the weak knees.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 36</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap036/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:32 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap036/</guid>
      <description>1 And it came to pass in the fourteenth year of king Ezechias, that Sennacherib king of the Assyrians came up against all the fenced cities of Juda, and took them.&#xA;2 And the king of the Assyrians sent Rabsaces from Lachis to Jerusalem, to king Ezechias with a great army, and he stood by the conduit of the upper pool in the way of the fuller&amp;rsquo;s field.&#xA;3 And there went out to him Eliacim the son of Helcias, who was over the house, and Sobna the scribe, and Joahe the son of Asaph the recorder.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 37</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap037/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:32 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap037/</guid>
      <description>1 And it came to pass, when king Ezechias had heard it, that he rent his garments and covered himself with sackcloth, and went into the house of the Lord.&#xA;2 And he sent Eliacim who was over the house, and Sobna the scribe, and the ancients of the priests covered with sackcloth, to Isaiah the son of Amos the prophet.&#xA;3 And they said to him: Thus saith Ezechias: This day is a day of tribulation, and of rebuke, and of blasphemy: for the children are come to the birth, and there is not strength to bring forth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 38</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap038/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:32 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap038/</guid>
      <description>1 In those days Ezechias was sick even to death, and Isaiah the son of Amos the prophet cane unto him, and said to him: Thus saith the Lord: Take order with thy house, for thou shalt die, and not live.&#xA;2 And Ezechias turned his face toward the wall, and prayed to the Lord,&#xA;3 And said: I beseech thee, O Lord, remember how I have walked before thee in truth, and with a perfect heart, and have done that which is good in thy sight.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 39</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap039/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:32 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap039/</guid>
      <description>1 At that time Merodach Baladan, the son of Baladan king of Babylon, sent letters and presents to Ezechias: for he had heard that he had been sick and was recovered.&#xA;2 And Ezechias rejoiced at their coming, and he shewed them the storehouses of his aromatical spices, and of the silver, and of the gold, and of the sweet odours, and of the precious ointment, and all the storehouses of his furniture, and all things that were found in his treasures.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 40</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap040/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:32 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap040/</guid>
      <description>1 Be comforted, be comforted, my people, saith your God.&#xA;2 Speak ye to the heart of Jerusalem, and call to her: for her evil is come to an end, her iniquity is forgiven: she hath received of the hand of the Lord double for all her sins.&#xA;3 The voice of one crying in the desert: Prepare ye the way of the Lord, make straight in the wilderness the paths of our God.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 41</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap041/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:32 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap041/</guid>
      <description>1 Let the islands keep silence before me, and the nations take new strength: let them come near, and then speak, let us come near to judgment together.&#xA;2 Who hath raised up the just one from the east, hath called him to follow him? he shall give the nations in his sight, and he shall rule over kings: he shall give them as the dust to his sword, as stubble driven by the wind, to his bow.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 42</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap042/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:32 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap042/</guid>
      <description>1 Behold my servant, I will uphold him: my elect, my soul delighteth in him: I have given my spirit upon him, he shall bring forth judgment to the Gentiles.&#xA;2 He shall not cry, nor have respect to person, neither shall his voice be heard abroad.&#xA;3 The bruised reed he shall not break, and smoking flax he shall not quench, he shall bring forth judgment unto truth.&#xA;4 He shall not be sad, nor troublesome, till he set judgment in the earth, and the islands shall wait for his law.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 43</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap043/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:32 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap043/</guid>
      <description>1 And now thus saith the Lord that created thee, O Jacob, and formed thee, O Israel: Fear not, for I have redeemed thee, and called thee by thy name: thou art mine.&#xA;2 When thou shalt pass through the waters, I will be with thee, and the rivers shall not cover thee: when thou shalt walk in the fire, thou shalt not be burnt, and the flames shall not burn in thee:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 44</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap044/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:32 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap044/</guid>
      <description>1 And now hear, O Jacob, my servant, and Israel whom I have chosen.&#xA;2 Thus saith the Lord that made and formed thee, thy helper from the womb: Fear not, O my servant Jacob, and thou most righteous whom I have chosen.&#xA;3 For I will pour out waters upon the thirsty ground, and streams upon the dry land: I will pour out my spirit upon thy seed, and my blessing upon thy stock.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 45</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap045/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:32 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap045/</guid>
      <description>1 Thus saith the Lord to my anointed Cyrus, whose right hand I have taken hold of, to subdue nations before his face, and to turn the backs of kings, and to open the doors before him, and the gates shall not be shut.&#xA;2 I will go before thee, and will humble the great ones of the earth: I will break in pieces the gates of brass, and will burst the bars of iron.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 46</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap046/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:32 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap046/</guid>
      <description>1 Bel is broken, Nebo is destroyed: their idols are put upon beasts and cattle, your burdens of heavy weight even unto weariness.&#xA;2 They are consumed, and are broken together: they could not save him that carried them, and they themselves shall go into captivity.&#xA;3 Hearken unto me, O house of Jacob, all the remnant of the house of Israel who are carried by my bowels, are borne up by my womb.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 47</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap047/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:32 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap047/</guid>
      <description>1 Come down, sit in the dust, O virgin daughter of Babylon, sit on the ground: there is no throne for the daughter of the Chaldeans, for thou shalt no more be called delicate and tender.&#xA;2 Take a millstone and grind meal: uncover thy shame, strip thy shoulder, make bare thy legs, pass over the rivers.&#xA;3 Thy nakedness shall be discovered, and thy shame shall be seen: I will take vengeance, and no man shall resist me.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 48</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap048/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:32 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap048/</guid>
      <description>1 Hear ye these things, O house of Jacob, you that are called by the name of Israel, and are come forth out of the waters of Juda, you who swear by the name of the Lord, and make mention of the God of Israel, but not in truth, nor in justice.&#xA;2 For they are called of the holy city, and are established upon the God of Israel: the Lord of hosts is his name.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 49</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap049/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:32 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap049/</guid>
      <description>1 Give ear, ye islands, and hearken, ye people from afar. The Lord hath called me from the womb, from the bowels of my mother he hath been mindful of my name.&#xA;2 And he hath made my mouth like a sharp sword: in the shadow of his hand he hath protected me, and hath made me as a chosen arrow: in his quiver he hath hidden me.&#xA;3 And he said to me: Thou art my servant Israel, for in thee will I glory.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 50</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap050/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:32 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap050/</guid>
      <description>1 Thus saith the Lord: What is this bill of the divorce of your mother, with which I have put her away? or who is my creditor, to whom I sold you: behold you are sold for your iniquities, and for your wicked deeds have I put your mother away.&#xA;2 Because I came, and there was not a man: I called, and there was none that would hear. Is my hand shortened and become little, that I cannot redeem?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 51</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap051/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:32 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap051/</guid>
      <description>1 Give ear to me, you that follow that which is just, and you that seek the Lord: look unto the rock whence you are hewn, and to the hole of the pit from which you are dug out.&#xA;2 Look unto Abraham your father, and to Sara that bore you: for I called him alone, and blessed him, and multiplied him.&#xA;3 The Lord therefore will comfort Sion, and will comfort all the ruins thereof: and he will make her desert as a place of pleasure, and her wilderness as the garden of the Lord.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 52</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap052/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:32 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap052/</guid>
      <description>1 Arise, arise, put on thy strength, O Sion, put on the garments of thy glory, O Jerusalem, the city of the Holy One: for henceforth the uncircumcised, and unclean shall no more pass through thee.&#xA;2 Shake thyself from the dust, arise, sit up, O Jerusalem: loose the bonds from off thy neck, O captive daughter of Sion.&#xA;3 For thus saith the Lord: You were sold gratis, and you shall be redeemed, without money.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 53</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap053/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:32 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap053/</guid>
      <description>1 Who a hath believed our report? and to whom is the arm of the Lord revealed?&#xA;2 And he shall grow up as a tender plant before him, and as a root out of a thirsty ground: there is no beauty in him, nor comeliness: and we have seen him, and there was no sightliness, that we should be desirous of him:&#xA;3 Despised, and the most abject of men, a man of sorrows, and acquainted with infirmity: and his look was as it were hidden and despised, whereupon we esteemed him not.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 54</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap054/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:32 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap054/</guid>
      <description>1 Give praise, O thou barren, that bearest not: sing forth praise, and make a joyful noise, thou that didst not travail with child: for many are the children of the desolate, more than of her that hath a husband, saith the Lord.&#xA;2 Enlarge the place of thy tent, and stretch out the skins of thy tabernacles, spare not: lengthen thy cords, and strengthen thy stakes.&#xA;3 For thou shalt pass on to the right hand, and to the left: and thy seed shall inherit the Gentiles, and shall inhabit the desolate cities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 55</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap055/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:32 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap055/</guid>
      <description>1 All you that thirst, come to the waters: and you that have no money make haste, buy, and eat: come ye, buy wine and milk without money, and without any price.&#xA;2 Why do you spend money for that which is not bread, and your labour for that which doth not satisfy you? Hearken diligently to me, and eat that which is good, and your soul shall be delighted in fatness.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 56</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap056/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:32 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap056/</guid>
      <description>1 Thus saith the Lord: Keep ye judgment, and do justice: for my salvation is near to come, and my justice to be revealed.&#xA;2 Blessed is the man that doth this, and the son of man that shall lay hold on this: that keepeth the sabbath from profaning it, that keepeth his hands from doing any evil.&#xA;3 And let not the son of the stranger, that adhereth to the Lord, speak, saying: The Lord will divide and separate me from his people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 57</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap057/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:32 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap057/</guid>
      <description>1 The just perisheth, and no man layeth it to heart, and men of mercy are taken away, because there is none that understandeth; for the just man is taken away from before the face of evil.&#xA;2 Let peace come, let him rest in his bed that hath walked in his uprightness.&#xA;3 But draw near hither, you sons of the sorceress, the seed of the adulterer, and of the harlot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 58</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap058/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:32 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap058/</guid>
      <description>1 Cry, cease not, lift up thy voice like a trumpet, and shew my people their wicked doings, and the house of Jacob their sins.&#xA;2 For they seek me from day to day, and desire to know my ways, as a nation that hath done justice, and hath not forsaken the judgment of their God: they ask of me the judgments of justice: they are willing to approach to God.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 59</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap059/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:32 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap059/</guid>
      <description>1 Behold the hand of the Lord is not shortened that it cannot save, neither is his ear heavy that it cannot hear.&#xA;2 But your iniquities have divided between you and your God, and your sins have hid his face from you that he should not hear.&#xA;3 For your hands are defiled with blood, and your fingers with iniquity: your lips have spoken lies, and your tongue uttereth iniquity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 6</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap006/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:32 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap006/</guid>
      <description>1 In the year that king Ozias died, I saw the Lord sitting upon a throne high and elevated: and his train filled the temple.&#xA;2 Upon it stood the seraphims: the one had six wings, and the other had six wings: with two they covered his face, and with two they covered his feet, and with two they flew.&#xA;3 And they cried one to another, and said: Holy, holy, holy, the Lord God of hosts, all the earth is full of his glory,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 60</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap060/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:32 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap060/</guid>
      <description>1 Arise, be enlightened, O Jerusalem: for thy light is come, and the glory of the Lord is risen upon thee.&#xA;2 For behold darkness shall cover the earth, and a mist the people: but the Lord shall arise upon thee, and his glory shall be seen upon thee.&#xA;3 And the Gentiles shall walk in thy light, and kings in the brightness of thy rising.&#xA;4 Lift up thy eyes round about, and see: all these are gathered together, they are come to thee: thy sons shall come from afar, and thy daughters shall rise up at thy side.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 61</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap061/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:32 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap061/</guid>
      <description>1 The spirit of the Lord is upon me, because the Lord hath anointed me: he hath sent me to preach to the meek, to heal the contrite of heart, and to preach a release to the captives, and deliverance to them that are shut up.&#xA;2 To proclaim the acceptable year of the Lord, and the day of vengeance of our God: to comfort all that mourn:&#xA;3 To appoint to the mourners of Sion, and to give them a crown for ashes, the oil of joy for mourning, a garment of praise for the spirit of grief: and they shall be called in it the mighty ones of justice, the planting of the Lord to glorify him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 62</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap062/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:32 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap062/</guid>
      <description>1 For Sion&amp;rsquo;s sake I will not hold my peace, and for the sake of Jerusalem, I will not rest till her just one come forth as brightness, and her saviour be lighted as a lamp.&#xA;2 And the Gentiles shall see thy just one, and all kings thy glorious one: and thou shalt be called by a new name, which the mouth of the Lord shall name.&#xA;3 And thou shalt be a crown of glory in the hand of the Lord, and a royal diadem in the hand of thy God.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 63</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap063/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:32 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap063/</guid>
      <description>1 Who is this that cometh from Edom, with dyed garments from Bosra, this beautiful one in his robe, walking in the greatness of his strength. I, that speak justice, and am a defender to save.&#xA;2 Why then is thy apparel red, and thy garments like theirs that tread in the winepress?&#xA;3 I have trodden the winepress alone, and of the Gentiles there is not a man with me: I have trampled on them in my indignation, and have trodden them down in my wrath, and their blood is sprinkled upon my garments, and I have stained all my apparel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 64</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap064/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:32 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap064/</guid>
      <description>1 O that thou wouldst rend the heavens, and wouldst come down: the mountains would melt away at thy presence.&#xA;2 They would melt as at the burning of fire, the waters would burn with fire, that thy name might be made known to thy enemies: that the nations might tremble at thy presence.&#xA;3 When thou shalt do wonderful things, we shall not bear them: thou didst come down, and at thy presence the mountains melted away.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 65</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap065/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:32 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap065/</guid>
      <description>1 They have sought me that before asked not for me, they have found me that sought me not. I said: Behold me, behold me, to a nation that did not call upon my name.&#xA;2 I have spread forth my hands all the day to an unbelieving people, who walk in a way that is not good after their own thoughts.&#xA;3 A people that continually provoke me to anger before my face, that immolate in gardens, and sacrifice upon bricks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 66</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap066/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:32 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap066/</guid>
      <description>1 Thus saith the Lord: Heaven is my throne, and the earth my footstool: what is this house that you will build to me? and what is this place of my rest?&#xA;2 My hand made all these things, and all these things were made, saith the Lord. But to whom shall I have respect, but to him that is poor and little, and of a contrite spirit, and that trembleth at my words?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 7</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap007/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:32 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap007/</guid>
      <description>1 And it came to pass in the days of Achaz the son of Joathan, the son of Ozias, king of Juda, that Rasin king of Syria and Phacee the son of Romelia king of Israel, came up to Jerusalem, to fight against it: but they could not prevail over it.&#xA;2 And they told the house of David, saying: Syria hath rested upon Ephraim, and his heart was moved, and the heart of his people, as the trees of the woods are moved with the wind.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 8</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap008/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:32 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap008/</guid>
      <description>1 And the Lord said to me: Take thee a great book, and write in it with a man&amp;rsquo;s pen. Take away the spoils with speed, quickly take the prey.&#xA;2 And I took unto me faithful witnesses, Urias the priest, and Zacharias the son of Barachias.&#xA;3 And I went to the prophetess, and she conceived, and bore a son. And the Lord said to me: Call his name, Hasten to take away the spoils: Make hast to take away the prey.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 9</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap009/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:32 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap009/</guid>
      <description>1 At the first time the land of Zabulon, and the land of Nephtali was lightly touched: and at the last the way of the sea beyond the Jordan of the Galilee of the Gentiles was heavily loaded.&#xA;2 The people that walked in darkness, have seen a great light: to them that dwelt in the region of the shadow of death, light is risen.&#xA;3 Thou hast multiplied the nation, and hast not increased the joy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 1</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap001/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:31 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap001/</guid>
      <description>1 The vision of Isaiah the Son of Amos, which he saw concerning Juda and Jerusalem in the days of Ozias, Joathan, Achaz, and Ezechias, kings of Juda.&#xA;2 Hear, O ye heavens, and give ear, O earth, for the Lord hath spoken. I have brought up children, and exalted them: but they have despised me.&#xA;3 The ox knoweth his owner, and the ass his master&amp;rsquo;s crib: but Israel hath not known me, and my people hath not understood.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 2</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap002/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:31 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap002/</guid>
      <description>1 The word that Isaiah the son of Amos saw, concerning Juda and Jerusalem.&#xA;2 And in the last days the mountain of the house of the Lord shall be prepared on the top of mountains, and it shall be exalted above the hills, and all nations shall flow unto it.&#xA;3 And many people shall go, and say: Come and let us go up to the mountain of the Lord, and to the house of the God of Jacob, and he will teach us his ways, and we will walk in his paths: for the law shall come forth from Sion, and the word of the Lord from Jerusalem.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 3</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap003/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:31 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap003/</guid>
      <description>1 For behold the sovereign Lord of hosts shall take away from Jerusalem, and from Juda the valiant and the strong, the whole strength of bread, and the whole strength of water.&#xA;2 The strong man, and the man of war, the judge, and the prophet and the cunning man, and the ancient.&#xA;3 The captain over fifty, and the honourable in countenance, and the counsellor, and the architect, and the skilful in eloquent speech.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 4</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap004/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:31 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap004/</guid>
      <description>1 And in that day seven women shall take hold of one man, saying: We will eat our own bread, and wear our own apparel: only let us be called by thy name, take away our reproach.&#xA;2 In that day the bud of the Lord shall be in magnificence and glory, and the fruit of the earth shall be high, and a great joy to them that shall have escaped of Israel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 5</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap005/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:31 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/54-isaiah/chap005/</guid>
      <description>1 I will sing to my beloved the canticle of my cousin concerning his vineyard. My beloved had a vineyard on a hill in a fruitful place.&#xA;2 And he fenced it in, and picked the stones out of it, and planted it with the choicest vines, and built a tower in the midst thereof, and set up a winepress therein: and he looked that it should bring forth grapes, and it brought forth wild grapes.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
