<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2 Corinthians on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</title>
    <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/08-2-corinthians/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2 Corinthians on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:24 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/08-2-corinthians/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 1</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/08-2-corinthians/chap001/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:24 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/08-2-corinthians/chap001/</guid>
      <description>1 Paul, an apostle of Jesus Christ by the will of God, and Timothy our brother: to the church of God that is at Corinth, with all the saints that are in all Achaia:&#xA;2 Grace unto you and peace from God our Father and from the Lord Jesus Christ.&#xA;3 Blessed be the God and Father of our Lord Jesus Christ, the Father of mercies and the God of all comfort:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 10</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/08-2-corinthians/chap010/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:24 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/08-2-corinthians/chap010/</guid>
      <description>1 Now I Paul, myself beseech you, by the mildness and modesty of Christ: who in presence indeed am lowly among you, but being absent am bold toward you.&#xA;2 But I beseech you, that I may not be bold when I am present with that confidence wherewith I am thought to be bold, against some who reckon us as if we walked according to the flesh.&#xA;3 For though we walk in the flesh, we do not war according to the flesh.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 11</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/08-2-corinthians/chap011/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:24 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/08-2-corinthians/chap011/</guid>
      <description>1 Would to God you could bear with some little of my folly! But do bear with me.&#xA;2 For I am jealous of you with the jealousy of God. For I have espoused you to one husband, that I may present you as a chaste virgin to Christ.&#xA;3 But I fear lest, as the serpent seduced Eve by his subtilty, so your minds should be corrupted and fall from the simplicity that is in Christ.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 12</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/08-2-corinthians/chap012/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:24 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/08-2-corinthians/chap012/</guid>
      <description>1 If I must glory (it is not expedient indeed) but I will come to visions and revelations of the Lord.&#xA;2 I know a man in Christ: above fourteen years ago (whether in the body, I know not, or out of the body, I know not: God knoweth), such a one caught up to the third heaven.&#xA;3 And I know such a man (whether in the body, or out of the body, I know not: God knoweth):</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 13</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/08-2-corinthians/chap013/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:24 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/08-2-corinthians/chap013/</guid>
      <description>1 Behold, this is the third time I am coming to you: In the mouth of two or three witnesses shall every word stand.&#xA;2 I have told before and foretell, as present and now absent, to them that sinned before and to all the rest, that if I come again, I will not spare.&#xA;3 Do you seek a proof of Christ that speaketh in me, who towards you is not weak, but is mighty in you?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 2</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/08-2-corinthians/chap002/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:24 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/08-2-corinthians/chap002/</guid>
      <description>1 But I determined this with myself, to come to you again in sorrow.&#xA;2 For if I make you sorrowful, who is he then that can make me glad, but the same who is made sorrowful by me?&#xA;3 And I wrote this same to you: that I may not, when I come, have sorrow upon sorrow from them of whom I ought to rejoice: having confidence in you all, that my joy is the joy of you all.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 3</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/08-2-corinthians/chap003/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:24 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/08-2-corinthians/chap003/</guid>
      <description>1 Do we begin again to commend ourselves? Or do we need (as some do) epistles of commendation to you, or from you?&#xA;2 You are our epistle, written in our hearts, which is known and read by all men:&#xA;3 Being manifested, that you are the epistle of Christ, ministered by us, and written: not with ink but with the Spirit of the living God: not in tables of stone but in the fleshly tables of the heart.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 4</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/08-2-corinthians/chap004/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:24 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/08-2-corinthians/chap004/</guid>
      <description>1 Therefore seeing we have this ministration, according as we have obtained mercy, we faint not.&#xA;2 But we renounce the hidden things of dishonesty, not walking in craftiness nor adulterating the word of God: but by manifestation of the truth commending ourselves to every man&amp;rsquo;s conscience, in the sight of God.&#xA;3 And if our gospel be also hid, it is hid to them that are lost,&#xA;4 In whom the god of this world hath blinded the minds of unbelievers, that the light of the gospel of the glory of Christ, who is the image of God, should not shine unto them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 5</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/08-2-corinthians/chap005/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:24 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/08-2-corinthians/chap005/</guid>
      <description>1 For we know, if our earthly house of this habitation be dissolved, that we have a building of God, a house not made with hands, eternal in heaven.&#xA;2 For in this also we groan, desiring to be clothed upon with our habitation that is from heaven.&#xA;3 Yet so that we be found clothed, not naked.&#xA;4 For we also, who are in this tabernacle, do groan, being burthened; because we would not be unclothed, but clothed upon, that that which is mortal may be swallowed up by life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 6</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/08-2-corinthians/chap006/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:24 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/08-2-corinthians/chap006/</guid>
      <description>1 And we helping do exhort you that you receive not the grace of God in vain.&#xA;2 For he saith: In an accepted time have I heard thee and in the day of salvation have I helped thee. Behold, now is the acceptable time: behold, now is the day of salvation.&#xA;3 Giving no offence to any man, that our ministry be not blamed.&#xA;4 But in all things let us exhibit ourselves as the ministers of God, in much patience, in tribulation, in necessities, in distresses,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 7</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/08-2-corinthians/chap007/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:24 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/08-2-corinthians/chap007/</guid>
      <description>1 Having therefore these promises, dearly beloved, let us cleanse ourselves from all defilement of the flesh and of the spirit, perfecting sanctification in the fear of God.&#xA;2 Receive us. We have injured no man: we have corrupted no man: we have overreached no man.&#xA;3 I speak not this to your condemnation. For we have said before that you are in our hearts: to die together and to live together.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 8</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/08-2-corinthians/chap008/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:24 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/08-2-corinthians/chap008/</guid>
      <description>1 Now we make known unto you, brethren, the grace of God that hath been given in the churches of Macedonia.&#xA;2 That in much experience of tribulation, they have had abundance of joy and their very deep poverty hath abounded unto the riches of their simplicity.&#xA;3 For according to their power (I bear them witness) and beyond their power, they were willing:&#xA;4 With much entreaty begging of us the grace and communication of the ministry that is done toward the saints.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 9</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/08-2-corinthians/chap009/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:24 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/08-2-corinthians/chap009/</guid>
      <description>1 For concerning the ministry that is done towards the saints, it is superfluous for me to write unto you.&#xA;2 For I know your forward mind: for which I boast of you to the Macedonians, that Achaia also is ready from the year past. And your emulation hath provoked very many.&#xA;3 Now I have sent the brethren, that the thing which we boast of concerning you be not made void in this behalf, that (as I have said) you may be ready:</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
