<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Baruch on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</title>
    <link>http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/57-baruch/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Baruch on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:32 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/57-baruch/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 1</title>
      <link>http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/57-baruch/chap001/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:32 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/57-baruch/chap001/</guid>
      <description>1 And these are the words of the book, which Baruch the son of Nerias, the son of Maasias, the son of Sedecias, the son of Sedei, the son Helcias, wrote in Babylonia.&#xA;2 In the fifth year, in the seventh day of the month, at the time that the Chaldeans took Jerusalem, and burnt it with fire.&#xA;3 And Baruch read the words of this book in the hearing of Jechonias the son of Joakim king of Juda, and in the hearing of all the people that came to hear the book.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 2</title>
      <link>http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/57-baruch/chap002/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:32 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/57-baruch/chap002/</guid>
      <description>1 Wherefore the Lord our God hath made good his word, that he spoke to us, and to our judges that have judged Israel, and to our kings, and to our princes, and to all Israel and Juda:&#xA;2 That the Lord would bring upon us great evils, such as never happened under heaven, as they have come to pass in Jerusalem, according to the things that are written in the law of Moses:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 3</title>
      <link>http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/57-baruch/chap003/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:32 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/57-baruch/chap003/</guid>
      <description>1 And now, O Lord Almighty, the God of Israel, the soul in anguish, and the troubled spirit crieth to thee:&#xA;2 Hear, O Lord, and have mercy, for thou art a merciful God, and have pity on us: for we have sinned before thee.&#xA;3 For thou remainest for ever, and shall we perish everlastingly?&#xA;4 O Lord Almighty, the God of Israel, hear now the prayer of the dead of Israel, and of their children, that have sinned before thee, and have not hearkened to the voice of the Lord their God, wherefore evils have cleaved fast to us.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 36</title>
      <link>http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/57-baruch/chap036/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:32 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/57-baruch/chap036/</guid>
      <description>7 They shall not pity the widow, nor do good to the fatherless.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 4</title>
      <link>http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/57-baruch/chap004/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:32 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/57-baruch/chap004/</guid>
      <description>1 This is the book of the commandments of God, and the law, that is for ever: all they that keep it, shall come to life: but they that have forsaken it, to death.&#xA;2 Return, O Jacob, and take hold of it, walk in the way by its brightness, in the presence of the light thereof.&#xA;3 Give not thy honour to another, nor thy dignity to a strange nation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 5</title>
      <link>http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/57-baruch/chap005/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:32 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/57-baruch/chap005/</guid>
      <description>1 Put off, O Jerusalem, the garment of thy mourning, and affliction: and put on the beauty, and honour of that everlasting glory which thou hast from God.&#xA;2 God will clothe thee with the double garment of justice, and will set a crown on thy head of everlasting honour.&#xA;3 For God will shew his brightness in thee, to every one under heaven.&#xA;4 For thy name shall be named to thee by God for ever: the peace of justice, and honour of piety.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 6</title>
      <link>http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/57-baruch/chap006/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:32 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/57-baruch/chap006/</guid>
      <description>38 Their gods, of wood, and of stone, and of gold, and of silver, are like the stones that are hewn out of the mountains: and they that worship them shall be confounded.&#xA;39 How then is it to be supposed, or to be said, that they are gods?&#xA;40 Even the Chaldeans themselves dishonor them: who when they hear of one dumb that cannot speak, they present him to Bel, entreating him, that he may speak.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
