<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>1 Timothy on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/15-1-timothy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 1 Timothy on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:36 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/15-1-timothy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 1</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/15-1-timothy/chap001/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:36 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/15-1-timothy/chap001/</guid>
      <description>1 Paul, an apostle of Jesus Christ, according to the commandment of God our Saviour and Christ Jesus our hope:&#xA;2 To Timothy, his beloved son in faith. Grace, mercy and peace, from God the Father and from Christ Jesus our Lord.&#xA;3 As I desired thee to remain at Ephesus when I went into Macedonia, that thou mightest charge some not to teach otherwise:&#xA;4 Not to give heed to fables and endless genealogies, which furnish questions rather than the edification of God which is in faith.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 2</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/15-1-timothy/chap002/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:36 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/15-1-timothy/chap002/</guid>
      <description>1 I desire therefore, first of all, that supplications, prayers, intercessions and thanksgivings be made for all men:&#xA;2 For kings and for all that are in high station: that we may lead a quiet and a peaceable life in all piety and chastity.&#xA;3 For this is good and acceptable in the sight of God our Saviour,&#xA;4 Who will have all men to be saved and to come to the knowledge of the truth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 3</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/15-1-timothy/chap003/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:36 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/15-1-timothy/chap003/</guid>
      <description>1 A faithful saying: If a man desire the office of a bishop, he desireth good work.&#xA;2 It behoveth therefore a bishop to be blameless, the husband of one wife, sober, prudent, of good behaviour, chaste, given to hospitality, a teacher,&#xA;3 Not given to wine, no striker, but modest, not quarrelsome, not covetous, but&#xA;4 One that ruleth well his own house, having his children in subjection with all chastity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 4</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/15-1-timothy/chap004/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:36 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/15-1-timothy/chap004/</guid>
      <description>1 Now the Spirit manifestly saith that in the last times some shall depart from the faith, giving heed to spirits of error and doctrines of devils,&#xA;2 Speaking lies in hypocrisy and having their conscience seared,&#xA;3 Forbidding to marry, to abstain from meats, which God hath created to be received with thanksgiving by the faithful and by them that have known the truth.&#xA;4 For every creature of God is good, and nothing to be rejected that is received with thanksgiving:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 5</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/15-1-timothy/chap005/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:36 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/15-1-timothy/chap005/</guid>
      <description>1 An ancient man rebuke not, but entreat him as a father: young men, as brethren:&#xA;2 Old women, as mothers: young women, as sisters, in all chastity.&#xA;3 Honour widows that are widows indeed.&#xA;4 But if any widow have children or grandchildren, let her learn first to govern her own house and to make a return of duty to her parents; for this is acceptable before God.&#xA;5 But she that is a widow indeed, and desolate, let her trust in God and continue in supplications and prayers night and day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 6</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/15-1-timothy/chap006/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:36 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/15-1-timothy/chap006/</guid>
      <description>1 Whosoever are servants under the yoke, let them count their masters worthy of all honour; lest the name of the Lord and his doctrine be blasphemed.&#xA;2 But they that have believing masters, let them not despise them, because they are brethren; but serve them the rather, because they are faithful and beloved, who are partakers of the benefit. These things teach and exhort.&#xA;3 If any man teach otherwise and consent not to the sound words of our Lord Jesus Christ and to that doctrine which is according to godliness,</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
