<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Luke on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</title>
    <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/03-luke/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Luke on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:23 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/03-luke/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 1</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/03-luke/chap001/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:23 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/03-luke/chap001/</guid>
      <description>1 Forasmuch as many have taken in hand to set forth in order a narration of the things that have been accomplished among us,&#xA;2 According as they have delivered them unto us, who from the beginning were eyewitnesses and ministers of the word:&#xA;3 It seemed good to me also, having diligently attained to all things from the beginning, to write to thee in order, most excellent Theophilus,&#xA;4 That thou mayest know the verity of those words in which thou hast been instructed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 10</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/03-luke/chap010/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:23 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/03-luke/chap010/</guid>
      <description>1 And after these things, the Lord appointed also other seventy-two. And he sent them two and two before his face into every city and place whither he himself was to come.&#xA;2 And he said to them: The harvest indeed is great, but the labourers are few. Pray ye therefore the Lord of the harvest that he send labourers into his harvest.&#xA;3 Go: Behold I send you as lambs among wolves.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 11</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/03-luke/chap011/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:23 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/03-luke/chap011/</guid>
      <description>1 And it came to pass that as he was in a certain place praying, when he ceased, one of his disciples said to him: Lord, teach us to pray, as John also taught his disciples.&#xA;2 And he said to them: When you pray, say: Father, hallowed be thy name. Thy kingdom come.&#xA;3 Give us this day our daily bread.&#xA;4 And forgive us our sins, for we also forgive every one that is indebted to us.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 12</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/03-luke/chap012/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:23 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/03-luke/chap012/</guid>
      <description>1 And when great multitudes stood about him, so that they trod one upon another, he began to say to his disciples: Beware ye of the leaven of the Pharisees, which is hypocrisy.&#xA;2 For there is nothing covered that shall not be revealed: nor hidden that shall not be known.&#xA;3 For whatsoever things you have spoken in darkness shall be published in the light: and that which you have spoken in the ear in the chambers shall be preached on the housetops.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 13</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/03-luke/chap013/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:23 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/03-luke/chap013/</guid>
      <description>1 And there were present, at that very time, some that told him of the Galileans, whose blood Pilate had mingled with their sacrifices.&#xA;2 And he answering, said to them: Think you that these Galileans were sinners above all the men of Galilee, because they suffered such things?&#xA;3 No, I say to you: but unless you shall do penance, you shall all likewise perish.&#xA;4 Or those eighteen upon whom the tower fell in Siloe and slew them: think you that they also were debtors above all the men that dwelt in Jerusalem?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 14</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/03-luke/chap014/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:23 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/03-luke/chap014/</guid>
      <description>1 And it came to pass, when Jesus went into the house of one of the Pharisees, on the sabbath day, that they watched him.&#xA;2 And behold, there was a certain man before him that had the dropsy.&#xA;3 And Jesus answering, spoke to the lawyers and Pharisees, saying: Is it lawful to heal on the sabbath day?&#xA;4 But they held their peace. But he taking him, healed him and sent him away.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 15</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/03-luke/chap015/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:23 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/03-luke/chap015/</guid>
      <description>1 Now the publicans and sinners drew near unto him to hear him.&#xA;2 And the Pharisees and the scribes murmured, saying: This man receiveth sinners and eateth with them.&#xA;3 And he spoke to them this parable, saying:&#xA;4 What man of you that hath an hundred sheep, and if he shall lose one of them, doth he not leave the ninety-nine in the desert and go after that which was lost, until he find it?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 16</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/03-luke/chap016/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:23 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/03-luke/chap016/</guid>
      <description>1 And he said also to his disciples: There was a certain rich man who had a steward: and the same was accused unto him, that he had wasted his goods.&#xA;2 And he called him and said to him: How is it that I hear this of thee? Give an account of thy stewardship: for now thou canst be steward no longer.&#xA;3 And the steward said within himself: What shall I do, because my lord taketh away from me the stewardship?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 17</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/03-luke/chap017/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:23 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/03-luke/chap017/</guid>
      <description>1 And he said to his disciples: It is impossible that scandals should not come. But woe to him through whom they come!&#xA;2 It were better for him that a millstone were hanged about his neck and he cast into the sea, than that he should scandalize one of these little ones.&#xA;3 Take heed to yourselves. If thy brother sin against thee, reprove him: and if he do penance, forgive him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 18</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/03-luke/chap018/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:23 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/03-luke/chap018/</guid>
      <description>1 And he spoke also a parable to them, that we ought always to pray and not to faint,&#xA;2 Saying: There was a judge in a certain city, who feared not God nor regarded man.&#xA;3 And there was a certain widow in that city; and she came to him, saying: Avenge me of my adversary.&#xA;4 And he would not for a long time. But afterwards he said within himself: Although I fear not God nor regard man,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 19</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/03-luke/chap019/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:23 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/03-luke/chap019/</guid>
      <description>1 And entering he walked through Jericho.&#xA;2 And behold, there was a man named Zacheus, who was the chief of the publicans: and he was rich.&#xA;3 And he sought to see Jesus who he was: and he could not for the crowd, because he was low of stature.&#xA;4 And running before, he climbed up into a sycamore tree, that he might see him: for he was to pass that way.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 2</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/03-luke/chap002/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:23 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/03-luke/chap002/</guid>
      <description>1 And it came to pass that in those days there went out a decree from Caesar Augustus that the whole world should be enrolled.&#xA;2 This enrolling was first made by Cyrinus, the governor of Syria.&#xA;3 And all went to be enrolled, every one into his own city.&#xA;4 And Joseph also went up from Galilee, out of the city of Nazareth, into Judea, to the city of David, which is called Bethlehem: because he was of the house and family of David.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 20</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/03-luke/chap020/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:23 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/03-luke/chap020/</guid>
      <description>1 And it came to pass that on one of the days, as he was teaching the people in the temple and preaching the gospel, the chief priests and the scribes, with the ancients, met together,&#xA;2 And spoke to him, saying: Tell us, by what authority dost thou these things? Or, who is he that hath given thee this authority?&#xA;3 And Jesus answering, said to them: I will also ask you one thing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 21</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/03-luke/chap021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:23 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/03-luke/chap021/</guid>
      <description>1 And looking on, he saw the rich men cast their gifts into the treasury.&#xA;2 And he saw also a certain poor widow casting in two brass mites.&#xA;3 And he said: Verily, I say to you that this poor widow hath cast in more than they all.&#xA;4 For all these have of their abundance cast into the offerings of God: but she of her want hath cast in all the living that she had.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 22</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/03-luke/chap022/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:23 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/03-luke/chap022/</guid>
      <description>1 Now the feast of unleavened bread, which is called the pasch, was at hand.&#xA;2 And the chief priests and the scribes sought how they might put Jesus to death: but they feared the people.&#xA;3 And Satan entered into Judas, who was surnamed Iscariot, one of the twelve.&#xA;4 And he went and discoursed with the chief priests and the magistrates, how he might betray him to them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 23</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/03-luke/chap023/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:23 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/03-luke/chap023/</guid>
      <description>1 And the whole multitude of them, rising up, led him to Pilate.&#xA;2 And they began to accuse him, saying: We have found this man perverting our nation and forbidding to give tribute to Caesar and saying that he is Christ the king.&#xA;3 And Pilate asked him, saying: Art thou the king of the Jews? But he answering, said: Thou sayest it.&#xA;4 And Pilate said to the chief priests and to the multitudes: I find no cause in this man.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 24</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/03-luke/chap024/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:23 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/03-luke/chap024/</guid>
      <description>1 And on the first day of the week, very early in the morning, they came to the sepulchre, bringing the spices which they had prepared.&#xA;2 And they found the stone rolled back from the sepulchre.&#xA;3 And going in, they found not the body of the Lord Jesus.&#xA;4 And it came to pass, as they were astonished in their mind at this, behold, two men stood by them, in shining apparel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 3</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/03-luke/chap003/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:23 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/03-luke/chap003/</guid>
      <description>1 Now in the fifteenth year of the reign of Tiberius Caesar, Pontius Pilate being governor of Judea, and Herod being tetrarch of Galilee, and Philip his brother tetrarch of Iturea and the country of Trachonitis, and Lysanias tetrarch of Abilina:&#xA;2 Under the high priests Anna and Caiphas: the word of the Lord was made unto John, the son of Zachary, in the desert.&#xA;3 And he came into all the country about the Jordan, preaching the baptism of penance for the remission of sins.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 4</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/03-luke/chap004/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:23 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/03-luke/chap004/</guid>
      <description>1 And Jesus being full of the Holy Ghost, returned from the Jordan and was led the by the spirit into the desert,&#xA;2 For the space of forty days, and was tempted by the devil. And he ate nothing in those days. And when they were ended, he was hungry.&#xA;3 And the devil said to him: If thou be the Son of God, say to this stone that it be made bread.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 5</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/03-luke/chap005/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:23 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/03-luke/chap005/</guid>
      <description>1 And it came to pass, that when the multitudes pressed upon him to hear the word of God, he stood by the lake of Genesareth,&#xA;2 And saw two ships standing by the lake: but the fishermen were gone out of them and were washing their nets.&#xA;3 And going into one of the ships that was Simon&amp;rsquo;s, he desired him to draw back a little from the land. And sitting, he taught the multitudes out of the ship.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 6</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/03-luke/chap006/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:23 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/03-luke/chap006/</guid>
      <description>1 And it came to pass on the second first sabbath that, as he went through the corn fields, his disciples plucked the ears and did eat, rubbing them in their hands.&#xA;2 And some of the Pharisees said to them: Why do you that which is not lawful on the sabbath days?&#xA;3 And Jesus answering them, said: Have you not read so much as this, what David did, when himself was hungry and they that were with him:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 7</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/03-luke/chap007/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:23 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/03-luke/chap007/</guid>
      <description>1 And when he had finished all his words in the hearing of the people, he entered into Capharnaum.&#xA;2 And the servant of a certain centurion who was dear to him, being sick, was ready to die.&#xA;3 And when he had heard of Jesus, he sent unto him the ancients of the Jews, desiring him to come and heal his servant.&#xA;4 And when they came to Jesus, they besought him earnestly, saying to him: He is worthy that thou shouldest do this for him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 8</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/03-luke/chap008/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:23 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/03-luke/chap008/</guid>
      <description>1 And it came to pass afterwards he travelled through the cities and towns, preaching and evangelizing the kingdom of God: and the twelve with him:&#xA;2 And certain women who had been healed of evil spirits and infirmities: Mary who is called Magdalen, out of whom seven devils were gone forth,&#xA;3 And Joanna the wife of Chusa, Herod&amp;rsquo;s steward, and Susanna and many others who ministered unto him of their substance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 9</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/03-luke/chap009/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:23 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/03-luke/chap009/</guid>
      <description>1 Then calling together the twelve apostles, he gave them power and authority over all devils and to cure diseases.&#xA;2 And he sent them to preach the kingdom of God and to heal the sick.&#xA;3 And he said to them: Take nothing for your journey, neither staff, nor scrip, nor bread, nor money; neither have two coats.&#xA;4 And whatsoever house you shall enter into, abide there and depart not from thence.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
