<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Colossians on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</title>
    <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/12-colossians/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Colossians on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:24 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/12-colossians/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 1</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/12-colossians/chap001/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:24 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/12-colossians/chap001/</guid>
      <description>1 Paul, an apostle of Jesus Christ, by the will of God, and Timothy, a brother:&#xA;2 To the saints and faithful brethren in Christ Jesus who are at Colossa.&#xA;3 Grace be to you and peace, from God our Father and from the Lord Jesus Christ. We give thanks to God and the Father of our Lord Jesus Christ, praying always for you.&#xA;4 Hearing your faith in Christ Jesus and the love which you have towards all the saints.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 2</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/12-colossians/chap002/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:24 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/12-colossians/chap002/</guid>
      <description>1 For I would have you know what manner of care I have for you and for them that are at Laodicea and whosoever have not seen my face in the flesh:&#xA;2 That their hearts may be comforted, being instructed in charity and unto all riches of fulness of understanding, unto the knowledge of the mystery of God the Father and of Christ Jesus:&#xA;3 In whom are hid all the treasures of wisdom and knowledge.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 3</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/12-colossians/chap003/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:24 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/12-colossians/chap003/</guid>
      <description>1 Therefore if you be risen with Christ, seek the things that are above, where Christ is sitting at the right hand of God.&#xA;2 Mind the things that are above, not the things that are upon the earth.&#xA;3 For you are dead: and your life is hid with Christ in God.&#xA;4 When Christ shall appear, who is your life, then you also shall appear with him in glory.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 4</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/12-colossians/chap004/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:24 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/12-colossians/chap004/</guid>
      <description>1 Masters, do to your servants that which is just and equal: knowing that you also have a master in heaven.&#xA;2 Be instant in prayer: watching in it with thanksgiving.&#xA;3 Praying withal for us also, that God may open unto us a door of speech to speak the mystery of Christ (for which also I am bound):&#xA;4 That I may make it manifest as I ought to speak.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
