<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>1 Maccabees on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/72-1-maccabees/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 1 Maccabees on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:34 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/72-1-maccabees/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 1</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/72-1-maccabees/chap001/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:34 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/72-1-maccabees/chap001/</guid>
      <description>50 Grant us peace, and let the Jews cease from assaulting us, and the city.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 10</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/72-1-maccabees/chap010/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:34 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/72-1-maccabees/chap010/</guid>
      <description>1 Now in the hundred and sixtieth year, Alexander, the son of Antiochus, surnamed the Illustrious, came up and took Ptolemais, and they received him, and he reigned there.&#xA;2 And king Demetrius heard of it, and gathered together an exceeding great army, and went forth against him to fight.&#xA;3 And Demetrius sent a letter to Jonathan, with peaceable words, to magnify him.&#xA;4 For he said: Let us first make a peace with him, before he make one with Alexander against us.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 11</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/72-1-maccabees/chap011/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:34 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/72-1-maccabees/chap011/</guid>
      <description>51 And they threw down their arms, and made peace, and the Jews were glorified in the sight of the king, and in the sight of all that were in his realm, and were renowned throughout the kingdom, and returned to Jerusalem with many spoils.&#xA;52 So king Demetrius sat in the throne of his kingdom: and the land was quiet before him.&#xA;53 And he falsified all whatsoever he had said, and alienated himself from Jonathan, and did not reward him according to the benefits he had received from him, but gave him great trouble.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 12</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/72-1-maccabees/chap012/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:34 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/72-1-maccabees/chap012/</guid>
      <description>1 And Jonathan saw that the time served him, and he chose certain men, and sent them to Rome, to confirm and to renew the amity with them:&#xA;2 And he sent letters to the Spartans, and to other places, according to the same form.&#xA;3 And they went to Rome, and entered into the senate house, and said: Jonathan, the high priest, and the nation of the Jews, have sent us to renew the amity, and alliance, as it was before.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 13</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/72-1-maccabees/chap013/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:34 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/72-1-maccabees/chap013/</guid>
      <description>1 Now Simon heard that Tryphon was gathering together a very great army to invade the land of Juda, and to destroy it.&#xA;2 And seeing that the people was in dread and in fear, he went up to Jerusalem, and assembled the people,&#xA;3 And exhorted them, saying: You know what great battles I and my brethren, and the house of my father, have fought for the laws, and the sanctuary, and the distresses that we have seen:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 14</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/72-1-maccabees/chap014/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:34 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/72-1-maccabees/chap014/</guid>
      <description>1 In the year one hundred and seventy-two king Demetrius assembled his army, and went into Media to get him succours to fight against Tryphon.&#xA;2 And Arsaces, the king of Persia and Media, heard that Demetrius was entered within his borders, and he sent one of his princes to take him alive, and bring him to him.&#xA;3 And he went, and defeated the army of Demetrius: and took him, and brought him to Arsaces, and he put him into custody.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 15</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/72-1-maccabees/chap015/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:34 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/72-1-maccabees/chap015/</guid>
      <description>1 And king Antiochus, the son of Demetrius, sent letters from the isles of the sea to Simon, the priest, and prince of the nation of the Jews, and to all the people:&#xA;2 And the contents were these: King Antiochus to Simon, the high priest, and to the nation of the Jews, greeting.&#xA;3 Forasmuch as certain pestilent men have usurped the kingdom of our fathers, and my purpose is to challenge the kingdom, and to restore it to its former estate; and I have chosen a great army, and have built ships of war.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 16</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/72-1-maccabees/chap016/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:34 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/72-1-maccabees/chap016/</guid>
      <description>1 Then John came up from Gazara, and told Simon, his father, what Cendebeus had done against their people.&#xA;2 And Simon called his two eldest sons, Judas and John, and said to them: I and my brethren, and my father&amp;rsquo;s house, have fought against the enemies of Israel from our youth even to this day: and things have prospered so well in our hands, that we have delivered Israel oftentimes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 2</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/72-1-maccabees/chap002/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:34 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/72-1-maccabees/chap002/</guid>
      <description>1 In those days arose Mathathias, the son of John, the son of Simeon, a priest of the sons of Joarib, from Jerusalem, and he abode in the mountain of Modin:&#xA;2 And he had five sons: John, who was surnamed Gaddis:&#xA;3 And Simon, who was surnamed Thasi;&#xA;4 And Judas, who was called Machabeus;&#xA;5 And Eleazar, who was surnamed Abaron; and Jonathan, who was surnamed Apphus.&#xA;6 These saw the evils that were done in the people of Juda, and in Jerusalem.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 3</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/72-1-maccabees/chap003/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:34 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/72-1-maccabees/chap003/</guid>
      <description>1 Then his son Judas, called Machabeus, rose up in his stead.&#xA;2 And all his brethren helped him, and all they that had joined themselves to his father, and they fought with cheerfulness the battle of Israel.&#xA;3 And he got his people great honour, and put on a breastplate as a giant, and girt his warlike armour about him in battles, and protected the camp with his sword.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 4</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/72-1-maccabees/chap004/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:34 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/72-1-maccabees/chap004/</guid>
      <description>1 Then Gorgias took five thousand men, and a thousand of the best horsemen; and they removed out of the camp by night.&#xA;2 That they might come upon the camp of the Jews and strike them suddenly: and the men that were of the castle were their guides.&#xA;3 And Judas heard of it, and rose up, he and the valiant men, to attack the king&amp;rsquo;s forces that were in Emmaus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 5</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/72-1-maccabees/chap005/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:34 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/72-1-maccabees/chap005/</guid>
      <description>1 Now it came to pass, when the nations round about heard that the altar and the sanctuary were built up, as before, that they were exceeding angry.&#xA;2 And they thought to destroy the generation of Jacob that were among them, and they began to kill some of the people, and to persecute them.&#xA;3 Then Judas fought against the children of Esau in Idumea, and them that were in Acrabathane: because they beset the Israelites round about, and he made a great slaughter of them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 6</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/72-1-maccabees/chap006/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:34 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/72-1-maccabees/chap006/</guid>
      <description>1 Now king Antiochus was going through the higher countries, and he heard that the city of Elymais in Persia, was greatly renowned, and abounding in silver and gold,&#xA;2 And that there was in it a temple exceeding rich; and coverings of gold, and breastplates, and shields, which king Alexander, son of Philip, the Macedonian, that reigned first in Greece, had left there.&#xA;3 So he came, and sought to take the city and to pillage it; but he was not able, because the design was known to them that were in the city.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 7</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/72-1-maccabees/chap007/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:34 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/72-1-maccabees/chap007/</guid>
      <description>1 In the hundred and fifty-first year, Demetrius, the son of Seleucus, departed from the city of Rome, and came up with few men into a city of the sea coast, and reigned there.&#xA;2 And it came to pass as he entered into the house of the kingdom of his fathers, that the army seized upon Antiochus, and Lysias, to bring them unto him.&#xA;3 And when he knew it, he said: Let me not see their face.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 8</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/72-1-maccabees/chap008/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:34 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/72-1-maccabees/chap008/</guid>
      <description>1 Now Judas heard of the fame of the Romans, that they are powerful and strong, and willingly agree to all things that are requested of them: and that whosoever have come to them, they have made amity with them, and that they are mighty in power.&#xA;2 And they heard of their battles, and their noble acts which they had done in Galatia, how they had conquered them, and brought them under tribute:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 9</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/72-1-maccabees/chap009/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:34 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/72-1-maccabees/chap009/</guid>
      <description>1 In the mean time, when Demetrius heard that Nicanor and his army were fallen in battle, he sent again Bacchides and Alcimus into Judea; and the right wing of his army with them.&#xA;2 And they took the road that leadeth to Galgal, and they camped in Masaloth, which is in Arabella: and they made themselves masters of it, and slew many people.&#xA;3 In the first month of the hundred and fifty-second year they brought the army to Jerusalem:</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
