<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ezekiel on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</title>
    <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/58-ezekiel/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ezekiel on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/58-ezekiel/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 10</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/58-ezekiel/chap010/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/58-ezekiel/chap010/</guid>
      <description>1 And I saw and behold in the firmament that was over the heads of the cherubims, there appeared over them as it were the sapphire stone, as the appearance of the likeness of a throne.&#xA;2 And he spoke to the man, that was clothed with linen, and said: Go in between the wheels that are under the cherubims and fill thy hand with the coals of fire that are between the cherubims, and pour them out upon the city.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 11</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/58-ezekiel/chap011/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/58-ezekiel/chap011/</guid>
      <description>1 And the spirit lifted me up, and brought me into the east gate of the house of the Lord, which looketh towards the rising of the sun: and behold in the entry of the gate five and twenty men: and I saw in the midst of them Jezonias the son of Azur, and Pheltias the son of Banaias, princes of the people.&#xA;2 And he said to me: Son of man, these are the men that study iniquity, and frame a wicked counsel in this city,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 12</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/58-ezekiel/chap012/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/58-ezekiel/chap012/</guid>
      <description>1 And the word of the Lord came to me, saying:&#xA;2 Son of man, thou dwellest in the midst of a provoking house: who have eyes to see, and see not: and ears to hear, and hear not: for they are a provoking house.&#xA;3 Thou, therefore, O son of man, prepare thee all necessaries for removing, and remove by day into their sight: and thou shalt remove out of thy place to another place in their sight, if so be they will regard it: for they are a provoking house.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 13</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/58-ezekiel/chap013/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/58-ezekiel/chap013/</guid>
      <description>1 And the word of the Lord came to me, saying:&#xA;2 Son of man, prophesy thou against the prophets of Israel that prophesy: and thou shalt say to them that prophesy out of their own heart: Hear ye the word of the Lord:&#xA;3 Thus saith the Lord God: Woe to the foolish prophets that follow their own spirit, and see nothing.&#xA;4 Thy prophets, O Israel, were like foxes in the deserts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 14</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/58-ezekiel/chap014/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/58-ezekiel/chap014/</guid>
      <description>1 And some of the ancients of Israel came to me, and sat before me.&#xA;2 And the word of the Lord came to me, saying:&#xA;3 Son of man, these men have placed their uncleannesses in their hearts, and have set up before their face the stumblingblock of their iniquity: and shall I answer when they inquire of me?&#xA;4 Therefore speak to them, and say to them: Thus saith the Lord God: Man, man of the house of Israel that shall place his uncleannesses in his heart, and set up the stumblingblock of his iniquity before his face, and shall come to the prophet inquiring of me by him: I the Lord will answer him according to the multitude of his uncleannesses:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 15</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/58-ezekiel/chap015/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/58-ezekiel/chap015/</guid>
      <description>1 And the word of the Lord came to me, saying:&#xA;2 Son of man, what shall be made of the wood of the vine, out of all the trees of the woods that are among the trees of the forests?&#xA;3 Shall wood be taken of it, to do any work, or shall a pin be made of it for any vessel to hang thereon?&#xA;4 Behold it is cast into the fire for fuel: the fire hath consumed both ends thereof, and the midst thereof is reduced to ashes: shall it be useful for any work?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 16</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/58-ezekiel/chap016/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/58-ezekiel/chap016/</guid>
      <description>1 And the word of the Lord came to me, saying:&#xA;2 Son of man, make known to Jerusalem her abominations.&#xA;3 And thou shalt say: Thus saith the Lord God to Jerusalem: Thy root, and thy nativity is of the land of Chanaan, thy father was an Amorrhite, and thy mother a Cethite.&#xA;4 And when thou wast born, in the day of thy nativity thy navel was not cut, neither wast thou washed with water for thy health, nor salted with salt, nor swaddled with clouts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 17</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/58-ezekiel/chap017/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/58-ezekiel/chap017/</guid>
      <description>1 And the word of the Lord came to me, saying:&#xA;2 Son of man, put forth a riddle, and speak a parable to the house of Israel,&#xA;3 And say: Thus saith the Lord God; A large eagle with great wings, long-limbed, full of feathers, and of variety, came to Libanus, and took away the marrow of the cedar.&#xA;4 He cropped off the top of the twigs thereof: and carried it away into the land of Chanaan, and he set it in a city of merchants.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 18</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/58-ezekiel/chap018/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/58-ezekiel/chap018/</guid>
      <description>1 And the word of the Lord came to me, saying: What is the meaning?&#xA;2 That you use among you this parable as a proverb in the land of Israel, saying: The fathers have eaten sour grapes, and the teeth of the children are set on edge.&#xA;3 As I live, saith the Lord God, this parable shall be no more to you a proverb in Israel.&#xA;4 Behold all souls are mine: as the soul of the father, so also the soul of the son is mine: the soul that sinneth, the same shall die.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 19</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/58-ezekiel/chap019/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/58-ezekiel/chap019/</guid>
      <description>1 Moreover take thou up a lamentation for the princes of Israel,&#xA;2 And say: Why did thy mother the lioness lie down among the lions, and bring up her whelps in the midst of young lions?&#xA;3 And she brought out one of her whelps, and he became a lion: and he learned to catch the prey, and to devour men.&#xA;4 And the nations heard of him, and took him, but not without receiving wounds: and they brought him in chains into the land of Egypt.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 2</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/58-ezekiel/chap002/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/58-ezekiel/chap002/</guid>
      <description>1 This was the vision of the likeness of the glory of the Lord, and I saw, and I fell upon my face, and I heard the voice of one that spoke, and he said to me: Son of man, stand upon thy feet, and I will speak to thee.&#xA;2 And the spirit entered into me after that he spoke to me, and he set me upon my feet: and I heard him speaking to me,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 20</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/58-ezekiel/chap020/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/58-ezekiel/chap020/</guid>
      <description>1 And it came to pass in the seventh year, in the fifth month, the tenth day of the month: there came men of the ancients of Israel to inquire of the Lord, and they sat before me.&#xA;2 And the word of the Lord came to me, saying:&#xA;3 Son of man, speak to the ancients of Israel and say to them: Thus saith the Lord God: Are you come to inquire of me?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 21</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/58-ezekiel/chap021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/58-ezekiel/chap021/</guid>
      <description>1 And the word of the Lord came to me, saying:&#xA;2 Son of man, set thy face toward Jerusalem, and let thy speech flow towards the holy places, and prophesy against the land of Israel:&#xA;3 And say to the land of Israel, Thus saith the Lord God: Behold I come against thee, and I will draw forth my sword out of its sheath, and will cut off in thee the just, and the wicked.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 22</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/58-ezekiel/chap022/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/58-ezekiel/chap022/</guid>
      <description>1 And the word of the Lord came to me, saying:&#xA;2 And thou son of man, dost thou not judge, dost thou not judge the city of blood?&#xA;3 And thou shalt shew her all her abominations, and shalt say: Thus saith the Lord God: This is the city that sheddeth blood in the midst of her, that her time may come: and that hath made idols against herself, to defile herself.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 23</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/58-ezekiel/chap023/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/58-ezekiel/chap023/</guid>
      <description>1 And the word of the Lord came to me, saying:&#xA;2 Son of man, there were two women, daughters of one mother.&#xA;3 And they committed fornication in Egypt, in their youth they committed fornication: there were their breasts pressed down, and the teats of their virginity were bruised.&#xA;4 And their names were Oolla the elder, and Ooliba her younger sister: and I took them, and they bore sons and daughters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 24</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/58-ezekiel/chap024/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/58-ezekiel/chap024/</guid>
      <description>1 And the word of the Lord came to me in the ninth year, in the tenth month, the tenth day of the month, saying:&#xA;2 Son of man, write thee the name of this day, on which the king of Babylon hath set himself against Jerusalem to day.&#xA;3 And thou shalt speak by a figure a parable to the provoking house, and say to them: Thus saith the Lord God: Set on a pot, set it on, I say, and put water in it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 25</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/58-ezekiel/chap025/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/58-ezekiel/chap025/</guid>
      <description>1 And the word of the Lord came to me, saying:&#xA;2 Son of man, set thy face against the children of Ammon, and thou shalt prophesy of them.&#xA;3 And thou shalt say to the children of Ammon: Hear ye the word of the Lord God: Thus saith the Lord God: Because thou hast said: Ha, ha, upon my sanctuary, because it was profaned: and upon the land of Israel, because it was laid waste: and upon the house of Juda, because they are led into captivity:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 26</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/58-ezekiel/chap026/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/58-ezekiel/chap026/</guid>
      <description>1 And it came to pass in the eleventh year, the first day of the month, that the word of the Lord came to me, saying:&#xA;2 Son of man, because Tyre hath said of Jerusalem: Aha, the gates of the people are broken, she is turned to me: I shall be filled, now she is laid waste.&#xA;3 Therefore thus saith the Lord God: Behold I come against thee, O Tyre, and I will cause many nations to come up to thee, as the waves of the sea rise up.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 27</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/58-ezekiel/chap027/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/58-ezekiel/chap027/</guid>
      <description>1 And the word of the Lord came to me, saying:&#xA;2 Thou therefore, O son of man, take up a lamentation for Tyre:&#xA;3 And say to Tyre that dwelleth at the entry of the sea, being the mart of the people for many islands: Thus saith the Lord God: O Tyre, thou hast said: I am of perfect beauty,&#xA;4 And situate in the heart of the sea. Thy neighbours, that built thee, have perfected thy beauty:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 28</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/58-ezekiel/chap028/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/58-ezekiel/chap028/</guid>
      <description>1 And the word of the Lord came to me, saying:&#xA;2 Son of man, say to the prince of Tyre: Thus saith the Lord God: Because thy heart is lifted up, and thou hast said: I am God, and I sit in the chair of God in the heart of the sea: whereas thou art a man, and not God: and hast set thy heart as if it were the heart of God.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 29</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/58-ezekiel/chap029/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/58-ezekiel/chap029/</guid>
      <description>1 In the tenth year, the tenth month, the eleventh day of the month, the word of the Lord came to me, saying:&#xA;2 Son of man, set thy face against Pharao king of Egypt: and thou shalt prophesy of him, and of all Egypt:&#xA;3 Speak, and say: Thus saith the Lord God: Behold, I come against thee, Pharao king of Egypt, thou great dragon that liest in the midst of thy rivers, and sayest: The river is mine, and I made myself.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 3</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/58-ezekiel/chap003/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/58-ezekiel/chap003/</guid>
      <description>1 And he said to me: Son of man, eat all that thou shalt find: eat this book, and go speak to the children of Israel.&#xA;2 And I opened my mouth, and he caused me to eat that book:&#xA;3 And he said to me: Son of man, thy belly shall eat, and thy bowels shall be filled with this book, which I give thee, and I did eat it: and it was sweet as honey in my mouth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 30</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/58-ezekiel/chap030/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/58-ezekiel/chap030/</guid>
      <description>1 And the word of the Lord came to me, saying:&#xA;2 Son of man prophesy, and say: Thus saith the Lord God: Howl ye, Woe, woe to the day:&#xA;3 For the day is near, yea the day of the Lord is near: a cloudy day, it shall be the time of the nations.&#xA;4 And the sword shall come upon Egypt: and there shall be dread in Ethiopia, when the wounded shall fall in Egypt, and the multitude thereof shall be taken away, and the foundations thereof shall be destroyed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 31</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/58-ezekiel/chap031/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/58-ezekiel/chap031/</guid>
      <description>1 And it came to pass, in the eleventh year, the third month the first day of the month, that the word of the Lord came to me, saying:&#xA;2 Son of man, speak to Pharao king of Egypt, and to his people: To whom art thou like in thy greatness?&#xA;3 Behold, the Assyrian like a cedar in Libanus, with fair branches, and full of leaves, of a high stature, and his top was elevated among the thick boughs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 32</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/58-ezekiel/chap032/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/58-ezekiel/chap032/</guid>
      <description>1 And it came to pass in the twelfth year, in the twelfth month, in the first day of the month, that the word of the Lord came to me, saying:&#xA;2 Son of man, take up a lamentation for Pharao the king of Egypt, and say to him: Thou art like the lion of the nations, and the dragon that is in the sea: and thou didst push with the horn in thy rivers, and didst trouble the waters with thy feet, and didst trample upon their streams.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 33</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/58-ezekiel/chap033/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/58-ezekiel/chap033/</guid>
      <description>1 And the word of the Lord came to me, saying:&#xA;2 Son of man, speak to the children of thy people, and say to them: When I bring the sword upon a land, if the people of the land take a man, one of their meanest, and make him a watchman over them:&#xA;3 And he sees the sword coming upon the land, and sound the trumpet, and tell the people:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 34</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/58-ezekiel/chap034/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/58-ezekiel/chap034/</guid>
      <description>1 And the word of the Lord came to me, it saying:&#xA;2 Son of man, prophesy concerning the shepherds of Israel: prophesy, and say to the shepherds: Thus saith the Lord God: Woe to the shepherds of Israel, that fed themselves: should not the flocks be fed by the shepherds?&#xA;3 You ate the milk, and you clothed yourselves with the wool, and you killed that which was fat: but my flock you did not feed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 35</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/58-ezekiel/chap035/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/58-ezekiel/chap035/</guid>
      <description>1 And the word of the Lord came to me, saying:&#xA;2 Son of man, set thy face against mount Seir, and prophesy concerning it, and say to it:&#xA;3 Thus saith the Lord God: Behold I come against thee, mount Seir, and I will stretch forth my hand upon thee, and I will make thee desolate and waste.&#xA;4 I will destroy thy cities, and thou shalt be desolate: and thou shalt know that I am the Lord.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 36</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/58-ezekiel/chap036/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/58-ezekiel/chap036/</guid>
      <description>1 And thou son of man, prophesy to the mountains of Israel, and say: Ye mountains of Israel, hear the word of the Lord:&#xA;2 Thus saith the Lord God: Because the enemy hath said to you: Aha, the everlasting heights are given to us for an inheritance.&#xA;3 Therefore prophesy, and say: Thus saith the Lord God: Because you have been desolate, and trodden under foot on every side, and made an inheritance to the rest of the nations, and are become the subject of the talk, and the reproach of the people:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 37</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/58-ezekiel/chap037/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/58-ezekiel/chap037/</guid>
      <description>1 The hand of the Lord was upon me, and brought me forth in the spirit of the Lord: and set me down in the midst of a plain that was full of bones.&#xA;2 And he led me about through them on every side: now they were very many upon the face of the plain, and they were exceeding dry.&#xA;3 And he said to me: Son of man, dost thou think these bones shall live and I answered: O Lord God, thou knowest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 38</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/58-ezekiel/chap038/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/58-ezekiel/chap038/</guid>
      <description>1 And the word of the Lord came to me, saying:&#xA;2 Son of man, set thy face against Gog, the land of Magog, the chief prince of Mosoch and Thubal: and prophesy of him,&#xA;3 And say to him: Thus saith the Lord God: Behold, I come against thee, O Gog, the chief prince of Mosoch and Thubal.&#xA;4 And I will turn thee about, and I will put a bit in thy jaws: and I will bring thee forth, and all thy army, horses and horsemen all clothed with coats of mail, a great multitude, armed with spears and shields and swords.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 39</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/58-ezekiel/chap039/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/58-ezekiel/chap039/</guid>
      <description>1 And thou, son of man, prophesy against Gog, and say: Thus saith the Lord God: Behold, I come against thee, O Gog, the chief prince of Mosoch and Thubal.&#xA;2 And I will turn thee round, and I will lead thee out, and will make thee go up from the northern parts: and will bring thee upon the mountains of Israel.&#xA;3 And I will break thy bow in thy left hand, and I will cause thy arrows to fall out of thy right hand.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 4</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/58-ezekiel/chap004/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/58-ezekiel/chap004/</guid>
      <description>1 And thou, O son of man, take thee a tile, and lay it before thee: and draw upon it the plan of the city of Jerusalem.&#xA;2 And lay siege against it, and build forts, and cast up a mount, and set a camp against it, and place battering rams round about it.&#xA;3 And take unto thee an iron pan, and set it for a wall of iron between thee and the city: and set thy face resolutely against it, and it shall be besieged, and thou shalt lay siege against it: it is a sign to the house of Israel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 40</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/58-ezekiel/chap040/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/58-ezekiel/chap040/</guid>
      <description>1 In the five and twentieth year of our captivity, in the beginning of the year, the tenth day of the month, the fourteenth year after the city was destroyed: in the selfsame day the hand of the Lord was upon me, and he brought me thither.&#xA;2 In the visions of God he brought me into the land of Israel, and set me upon a very high mountain: upon which there was as the building of a city, bending towards the south.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 41</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/58-ezekiel/chap041/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/58-ezekiel/chap041/</guid>
      <description>1 And he brought me into the temple, and he measured the fronts six cubits broad on this side, and six cubits on that side, the breadth of the tabernacle.&#xA;2 And the breadth of the gate was ten cubits: and the sides of the gate five cubits on this side, and five cubits on that side: and he measured the length thereof forty cubits, and the breadth twenty cubits.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 42</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/58-ezekiel/chap042/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/58-ezekiel/chap042/</guid>
      <description>1 And he brought me forth into the outward court by the way that leadeth to the north, and he brought me into the chamber that was over against the separate building, and over against the house toward the north.&#xA;2 In the face of the north door was the length of hundred cubits, and the breadth of fifty cubits.&#xA;3 Over against the twenty cubits of the inner court, and over against the pavement of the outward court that was paved with stone, where there was a gallery joined to a triple gallery.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 43</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/58-ezekiel/chap043/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/58-ezekiel/chap043/</guid>
      <description>1 And he brought me to the gate that looked towards the east.&#xA;2 And behold the glory of the God of Israel came in by the way of the east: and his voice was like the noise of many waters, and the earth shone with his majesty.&#xA;3 And I saw the vision according to the appearance which I had seen when he came to destroy the city: and the appearance was according to the vision which I had seen by the river Chobar: and I fell upon my face.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 44</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/58-ezekiel/chap044/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/58-ezekiel/chap044/</guid>
      <description>1 And he brought me back to the way of the gate of the outward sanctuary, which looked towards the east: and it was shut.&#xA;2 And the Lord said to me: This gate shall be shut, it shall not be opened, and no man shall pass through it: because the Lord the God of Israel hath entered in by it, and it shall be shut&#xA;3 For the prince. The prince himself shall sit in it, to eat bread before the Lord: he shall enter in by the way of the porch of the gate, and shall go out by the same way.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 45</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/58-ezekiel/chap045/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/58-ezekiel/chap045/</guid>
      <description>1 And when you shall begin to divide the land by lot, separate ye firstfruits to the Lord, a portion of the land to be holy, in length twenty-five thousand and in breadth ten thousand: it shall be holy in all the borders thereof round about.&#xA;2 And there shall be for the sanctuary on every side five hundred by five hundred, foursquare round about: and fifty cubits for the suburbs thereof round about.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 46</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/58-ezekiel/chap046/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/58-ezekiel/chap046/</guid>
      <description>1 Thus saith the Lord God: The gate of the inner court that looketh toward the east, shall be shut the six days, on which work is done; but on the sabbath day it shall be opened, yea and on the day of the new moon it shall be opened.&#xA;2 And the prince shall enter by the way of the porch of the gate from without, and he shall stand at the threshold of the gate: and the priests shall offer his holocaust, and his peace offerings: and he shall adore upon the threshold of the gate, and shall go out: but the gate shall not be shut till the evening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 47</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/58-ezekiel/chap047/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/58-ezekiel/chap047/</guid>
      <description>1 And he brought me again to the gate of the house, and behold waters issued out from under the threshold of the house toward the east: for the forefront of the house looked toward the east: but the waters came down to the right side of the temple to the south part of the altar.&#xA;2 And he led me out by the way of the north gate, and he caused me to turn to the way without the outward gate to the way that looked toward the east: and behold there ran out waters on the right side.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 48</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/58-ezekiel/chap048/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/58-ezekiel/chap048/</guid>
      <description>1 And these are the names of the tribes from the borders of the north, by the way of Hethalon, as they go to Emath, the court of Enan the border of Damascus northward, by the way off Emath. And from the east side thereof to the sea shall be one portion for Dan.&#xA;2 And by the border of Dan, from the east side even to the side of the sea, one portion for Aser:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 5</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/58-ezekiel/chap005/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/58-ezekiel/chap005/</guid>
      <description>1 And thou, son of man, take thee a sharp knife that shaveth the hair: and cause it to pass over thy head, and over thy beard: and take thee a balance to weigh in, and divide the hair.&#xA;2 A third part thou shalt burn with fire in the midst of the city, according to the fulfilling of the days of the siege: and thou shalt take a third part, and cut it in pieces with the knife all round about: and the other third part thou shalt scatter in the wind, and I will draw out the sword after them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 6</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/58-ezekiel/chap006/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/58-ezekiel/chap006/</guid>
      <description>1 And the word of the Lord came to me, saying:&#xA;2 Son of man set thy face towards the mountains of Israel, and prophesy against them.&#xA;3 And say: Ye mountains of Israel, hear the word of the Lord God: Thus saith the Lord God to the mountains, and to the hills, and to the rocks, and the valleys: Behold, I will bring upon you the sword, and I will destroy your high places.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 7</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/58-ezekiel/chap007/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/58-ezekiel/chap007/</guid>
      <description>1 And the word of the Lord came to me, saying:&#xA;2 And thou son of man, thus saith the Lord God to the land of Israel: The end is come, the end is come upon the four quarters of the land.&#xA;3 Now is an end come upon thee, and I will send my wrath upon thee, and I will judge thee according to thy ways: and I will set all thy abominations against thee.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 8</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/58-ezekiel/chap008/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/58-ezekiel/chap008/</guid>
      <description>1 And it came to pass in the sixth year, in the sixth month, in the fifth day of the month, as I sat in my house, and the ancients of Juda sat before me, that the hand of the Lord God fell there upon me.&#xA;2 And I saw, and behold a likeness as the appearance of fire: from the appearance of his loins, and downward, fire: and from his loins, and upward, as the appearance of brightness, as the appearance of amber.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 9</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/58-ezekiel/chap009/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/58-ezekiel/chap009/</guid>
      <description>1 And he cried in my ears with a loud voice, saying: The visitations of the city are at hand, and every one hath a destroying weapon in his hand.&#xA;2 And behold six men came from the way of the upper gate, which looketh to the north: and each one had his weapon of destruction in his hand: and there was one man in the midst of them clothed with linen, with a writer&amp;rsquo;s inkhorn at his reins: and they went in, and stood by the brazen altar.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 1</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/58-ezekiel/chap001/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:32 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/58-ezekiel/chap001/</guid>
      <description>1 Now it came to pass in the thirtieth year, in the fourth month, on the fifth day of the month, when I was in the midst of the captives by the river Chobar, the heavens were opened, and I saw the visions of God.&#xA;2 On the fifth day of the month, the same was the fifth year of the captivity of king Joachin,&#xA;3 The word of the Lord came to Ezekiel the priest the son of Buzi in the land of the Chaldeans, by the river Chobar: and the hand of the Lord was there upon him.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
