<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2 Kings on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/39-2-kings/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2 Kings on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:38 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/39-2-kings/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 1</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/39-2-kings/chap001/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:38 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/39-2-kings/chap001/</guid>
      <description>1 And Moab rebelled against Israel, after the death of Achab.&#xA;2 And Ochozias fell through the lattices of his upper chamber, which he had in Samaria, and was sick: and he sent messengers, saying to them: Go, consult Beelzebub, the god of Accaron, whether I shall recover of this my illness.&#xA;3 And an angel of the Lord spoke to Elias, the Thesbite, saying: Arise, and go up to meet the messengers of the king of Samaria, and say to them: Is there not a God in Israel, that ye go to consult Beelzebub, the god of Accaron?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 10</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/39-2-kings/chap010/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:38 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/39-2-kings/chap010/</guid>
      <description>1 And Achab had seventy sons in Samaria: so Jehu wrote letters, and sent to Samaria, to the chief men of the city, and to the ancients, and to them that brought up Achab&amp;rsquo;s children, saying:&#xA;2 As soon as you receive these letters, ye that have your master&amp;rsquo;s sons, and chariots, and horses, and fenced cities, and armour,&#xA;3 Choose the best, and him that shall please you most of your master&amp;rsquo;s sons, and set him on his father&amp;rsquo;s throne, and fight for the house of your master.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 11</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/39-2-kings/chap011/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:38 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/39-2-kings/chap011/</guid>
      <description>1 Now Athalia, the mother of Ochozias, seeing that her son was dead, arose and slew all the royal seed.&#xA;2 But Josaba the daughter of king Joram, sister of Ochozias, took Joas, the son of Ochozias, and stole him from among the king&amp;rsquo;s sons that were slain, out of the bedchamber with his nurse: and hid him from the face of Athalia; so that he was not slain.&#xA;3 And he was with her six years, hid in the house of the Lord.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 12</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/39-2-kings/chap012/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:38 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/39-2-kings/chap012/</guid>
      <description>1 In the seventh year of Jehu, Joas began to reign: and he reigned forty years in Jerusalem. The name of his mother was Sebia, of Bersabee.&#xA;2 And Joas did that which was right before the Lord all the days that Joiada, the priest, taught him.&#xA;3 But yet he took not away the high places: for the people still sacrificed and burnt incense in the high places.&#xA;4 And Joas said to the priests: all the money of the sanctified things, which is brought into the temple of the Lord by those that pass, which is offered for the price of a soul, and which of their own accord, and of their own free heart, they bring into the temple of the Lord:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 13</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/39-2-kings/chap013/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:38 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/39-2-kings/chap013/</guid>
      <description>1 In the three and twentieth year of Joas son of Ochozias, king of Juda, Joachaz, the son of Jehu, reigned over Israel, in Samaria, seventeen years.&#xA;2 And he did evil before the Lord, and followed the sins of Jeroboam, the son of Nabat, who made Israel to sin; and he departed not from them.&#xA;3 And the wrath of the Lord was kindled against Israel, and he delivered them into the hand of Hazael, the king of Syria, and into the hand of Benadad, the son of Hazael, all days.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 14</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/39-2-kings/chap014/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:38 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/39-2-kings/chap014/</guid>
      <description>1 In the second year of Joas son of Joachaz, king of Israel, reigned Amasias son of Joas, king of Juda.&#xA;2 He was five and twenty years old when he began to reign; and nine and twenty years he reigned in Jerusalem; the name of his mother was Joadan, of Jerusalem.&#xA;3 And he did that which was right before the Lord, but yet not like David his father. He did according to all things that Joas his father, did:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 15</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/39-2-kings/chap015/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:38 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/39-2-kings/chap015/</guid>
      <description>1 In the seven and twentieth year of Jeroboam, king of Israel, reigned Azarias, son of Amasias, king of Juda.&#xA;2 He was sixteen years old when he began to reign, and he reigned two and fifty years in Jerusalem: the name of his mother was Jechelia, of Jerusalem.&#xA;3 And he did that which was pleasing before the Lord, according to all that his father, Amasias, had done.&#xA;4 But the high places he did not destroy, for the people sacrificed, and burnt incense in the high places.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 16</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/39-2-kings/chap016/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:38 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/39-2-kings/chap016/</guid>
      <description>1 In the seventeenth year of Phacee, the son of Romelia reigned Achaz, the son of Joatham, king of Juda.&#xA;2 Achaz was twenty years old when he began to reign, and he reigned sixteen years in Jerusalem: he did not that which was pleasing in the sight of the Lord, his God, as David, his father.&#xA;3 But he walked in the way of the kings of Israel: moreover, he consecrated also his son, making him pass through the fire, according to the idols of the nations which the Lord destroyed before the children of Israel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 17</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/39-2-kings/chap017/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:38 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/39-2-kings/chap017/</guid>
      <description>1 In the twelfth year of Achaz king of Juda, Osee the son of Ela reigned in Samaria, over Israel, nine years.&#xA;2 And he did evil before the Lord: but not as the kings of Israel that had been before him.&#xA;3 Against him came up Salmanasar, king of the Assyrians; and Osee became his servant, and paid him tribute.&#xA;4 And when the king of the Assyrians found that Osee, endeavouring to rebel, had sent messengers to Sua, the king of Egypt, that he might not pay tribute to the king of the Assyrians, as he had done every year, he besieged him, bound him, and cast him into prison.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 18</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/39-2-kings/chap018/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:38 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/39-2-kings/chap018/</guid>
      <description>1 In the third year of Osee, the son of Ela, king of Israel, reigned Ezechias, the son of Achaz, king of Juda.&#xA;2 He was five and twenty years old when he began to reign: and he reigned nine and twenty years in Jerusalem: the name of his mother was Abi, the daughter of Zacharias.&#xA;3 And he did that which was good before the Lord, according to all that David, his father, had done</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 19</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/39-2-kings/chap019/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:38 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/39-2-kings/chap019/</guid>
      <description>1 And when king Ezechias heard these words, he rent his garments, and covered himself with sackcloth, and went into the house of the Lord.&#xA;2 And he sent Eliacim, who was over the house, and Sobna, the scribe, and the ancients of the priests, covered with sackcloths, to Isaias, the prophet, the son of Amos.&#xA;3 And they said to him: Thus saith Ezechias: This day is a day of tribulation, and of rebuke, and of blasphemy: the children are come to the birth, and the woman in travail hath not strength.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 2</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/39-2-kings/chap002/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:38 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/39-2-kings/chap002/</guid>
      <description>1 And it came to pass, when the Lord would take up Elias, into heaven, by a whirlwind, that Elias and Eliseus were going from Galgal.&#xA;2 And Elias said to Eliseus: Stay thou here, because the Lord hath sent me as far as Bethel. And Eliseus said to him: As the Lord liveth, and as thy soul liveth, I will not leave thee. And when they were come down to Bethel,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 20</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/39-2-kings/chap020/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:38 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/39-2-kings/chap020/</guid>
      <description>1 In those days Ezechias was sick unto death: and Isaias, the son of Amos, the prophet, came and said to him: Thus saith the Lord God: Give charge concerning thy house, for thou shalt die, and not llve.&#xA;2 And he turned his face to the wall, and prayed to the Lord, saying:&#xA;3 I beseech thee, O Lord, remember how I have walked before thee in truth, and with a perfect heart, and have done that which is pleasing before thee.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 21</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/39-2-kings/chap021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:38 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/39-2-kings/chap021/</guid>
      <description>1 Manasses was twelve years old when he began to reign, and he reigned five and fifty years in Jerusalem: the name of his mother was Haphsiba.&#xA;2 And he did evil in the sight of the Lord, according to the idols of the nations, which the Lord destroyed from before the face of the children of Israel.&#xA;3 And he turned, and built up the high places, which Ezechias, his father, had destroyed: and he set up altars to Baal, and made groves, as Achab, the king of Israel, had done: and he adored all the host of heaven, and served them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 22</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/39-2-kings/chap022/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:38 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/39-2-kings/chap022/</guid>
      <description>1 Josias was eight years old when he began to reign: he reigned one and thirty years in Jerusalem: the name of his mother was Idida, the daughter of Hadaia, of Besecath.&#xA;2 And he did that which was right in the sight of the Lord, and walked in all the ways of David, his father: he turned not aside to the right hand, or to the left.&#xA;3 And in the eighteenth year of king Josias, the king sent Saphan, the son of Assia, the son of Messulam, the scribe of the temple of the Lord, saying to him:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 23</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/39-2-kings/chap023/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:38 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/39-2-kings/chap023/</guid>
      <description>1 And they brought the king word again what she had said. And he sent: and all the ancients of Juda and Jerusalem were assembled to him.&#xA;2 And the king went up to the temple of the Lord, and all the men of Juda, and all the inhabitants of Jerusalem with him, the priests, and the prophets, and all the people, both little and great: and in the hearing of them all he read all the words of the book of the covenant, which was found in the house of the Lord.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 24</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/39-2-kings/chap024/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:38 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/39-2-kings/chap024/</guid>
      <description>1 In his days Nabuchodonosor, king of Babylon came up, and Joakim became his servant three years: then again he rebelled against him.&#xA;2 And the Lord sent against him the rovers of the Chaldees, and the rovers of Syria, and the rovers of Moab, and the rovers of the children of Ammon: and he sent them against Juda, to destroy it, according to the word of the Lord, which he had spoken by his servants, the prophets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 25</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/39-2-kings/chap025/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:38 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/39-2-kings/chap025/</guid>
      <description>1 And it came to pass in the ninth year of his reign, in the tenth month, the tenth day of the month, that Nabuchodonosor, king of Babylon, came, he and all his army, against Jerusalem: and they surrounded it: and raised works round about it.&#xA;2 And the city was shut up and besieged till the eleventh year of king Sedecias,&#xA;3 The ninth day of the month: and a famine prevailed in the city, and there was no bread for the people of the land.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 3</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/39-2-kings/chap003/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:38 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/39-2-kings/chap003/</guid>
      <description>1 And Joram the son of Achab, reigned over Israel, in Samaria, in the eighteenth year of Josaphat, king of Juda. And he reigned twelve years.&#xA;2 And he did evil before the Lord, but not like his father and his mother: for he took away the statues of Baal, which his father had made.&#xA;3 Nevertheless, he stuck to the sins of Jeroboam, the son of Nabat, who made Israel to sin, nor did he depart from them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 4</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/39-2-kings/chap004/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:38 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/39-2-kings/chap004/</guid>
      <description>1 Now a certain woman of the wives of the prophets, cried to Eliseus, saying: Thy servant, my husband, is dead, and thou knowest that thy servant was one that feared God, and behold the creditor is come to take away my two sons to serve him.&#xA;2 And Eliseus said to her: What wilt thou have me do for thee? Tell me, what hast thou in thy house? And she answered: I, thy handmaid, have nothing in my house but a little oil, to anoint me.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 5</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/39-2-kings/chap005/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:38 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/39-2-kings/chap005/</guid>
      <description>1 Naaman, general of the army, of the king of Syria, was a great man with his master, and honourable: for by him the Lord gave deliverance to Syria: and he was a valiant man, and rich, but a leper.&#xA;2 Now there had gone out robbers from Syria, and had led away captive out of the land of Israel, a little maid, and she waited upon Naaman&amp;rsquo;s wife.&#xA;3 And she said to her mistress: I wish my master had been with the prophet that is in Samaria: he would certainly have healed him of the leprosy which he hath.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 6</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/39-2-kings/chap006/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:38 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/39-2-kings/chap006/</guid>
      <description>1 And the sons of the prophets said to Eliseus: Behold, the place where we dwell with thee is too strait for us.&#xA;2 Let us go as far as the Jordan, and take out of the wood every man a piece of timber, that we may build us there a place to dwell in. And he said: Go.&#xA;3 And one of them said: But come thou also with thy servants.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 7</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/39-2-kings/chap007/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:38 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/39-2-kings/chap007/</guid>
      <description>1 And Eliseus said: Hear ye the word of the Lord: Thus saith the Lord: Tomorrow, about this time, a bushel of fine flour shall be sold for a stater, and two bushels of barley for a stater, in the gate of Samaria.&#xA;2 Then one of the lords, upon whose hand the king leaned, answering the man of God, said: If the Lord should make flood-gates in heaven, can that possibly be which thou sayest?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 8</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/39-2-kings/chap008/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:38 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/39-2-kings/chap008/</guid>
      <description>1And Eliseus spoke to the woman, whose son he had restored to life, saying: Arise, and go thou, and thy household, and sojourn wheresoever thou canst find: for the Lord hath called a famine, and it shall come upon the land seven years.&#xA;2 And she arose, and did according to the word of the man of God: and going with her household, she sojourned in the land of the Philistines many days.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 9</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/39-2-kings/chap009/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:38 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/39-2-kings/chap009/</guid>
      <description>1 And Eliseus the prophet, called one of the sons of the prophets, and said to him: Gird up thy loins, and take this little bottle of oil in thy hand, and go to Ramoth Galaad.&#xA;2 And when thou art come thither, thou shalt see Jehu the son of Josaphat the son of Namsi: and going in, thou shalt make him rise up from amongst his brethren, and carry him into an inner chamber.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
