<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Daniel on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/59-daniel/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Daniel on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:42 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/59-daniel/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 1</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/59-daniel/chap001/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:42 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/59-daniel/chap001/</guid>
      <description>1 In the third year of the reign of Joakim, king of Juda, Nabuchodonosor, king of Babylon, came to Jerusalem, and beseiged it.&#xA;2 And the Lord delivered into his hands Joakim, the king of Juda, and part of the vessels of the house of God: and he carried them away into the land of Sennaar, to the house of his god, and the vessels he brought into the treasure house of his god.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 10</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/59-daniel/chap010/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:42 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/59-daniel/chap010/</guid>
      <description>1 In the third year of Cyrus, king of the Persians, a word was revealed to Daniel, surnamed Baltassar, and a true word, and great strength: and he understood the word: for there is need of understanding in a vision.&#xA;2 In those days I, Daniel, mourned the days of three weeks.&#xA;3 I ate no desirable bread, and neither flesh, nor wine, entered into my mouth, neither was I anointed with ointment: till the days of three weeks were accomplished.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 11</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/59-daniel/chap011/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:42 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/59-daniel/chap011/</guid>
      <description>1 And from the first year of Darius, the Mede, I stood up, that he might be strengthened, and confirmed.&#xA;2 And now I will shew thee the truth. Behold, there shall stand yet three kings in Persia, and the fourth shall be enriched exceedingly above them all: and when he shall be grown mighty by his riches, he shall stir up all against the kingdom of Greece.&#xA;3 But there shall rise up a strong king, and shall rule with great power: and he shall do what he pleaseth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 12</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/59-daniel/chap012/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:42 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/59-daniel/chap012/</guid>
      <description>1 But at that time shall Michael rise up, the great prince, who standeth for the children of thy people: and a time shall come, such as never was from the time that nations began, even until that time. And at that time shall thy people be saved, every one that shall be found written in the book.&#xA;2 And many of those that sleep in the dust of the earth, shall awake: some unto life everlasting, and others unto reproach, to see it always.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 13</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/59-daniel/chap013/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:42 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/59-daniel/chap013/</guid>
      <description>1 Now there was a man that dwelt in Babylon, and his name was Joakim:&#xA;2 And he took a wife, whose name was Susanna, the daughter of Helcias, a very beautiful woman, and one that feared God.&#xA;3 For her parents being just, had instructed their daughter according to the law of Moses.&#xA;4 Now Joakim was very rich, and had an orchard near his house: and the Jews resorted to him, because he was the most honourable of them all.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 14</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/59-daniel/chap014/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:42 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/59-daniel/chap014/</guid>
      <description>1 And Daniel was the king&amp;rsquo;s guest, and was honoured above all his friends.&#xA;2 Now the Babylonians had an idol called Bel: and there was spent upon him every day twelve great measures of fine flour, and forty sheep, and six vessels of wine.&#xA;3 The king also worshipped him, and went every day to adore him: but Daniel adored his God. And the king said to him: Why dost thou not adore Bel?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 2</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/59-daniel/chap002/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:42 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/59-daniel/chap002/</guid>
      <description>1 In the second year of the reign of Nabuchodonosor, Nabuchodonosor had a dream, and his spirit was terrified, and his dream went out of his mind.&#xA;2 Then the king commanded to call together the diviners and the wise men, and the magicians, and the Chaldeans: to declare to the king his dreams: so they came and stood before the king.&#xA;3 And the king said to them: I saw a dream: and being troubled in mind I know not what I saw.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 3</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/59-daniel/chap003/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:42 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/59-daniel/chap003/</guid>
      <description>1 King Nabuchodonosor made a statue of gold, of sixty cubits high, and six cubits broad, and he set it up in the plain of Dura, of the province of Babylon.&#xA;2 Then Nabuchodonosor, the king, sent to call together the nobles, the magistrates, and the judges, the captains, the rulers, and governors, and all the chief men of the provinces, to come to the dedication of the statue which king Nabuchodonosor had set up.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 4</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/59-daniel/chap004/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:42 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/59-daniel/chap004/</guid>
      <description>1 I, Nabuchodonosor, was at rest in my house, and flourishing in my palace:&#xA;2 I saw a dream that affrighted me: and my thoughts in my bed, and the visions of my head, troubled me.&#xA;3 Then I set forth a decree, that all the wise men of Babylon should be brought in before me, and that they should shew me the interpretation of the dream.&#xA;4 Then came in the diviners, the wise men, the Chaldeans, and the soothsayers, and I told the dream before them: but they did not shew me the interpretation thereof.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 5</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/59-daniel/chap005/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:42 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/59-daniel/chap005/</guid>
      <description>1 Baltasar, the king, made a great feast for a thousand of his nobles: and every one drank according to his age.&#xA;2 And being now drunk, he commanded that they should bring the vessels of gold and silver, which Nabuchodonosor, his father, had brought away out of the temple, that was in Jerusalem, that the king and his nobles, and his wives, and his concubines, might drink in them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 6</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/59-daniel/chap006/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:42 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/59-daniel/chap006/</guid>
      <description>1 It seemed good to Darius, and he appointed over the kingdom a hundred and twenty governors, to be over his whole kingdom.&#xA;2 And three princes over them of whom Daniel was one: that the governors might give an account to them, and the king might have no trouble.&#xA;3 And Daniel excelled all the princes, and governors: because a greater spirit of God was in him.&#xA;4 And the king thought to set him over all the kingdom; whereupon the princes, and the governors, sought to find occasion against Daniel, with regard to the king: and they could find no cause, nor suspicion, because he was faithful, and no fault, nor suspicion was found in him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 7</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/59-daniel/chap007/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:42 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/59-daniel/chap007/</guid>
      <description>1 In the first year of Baltasar, king of Babylon, Daniel saw a dream: and the vision of his head was upon his bed: and writing the dream, he comprehended it in a few words: and relating the sum of it in short, he said:&#xA;2 I saw in my vision by night, and behold the four winds of the heavens strove upon the great sea.&#xA;3 And four great beasts, different one from another, came up out of the sea.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 8</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/59-daniel/chap008/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:42 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/59-daniel/chap008/</guid>
      <description>1 In the third year of the reign of king Baltasar, a vision appeared to me. I, Daniel, after what I had seen in the beginning,&#xA;2 Saw in my vision when I was in the castle of Susa, which is in the province of Elam: and I saw in the vision that I was over the gate of Ulai.&#xA;3 And I lifted up my eyes, and saw: and behold a ram stood before the water, having two high horns, and one higher than the other, and growing up.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 9</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/59-daniel/chap009/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:42 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/59-daniel/chap009/</guid>
      <description>1 In the first year of Darius, the son of Assuerus, of the seed of the Medes, who reigned over the kingdom of the Chaldeans:&#xA;2 The first year of his reign I, Daniel, understood by books the number of the years, concerning which the word of the Lord came to Jeremias, the prophet, that seventy years should be accomplished of the desolation of Jerusalem.&#xA;3 And I set my face to the Lord, my God, to pray and make supplication with fasting, and sackcloth, and ashes.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
