<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tobit on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/44-tobit/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tobit on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/44-tobit/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 1</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/44-tobit/chap001/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/44-tobit/chap001/</guid>
      <description>1 Tobias of the tribe and city of Nephtali, (which is in the upper parts of Galilee above Naasson, beyond the way that leadeth to the west, having on the right hand the city of Sephet,)&#xA;2 When he was made captive in the days of Salmanasar king of the Assyrians, even in his captivity, forsook not the way of truth,&#xA;3 But every day gave all he could get to his brethren his fellow captives, that were of his kindred.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 10</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/44-tobit/chap010/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/44-tobit/chap010/</guid>
      <description>1 But as Tobias made longer stay upon occasion of the marriage, Tobias his father was solicitous, saying: Why thinkest thou doth my son tarry, or why is he detained there?&#xA;2 Is Gabelus dead, thinkest thou, and no man will pay him the money?&#xA;3 And he began to be exceeding sad, both he and Anna his wife with him: and they began both to weep together, because their son did not return to them on the day appointed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 11</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/44-tobit/chap011/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/44-tobit/chap011/</guid>
      <description>1 And as they were returning they came to Charan, which is in the midway to Ninive, the eleventh day.&#xA;2 And the angel said: Brother Tobias, thou knowest how thou didst leave thy father.&#xA;3 If it please thee therefore, let us go before, and let the family follow softly after us, together with thy wife, and with the beasts.&#xA;4 And as this their going pleased him, Raphael said to Tobias: Take with thee of the gall of the fish, for it will be necessary.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 12</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/44-tobit/chap012/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/44-tobit/chap012/</guid>
      <description>1 Then Tobias called to him his son and said to him: What can we give to this holy man, that is come with thee?&#xA;2 Tobias answering, said to his father: Father, what wages shall we give him? or what can be worthy of his benefits?&#xA;3 He conducted me and brought me safe again, he received the money of Gabelus, he caused me to have my wife, and he chased from her the evil spirit, he gave joy to her parents, myself he delivered from being devoured by the fish, thee also he hath made to see the light of heaven, and we are filled with all good things through him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 13</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/44-tobit/chap013/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/44-tobit/chap013/</guid>
      <description>1 And Tobias the elder opening his mouth, blessed the Lord, and said: Thou art great O Lord, for ever, and thy kingdom is unto all ages.&#xA;2 For thou scourgest, and thou savest: thou leadest down to hell, and bringest up again: and there is none that can escape thy hand.&#xA;3 Give glory to the Lord, ye children of Israel, and praise him in the sight of the Gentiles:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 14</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/44-tobit/chap014/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/44-tobit/chap014/</guid>
      <description>1 And the words of Tobias were ended. And after Tobias was restored to his sight, he lived two and forty years, and saw the children of his grandchildren.&#xA;2 And after he had lived a hundred and two years, he was buried honorably in Ninive.&#xA;3 For he was six and fifty years old when he lost the sight of his eyes, and sixty when he recovered it again.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 2</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/44-tobit/chap002/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/44-tobit/chap002/</guid>
      <description>1 But after this, when there was a festival of the Lord, and a good dinner was prepared in Tobias&amp;rsquo;s house,&#xA;2 He said to his son: Go, and bring some of our tribe that fear God, to feast with us.&#xA;3 And when he had gone, returning he told him, that one of the children of Israel lay slain in the street. And he forthwith leaped up from his place at the table, and left his dinner, and came fasting to the body.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 3</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/44-tobit/chap003/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/44-tobit/chap003/</guid>
      <description>1 Then Tobias sighed, and began to pray with tears,&#xA;2 Saying, Thou art just, O Lord, and all thy judgments are just, and all thy ways mercy, and truth, and judgment:&#xA;3 And now, O Lord, think of me, and take not revenge of my sins, neither remember my offences, nor those of my parents.&#xA;4 For we have not obeyed thy commandments, therefore are we delivered to spoil and to captivity, and death, and are made a fable, and a reproach to all nations, amongst which thou hast scattered us.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 4</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/44-tobit/chap004/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/44-tobit/chap004/</guid>
      <description>1 Therefore when Tobias thought that his prayer was heard that he might die, he called to him Tobias his son,&#xA;2 And said to him: Hear, my son, the words of my mouth, and lay them as a foundation in thy heart.&#xA;3 When God shall take my soul, thou shalt bury my body: and thou shalt honour thy mother all the days of her life:&#xA;4 For thou must be mindful what and how great perils she suffered for thee in her womb.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 5</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/44-tobit/chap005/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/44-tobit/chap005/</guid>
      <description>1 Then Tobias answered his father, and said: I will do all things, father, which thou hast commanded me.&#xA;2 But how I shall get this money, I cannot tell; he knoweth not me, and I know not him: what token shall I give him? nor did I ever know the way which leadeth thither.&#xA;3 Then his father answered him, and said: I have a note of his hand with me, which when thou shalt shew him, he will presently pay it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 6</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/44-tobit/chap006/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/44-tobit/chap006/</guid>
      <description>1 And Tobias went forward, and the dog followed him, and he lodged the first night by the river of Tigris.&#xA;2 And he went out to wash his feet, and behold a monstrous fish came up to devour him.&#xA;3 And Tobias being afraid of him, cried out with a loud voice, saying: Sir, he cometh upon me.&#xA;4 And the angel said to him: Take him by the gill, and draw him to thee.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 7</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/44-tobit/chap007/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/44-tobit/chap007/</guid>
      <description>1 And they went in to Raguel, and Raguel received them with joy.&#xA;2 And Raguel looking upon Tobias, said to Anna his wife: How like is this young man to my cousin?&#xA;3 And when he had spoken these words, he said: Whence are ye young men our brethren?&#xA;4 But they said: We are of the tribe of Nephtali, of the captivity of Ninive.&#xA;5 And Raguel said to them: Do you know Tobias my brother?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 8</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/44-tobit/chap008/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/44-tobit/chap008/</guid>
      <description>1 And after they had supped, they brought in the young man to her.&#xA;2 And Tobias remembering the angel&amp;rsquo;s word, took out of his bag part of the liver, and laid it upon burning coals.&#xA;3 Then the angel Raphael took the devil, and bound him in the desert of upper Egypt.&#xA;4 Then Tobias exhorted the virgin, and said to her: Sara, arise, and let us pray to God to day, and to morrow, and the next day: because for these three nights we are joined to God: and when the third night is over, we will be in our own wedlock.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 9</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/44-tobit/chap009/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/44-tobit/chap009/</guid>
      <description>1 Then Tobias called the angel to him, whom he took to be a man, and said to him: Brother Azarias, I pray thee hearken to my words:&#xA;2 If I should give myself to be thy servant I should not make a worthy return for thy care.&#xA;3 However, I beseech thee, to take with thee beasts and servants, and to go to Gabelus to Rages the city of the Medes: and to restore to him his note of hand, and receive of him the money, and desire him to come to my wedding.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
