<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>John on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/04-john/</link>
    <description>Recent content in John on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:24 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/04-john/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 10</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/04-john/chap010/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:24 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/04-john/chap010/</guid>
      <description>1 Amen, amen, I say to you: He that entereth not by the door into the sheepfold but climbeth up another way, the same is a thief and a robber.&#xA;2 But he that entereth in by the door is the shepherd of the sheep.&#xA;3 To him the porter openeth: and the sheep hear his voice. And he calleth his own sheep by name and leadeth them out.&#xA;4 And when he hath let out his own sheep, he goeth before them: and the sheep follow him, because they know his voice.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 11</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/04-john/chap011/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:24 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/04-john/chap011/</guid>
      <description>1 Now there was a certain man sick, named Lazarus, of Bethania, of the town of Mary and of Martha her sister.&#xA;2 (And Mary was she that anointed the Lord with ointment and wiped his feet with her hair: whose brother Lazarus was sick.)&#xA;3 His sisters therefore sent to him, saying: Lord, behold, he whom thou lovest is sick.&#xA;4 And Jesus hearing it, said to them: This sickness is not unto death, but for the glory of God: that the Son of God may be glorified by it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 12</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/04-john/chap012/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:24 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/04-john/chap012/</guid>
      <description>1 Jesus therefore, six days before the pasch, came to Bethania, where Lazarus had been dead, whom Jesus raised to life.&#xA;2 And they made him a supper there: and Martha served. But Lazarus was one of them that were at table with him.&#xA;3 Mary therefore took a pound of ointment of right spikenard, of great price, and anointed the feet of Jesus and wiped his feet with her hair.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 13</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/04-john/chap013/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:24 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/04-john/chap013/</guid>
      <description>1 Before the festival day of the pasch, Jesus knowing that his hour was come, that he should pass out of this world to the Father: having loved his own who were in the world, he loved them unto the end.&#xA;2 And when supper was done (the devil having now put into the heart of Judas Iscariot, the son of Simon, to betray him),&#xA;3 Knowing that the Father had given him all things into his hands and that he came from God and goeth to God,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 14</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/04-john/chap014/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:24 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/04-john/chap014/</guid>
      <description>1 Let not your heart be troubled. You believe in God: believe also in me.&#xA;2 In my Father&amp;rsquo;s house there are many mansions. If not, I would have told you: because I go to prepare a place for you.&#xA;3 And if I shall go and prepare a place for you, I will come again and will take you to myself: that where I am, you also may be.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 15</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/04-john/chap015/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:24 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/04-john/chap015/</guid>
      <description>1 I am the true vine: and my Father is the husbandman.&#xA;2 Every branch in me that beareth not fruit, he will take away: and every one that beareth fruit, he will purge it, that it may bring forth more fruit.&#xA;3 Now you are clean, by reason of the word which I have spoken to you.&#xA;4 Abide in me: and I in you. As the branch cannot bear fruit of itself, unless it abide in the vine, so neither can you, unless you abide in me.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 16</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/04-john/chap016/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:24 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/04-john/chap016/</guid>
      <description>1 These things have I spoken to you things have I spoken to you that you may not be scandalized.&#xA;2 They will put you out of the synagogues: yea, the hour cometh, that whosoever killeth you will think that he doth a service to God.&#xA;3 And these things will they do to you; because they have not known the Father nor me.&#xA;4 But these things I have told you, that when the hour shall come, you may remember that I told you of them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 17</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/04-john/chap017/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:24 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/04-john/chap017/</guid>
      <description>1 These things Jesus spoke: and lifting up his eyes to heaven, he said: the hour is come. Glorify thy Son, that thy Son may glorify thee.&#xA;2 As thou hast given him power over all flesh, that he may give eternal life to all whom thou hast given him.&#xA;3 Now this is eternal life: That they may know thee, the only true God, and Jesus Christ, whom thou hast sent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 18</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/04-john/chap018/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:24 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/04-john/chap018/</guid>
      <description>1 When Jesus had said these things, he went forth with his disciples over the brook Cedron, where there was a garden, into which he entered with his disciples.&#xA;2 And Judas also, who betrayed him, knew the place: because Jesus had often resorted thither together with his disciples.&#xA;3 Judas therefore having received a band of soldiers and servants from the chief priests and the Pharisees, cometh thither with lanterns and torches and weapons.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 19</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/04-john/chap019/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:24 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/04-john/chap019/</guid>
      <description>1 Then therefore Pilate took Jesus and scourged him.&#xA;2 And the soldiers platting a crown of thorns, put it upon his head: and they put on him a purple garment.&#xA;3 And they came to him and said: Hail, king of the Jews. And they gave him blows.&#xA;4 Pilate therefore went forth again and saith to them: Behold, I bring him forth unto you, that you may know that I find no cause in him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 20</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/04-john/chap020/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:24 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/04-john/chap020/</guid>
      <description>1 And on the first day of the week, Mary Magdalen cometh early, when it was yet dark, unto the sepulchre: and she saw the stone taken away from the sepulchre.&#xA;2 She ran therefore and cometh to Simon Peter and to the other disciple whom Jesus loved and saith to them: They have taken away the Lord out of the sepulchre: and we know not where they have laid him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 21</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/04-john/chap021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:24 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/04-john/chap021/</guid>
      <description>1 After this, Jesus shewed himself to the disciples at the sea of Tiberias. And he shewed himself after this manner.&#xA;2 There were together: Simon Peter and Thomas, who is called Didymus, and Nathanael, who was of Cana of Galilee, and the sons of Zebedee and two others of his disciples.&#xA;3 Simon Peter saith to them: I go a fishing. They say to him: We also come with thee.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 8</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/04-john/chap008/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:24 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/04-john/chap008/</guid>
      <description>1 And Jesus went unto mount Olivet.&#xA;2 And early in the morning he came again into the temple: and all the people came to him. And sitting down he taught them.&#xA;3 And the scribes and Pharisees bring unto him a woman taken in adultery: and they set her in the midst,&#xA;4 And said to him: Master, this woman was even now taken in adultery.&#xA;5 Now Moses in the law commanded us to stone such a one.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 9</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/04-john/chap009/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:24 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/04-john/chap009/</guid>
      <description>1 And Jesus passing by, saw a man who was blind from his birth.&#xA;2 And his disciples asked him: Rabbi, who hath sinned, this man or his parents, that he should be born blind?&#xA;3 Jesus answered: Neither hath this man sinned, nor his parents; but that the works of God should be made manifest in him.&#xA;4 I must work the works of him that sent me, whilst it is day: the night cometh, when no man can work.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 1</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/04-john/chap001/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:23 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/04-john/chap001/</guid>
      <description>1 In the beginning was the Word: and the Word was with God: and the Word was God.&#xA;2 The same was in the beginning with God.&#xA;3 All things were made by him: and without him was made nothing that was made.&#xA;4 In him was life: and the life was the light of men.&#xA;5 And the light shineth in darkness: and the darkness did not comprehend it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 2</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/04-john/chap002/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:23 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/04-john/chap002/</guid>
      <description>1 And the third day, there was a marriage in Cana of Galilee: and the mother of Jesus was there.&#xA;2 And Jesus also was invited, and his disciples, to the marriage.&#xA;3 And the wine failing, the mother of Jesus saith to him: They have no wine.&#xA;4 And Jesus saith to her: Woman, what is that to me and to thee? My hour is not yet come.&#xA;5 His mother saith to the waiters: Whatsoever he shall say to you, do ye.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 3</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/04-john/chap003/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:23 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/04-john/chap003/</guid>
      <description>1 And there was a man of the Pharisees, named Nicodemus, a ruler of the Jews.&#xA;2 This man came to Jesus by night and said to him: Rabbi, we know that thou art come a teacher from God; for no man can do these signs which thou dost, unless God be with him.&#xA;3 Jesus answered and said to him: Amen, amen, I say to thee, unless a man be born again, he cannot see the kingdom of God.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 4</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/04-john/chap004/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:23 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/04-john/chap004/</guid>
      <description>1 When Jesus therefore understood the Pharisees had heard that Jesus maketh more disciples and baptizeth more than John&#xA;2 (Though Jesus himself did not baptize, but his disciples),&#xA;3 He left Judea and went again into Galilee.&#xA;4 And he was of necessity to pass through Samaria.&#xA;5 He cometh therefore to a city of Samaria, which is called Sichar, near the land which Jacob gave to his son Joseph.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 5</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/04-john/chap005/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:23 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/04-john/chap005/</guid>
      <description>1 After these things was a festival day of the Jews: and Jesus went up to Jerusalem.&#xA;2 Now there is at Jerusalem a pond, called Probatica, which in Hebrew is named Bethsaida, having five porches.&#xA;3 In these lay a great multitude of sick, of blind, of lame, of withered: waiting for the moving of the water.&#xA;4 And an angel of the Lord descended at certain times into the pond and the water was moved.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 6</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/04-john/chap006/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:23 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/04-john/chap006/</guid>
      <description>1 After these things Jesus went over the sea of Galilee, which is that of Tiberias.&#xA;2 And a great multitude followed him, because they saw the miracles which he did on them that were diseased.&#xA;3 Jesus therefore went up into a mountain: and there he sat with his disciples.&#xA;4 Now the pasch, the festival day of the Jews, was near at hand.&#xA;5 When Jesus therefore had lifted up his eyes and seen that a very great multitude cometh to him, he said to Philip: Whence shall we buy bread, that these may eat?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 7</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/04-john/chap007/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:23 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/04-john/chap007/</guid>
      <description>1 After these things, Jesus walked in Galilee: for he would not walk in Judea, because the Jews sought to kill him.&#xA;2 Now the Jews feast of tabernacles was at hand.&#xA;3 And his brethren said to, him: Pass from hence and go into Judea, that thy disciples also may see thy works which thou dost.&#xA;4 For there is no man that doth any thing in secret, and he himself seeketh to be known openly.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
