<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Deuteronomy on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/32-deuteronomy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Deuteronomy on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:27 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/32-deuteronomy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 24</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/32-deuteronomy/chap024/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:27 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/32-deuteronomy/chap024/</guid>
      <description>1 If a man take a wife, and have her, and she find not favour in his eyes, for some uncleanness: he shall write a bill of divorce, and shall give it in her hand, and send her out of his house.&#xA;2 And when she is departed, and marrieth another husband,&#xA;3 And he also hateth her, and hath given her a bill of divorce, and hath sent her out of his house or is dead:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 25</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/32-deuteronomy/chap025/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:27 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/32-deuteronomy/chap025/</guid>
      <description>1 If there be a controversy between men, and they call upon the judges: they shall give the prize of justice to him whom they perceive to be just: and him whom they find to be wicked, they shall condemn of wickedness.&#xA;2 And if they see that the offender be worthy of stripes: they shall lay him down, and shall cause him to be beaten before them. According to the measure of the sin shall the measure also of the stripes be:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 26</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/32-deuteronomy/chap026/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:27 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/32-deuteronomy/chap026/</guid>
      <description>1 And when thou art come into the land which the Lord thy God will give thee to possess, and hast conquered it, and dwellest in it:&#xA;2 Thou shalt take the first of all thy fruits, and put them in a basket, and shalt go to the place which the Lord thy God shall choose, that his name may be invocated there:&#xA;3 And thou shalt go to the priest that shall be in those days, and say to him: I profess this day before the Lord thy God, that I am come into the land, for which he swore to our fathers, that he would give it us.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 27</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/32-deuteronomy/chap027/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:27 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/32-deuteronomy/chap027/</guid>
      <description>1 And Moses with the ancients of Israel commanded the people, saying: Keep every commandment that I command you this day.&#xA;2 And when you are passed over the Jordan into the land which the Lord thy God will give thee, thou shalt set up great stones, and shalt plaster them over with plaster,&#xA;3 That thou mayst write on them all the words of this law, when thou art passed over the Jordan: that thou mayst enter into the land which the Lord thy God will give thee, a land flowing with milk and honey, as he swore to thy fathers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 28</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/32-deuteronomy/chap028/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:27 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/32-deuteronomy/chap028/</guid>
      <description>1 Now if thou wilt hear the voice of all his commandments, which I command thee this day, the Lord thy God will make thee higher than all the nations that are on the earth.&#xA;2 And all these blessings shall come upon thee and overtake thee: yet so if thou hear his precepts.&#xA;3 Blessed shalt thou be in the city, and blessed in the field.&#xA;4 Blessed shall be the fruit of thy womb, and the fruit of thy ground, and the fruit of thy cattle, the droves of thy herds, and the folds of thy sheep.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 29</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/32-deuteronomy/chap029/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:27 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/32-deuteronomy/chap029/</guid>
      <description>1 These are the words of the covenant which the Lord commanded Moses to make with the children of Israel in the land of Moab: beside that covenant which he made with them in Horeb.&#xA;2 And Moses called all Israel, and said to them: You have seen all the things that the Lord did before you in the land of Egypt to Pharao, and to all his servants, and to his whole land.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 30</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/32-deuteronomy/chap030/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:27 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/32-deuteronomy/chap030/</guid>
      <description>1 Now when all these things shall be come upon thee, the blessing or the curse, which I have set forth before thee, and thou shalt be touched with repentance of thy heart among all the nations, into which the Lord thy God shall have scattered thee,&#xA;2 And shalt return to him, and obey his commandments, as I command thee this day, thou and thy children, with all thy heart, and with all thy soul:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 31</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/32-deuteronomy/chap031/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:27 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/32-deuteronomy/chap031/</guid>
      <description>1 And Moses went, and spoke all these words to all Israel,&#xA;2 And he said to them: I am this day a hundred and twenty years old, I can no longer go out and come in, especially as the Lord also hath said to me: Thou shalt not pass over this Jordan.&#xA;3 The Lord thy God then will pass over before thee: he will destroy all these nations in thy sight, and thou shalt possess them: and this Josue shall go over before thee, as the Lord hath spoken.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 32</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/32-deuteronomy/chap032/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:27 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/32-deuteronomy/chap032/</guid>
      <description>1 Hear, O ye heavens, the things I speak, let the earth give ear to the words of my mouth.&#xA;2 Let my doctrine gather as the rain, let my speech distil as the dew, as a shower upon the herb, and as drops upon the grass.&#xA;3 Because I will invoke the name of the Lord: give ye magnificence to our God.&#xA;4 The works of God are perfect, and all his ways are judgments: God is faithful and without any iniquity, he is just and right.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 33</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/32-deuteronomy/chap033/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:27 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/32-deuteronomy/chap033/</guid>
      <description>1 This is the blessing, wherewith the man of God, Moses, blessed the children of Israel, before his death.&#xA;2 And he said: The Lord came from Sinai, and from Seir he rose up to us: he hath appeared from mount Pharan, and with him thousands of saints. In his right hand a fiery law.&#xA;3 He hath loved the people, all the saints are in his hand: and they that approach to his feet, shall receive of his doctrine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 34</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/32-deuteronomy/chap034/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:27 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/32-deuteronomy/chap034/</guid>
      <description>1 Then Moses went up from the plains of Moab upon mount Nebo, to the top of Phasga over against Jericho: and the Lord shewed him all the land of Galaad as far as Dan.&#xA;2 And all Nephtali, and the land of Ephraim and Manasses, and all the land of Juda unto the furthermost sea,&#xA;3 And the south part, and the breadth of the plain of Jericho the city of palm trees as far as Segor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 1</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/32-deuteronomy/chap001/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/32-deuteronomy/chap001/</guid>
      <description>1 These are the words, which Moses spoke to all Israel beyond the Jordan, in the plain wilderness, over against the Red Sea, between Pharan and Thophel and Laban and Haseroth, where there is very much gold.&#xA;2 Eleven days&amp;rsquo; journey from Horeb by the way of mount Seir to Cadesbarne.&#xA;3 In the fortieth year, the eleventh month, the first day of the month, Moses spoke to the children of Israel all that the Lord had commanded him to say to them:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 10</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/32-deuteronomy/chap010/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/32-deuteronomy/chap010/</guid>
      <description>1 At that time the Lord said to me: Hew thee two tables of stone like the former, and come up to me into the mount: and thou shalt make an ark of wood,&#xA;2 And I will write on the tables the words that were in them, which thou brokest before, and thou shalt put them in the ark.&#xA;3 And I made an ark of setim wood. And when I had hewn two tables of stone like the former, I went up into the mount, having them in my hands.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 11</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/32-deuteronomy/chap011/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/32-deuteronomy/chap011/</guid>
      <description>1 Therefore love the Lord thy God and observe his precepts and ceremonies, his judgments and commandments at all times.&#xA;2 Know this day the things that your children know not, who saw not the chastisements of the Lord your God, his great doings and strong hand, and stretched out arm,&#xA;3 The signs and works which he did in the midst of Egypt to king Pharao, and to all his land,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 12</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/32-deuteronomy/chap012/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/32-deuteronomy/chap012/</guid>
      <description>1 These are the precepts and judgments, that you must do in the land, which the Lord the God of thy fathers will give thee, to possess it all the days that thou shalt walk upon the earth.&#xA;2 Destroy all the places in which the nations, that you shall possess, worshipped their gods upon high mountains, and hills, and under every shady tree:&#xA;3 Overthrow their altars, and break down their statues, burn their groves with fire, and break their idols in pieces: destroy their names out of those places.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 13</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/32-deuteronomy/chap013/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/32-deuteronomy/chap013/</guid>
      <description>1 If there rise in the midst of thee a prophet or one that saith he hath dreamed a dream, and he foretell a sign and a wonder,&#xA;2 And that come to pass which he spoke, and he say to thee: Let us go and follow strange gods, which thou knowest not, and let us serve them:&#xA;3 Thou shalt not hear the words of that prophet or dreamer: for the Lord your God trieth you, that it may appear whether you love him with all your heart, and with all your soul, or not.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 14</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/32-deuteronomy/chap014/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/32-deuteronomy/chap014/</guid>
      <description>1 Be ye children of the Lord your God: you shall not cut yourselves, nor make any baldness for the dead;&#xA;2 Because thou art a holy people to the Lord thy God: and he chose thee to be his peculiar people of all nations that are upon the earth.&#xA;3 Eat not the things that are unclean.&#xA;4 These are the beasts that you shall eat, the ox, and the sheep, and the goat,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 15</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/32-deuteronomy/chap015/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/32-deuteronomy/chap015/</guid>
      <description>1 In the seventh year thou shalt make a remission,&#xA;2 Which shall be celebrated in this order. He to whom any thing is owing from his friend or neighbour or brother, cannot demand it again, because it is the year of remission of the Lord.&#xA;3 Of the foreigner or stranger thou mayst exact it: of thy countryman and neighbour thou shalt not have power to demand it again.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 16</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/32-deuteronomy/chap016/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/32-deuteronomy/chap016/</guid>
      <description>1 Observe the month of new corn, which is the first of the spring, that thou mayst celebrate the phase to the Lord thy God: because in this month the Lord thy God brought thee out of Egypt by night.&#xA;2 And thou shalt sacrifice the phase to the Lord thy God, of sheep, and of oxen, in the place which the Lord thy God shall choose, that his name may dwell there.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 17</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/32-deuteronomy/chap017/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/32-deuteronomy/chap017/</guid>
      <description>1 Thou shalt not sacrifice to the Lord thy God a sheep, or an ox, wherein there is blemish, or any fault: for that is an abomination to the Lord thy God.&#xA;2 When there shall be found among you within any of thy gates, which the Lord thy God shall give thee, man or woman that do evil in the sight of the Lord thy God, and transgress his covenant,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 18</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/32-deuteronomy/chap018/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/32-deuteronomy/chap018/</guid>
      <description>1 The priests and Levites, and all that are of the same tribe, shall have no part nor inheritance with the rest of Israel, because they shall eat the sacrifices of the Lord, and his oblations,&#xA;2 And they shall receive nothing else of the possession of their brethren: for the Lord himself is their inheritance, as he hath said to them.&#xA;3 This shall be the priest&amp;rsquo;s due from the people, and from them that offer victims: whether they sacrifice an ox, or a sheep, they shall give to the priest the shoulder and the breast:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 19</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/32-deuteronomy/chap019/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/32-deuteronomy/chap019/</guid>
      <description>1 When the Lord thy God hath destroyed the nations, whose land he will deliver to thee, and thou shalt possess it, and shalt dwell in the cities and houses thereof:&#xA;2 Thou shalt separate to thee three cities in the midst of the land, which the Lord will give thee in possession,&#xA;3 Paving diligently the way: and thou shalt divide the whole province of thy land equally into three parts: that he who is forced to flee for manslaughter, may have near at hand whither to escape.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 2</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/32-deuteronomy/chap002/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/32-deuteronomy/chap002/</guid>
      <description>1 And departing from thence we came into the wilderness that leadeth to the Red Sea, as the Lord had spoken to me: and we compassed mount Seir a long time.&#xA;2 And the Lord said to me:&#xA;3 You have compassed this mountain long enough: go toward the north:&#xA;4 And command thou the people, saying: You shall pass by the borders of your brethren the children of Esau, who dwell in Seir, and they will be afraid of you.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 20</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/32-deuteronomy/chap020/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/32-deuteronomy/chap020/</guid>
      <description>1 If thou go out to war against thy enemies, and see horsemen and chariots, and the numbers of the enemy&amp;rsquo;s army greater than thine, thou shalt not fear them: because the Lord thy God is with thee, who brought thee out of the land of Egypt.&#xA;2 And when the battle is now at hand, the priest shall stand before the army, and shall speak to the people in this manner:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 21</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/32-deuteronomy/chap021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/32-deuteronomy/chap021/</guid>
      <description>1 When there shall be found in the land, which the Lord thy God will give thee, the corpse of a man slain, and it is not known who is guilty of the murder,&#xA;2 Thy ancients and judges shall go out, and shall measure from the place where the body lieth the distance of every city round about:&#xA;3 And the ancients of that city which they shall perceive to be nearer than the rest, shall take a heifer of the herd, that hath not drawn in the yoke, nor ploughed the ground,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 22</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/32-deuteronomy/chap022/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/32-deuteronomy/chap022/</guid>
      <description>1 Thou shalt not pass by if thou seest thy brother&amp;rsquo;s ox, or his sheep go astray: but thou shalt bring them back to thy brother.&#xA;2 And if thy brother be not nigh, or thou know him not: thou shalt bring them to thy house, and they shall be with thee until thy brother seek them, and receive them.&#xA;3 Thou shalt do in like manner with his ass, and with his raiment, and with every thing that is thy brother&amp;rsquo;s, which is lost: if thou find it, neglect it not as pertaining to another.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 23</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/32-deuteronomy/chap023/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/32-deuteronomy/chap023/</guid>
      <description>1 An eunuch, whose testicles are broken or cut away, or yard cut off, shall not enter into the church of the Lord.&#xA;2 A mamzer, that is to say, one born of a prostitute, shall not enter into the church of the Lord, until the tenth generation.&#xA;3 The Ammonite and the Moabite, even after the tenth generation shall not enter into the church of the Lord for ever:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 3</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/32-deuteronomy/chap003/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/32-deuteronomy/chap003/</guid>
      <description>1 Then we turned and went by the way of Basan: and Og the king of Basan came out to meet us with his people to fight in Edrai.&#xA;2 And the Lord said to me: Fear him not: because he is delivered into thy hand, with all his people and his land: and thou shalt do to him as thou hast done to Sehon king of the Amorrhites, that dwelt in Hesebon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 4</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/32-deuteronomy/chap004/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/32-deuteronomy/chap004/</guid>
      <description>1 And now, O Israel, hear the commandments and judgments which I teach thee: that doing them, thou mayst live, and entering in mayst possess the land which the Lord the God of your fathers will give you.&#xA;2 You shall not add to the word that I speak to you, neither shall you take away from it: keep the commandments of the Lord your God which I command you.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 5</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/32-deuteronomy/chap005/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/32-deuteronomy/chap005/</guid>
      <description>1 And Moses called all Israel, and said to them: Hear, O Israel, the ceremonies and judgments, which I speak in your ears this day: learn them, and fulfil them in work.&#xA;2 The Lord our God made a covenant with us in Horeb.&#xA;3 He made not the covenant with our fathers, but with us, who are now present and living.&#xA;4 He spoke to us face to face in the mount out of the midst of fire.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 6</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/32-deuteronomy/chap006/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/32-deuteronomy/chap006/</guid>
      <description>1 These are the precepts, and ceremonies, and judgments, which the Lord your God commanded that I should teach you, and that you should do them in the land into which you pass over to possess it:&#xA;2 That thou mayst fear the Lord thy God, and keep all his commandments and precepts, which I command thee, and thy sons, and thy grandsons, all the days of thy life, that thy days may be prolonged.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 7</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/32-deuteronomy/chap007/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/32-deuteronomy/chap007/</guid>
      <description>1 When the Lord thy God shall have brought thee into the land, which thou art going in to possess, and shall have destroyed many nations before thee, the Hethite, and the Gergezite, and the Amorrhite, and the Chanaanite, and the Pherezite, and the Hevite, and the Jebusite, seven nations much more numerous than thou art, and stronger than thou:&#xA;2 And the Lord thy God shall have delivered them to thee, thou shalt utterly destroy them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 8</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/32-deuteronomy/chap008/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/32-deuteronomy/chap008/</guid>
      <description>1 All the commandments, that I command thee this day, take great care to observe: that you may live, and be multiplied, and going in may possess the land, for which the Lord swore to your fathers.&#xA;2 And thou shalt remember all the way through which the Lord thy God hath brought thee for forty years through the desert, to afflict thee and to prove thee, and that the things that were known in thy heart might be made known, whether thou wouldst keep his commandments or no.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 9</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/32-deuteronomy/chap009/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/32-deuteronomy/chap009/</guid>
      <description>1 Hear, O Israel: Thou shalt go over the Jordan this day; to possess nations very great, and stronger than thyself, cities great, and walled up to the sky,&#xA;2 A people great and tall, the sons of the Enacims, whom thou hast seen, and heard of, against whom no man is able to stand.&#xA;3 Thou shalt know therefore this day that the Lord thy God himself will pass over before thee, a devouring and consuming fire, to destroy and extirpate and bring them to nothing before thy face quickly, as he hath spoken to thee.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
