<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ezra on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/42-ezra/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ezra on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:28 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/42-ezra/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 1</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/42-ezra/chap001/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:28 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/42-ezra/chap001/</guid>
      <description>1 In the first year of Cyrus king of the Persians, that the word of the Lord by the mouth of Jeremias might be fulfilled, the Lord stirred up the spirit of Cyrus king of the Persians: and he made a proclamation throughout all his kingdom, and in writing also, saying:&#xA;2 Thus saith Cyrus king of the Persians: The Lord the God of heaven hath given to me all the kingdoms of the earth, and he hath charged me to build him a house in Jerusalem, which is in Judea.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 10</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/42-ezra/chap010/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:28 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/42-ezra/chap010/</guid>
      <description>1 Now when Esdras was thus praying, and beseeching, and weeping, and lying before the temple of God, there was gathered to him of Israel an exceeding great assembly of men and women and children, and the people wept with much lamentation.&#xA;2 And Sechenias the son of Jehiel of the sons of Elam answered, and said to Esdras: We have sinned against our God, and have taken strange wives of the people of the land: and now if there be repentance in Israel concerning this,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 2</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/42-ezra/chap002/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:28 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/42-ezra/chap002/</guid>
      <description>1 Now these are the children of the province, that went out of the captivity, which Nabuchodonosor king of Babylon had carried away to Babylon, and who returned to Jerusalem and Juda, every man to his city.&#xA;2 Who came with Zorobabel, Josue, Nehemia, Saraia, Rahelaia, Mardochai, Belsan, Mesphar, Beguai, Rehum, Baana. The number of the men of the people of Israel:&#xA;3 The children of Pharos two thousand one hundred seventy-two.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 3</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/42-ezra/chap003/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:28 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/42-ezra/chap003/</guid>
      <description>1 And now the seventh month was come, and the children of Israel were in their cities: and the people gathered themselves together as one man to Jerusalem.&#xA;2 And Josue the son of Josedec rose up, and his brethren the priests, and Zorobabel the son of Salathiel, and his brethren, and they built the altar of the God of Israel that they might offer holocausts upon it, as it is written in the law of Moses the man of God.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 4</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/42-ezra/chap004/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:28 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/42-ezra/chap004/</guid>
      <description>1 Now the enemies of Juda and Benjamin heard that the children of the captivity were building a temple to the Lord the God of Israel.&#xA;2 And they came to Zorobabel, and the chief of the fathers, and said to them: Let us build with you, for we seek your God as ye do: behold we have sacrificed to him, since the days of Asor Haddan king of Assyria, who brought us hither.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 5</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/42-ezra/chap005/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:28 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/42-ezra/chap005/</guid>
      <description>1 Now Aggeus the prophet, and Zacharias the son of Addo, prophesied to the Jews that were in Judea and Jerusalem, in the name of the God of Israel.&#xA;2 Then rose up Zorobabel the son of Salathiel, and Josue the son of Josedec, and began to build the temple of God in Jerusalem, and with them were the prophets of God helping them.&#xA;3 And at the same time came to them Thathanai, who was governor beyond the river, and Stharbuzanai, and their counsellors: and said thus to them: Who hath given you counsel to build this house, and to repair the walls thereof?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 6</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/42-ezra/chap006/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:28 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/42-ezra/chap006/</guid>
      <description>1 Then king Darius gave orders, and they searched in the library of the books that were laid up in Babylon,&#xA;2 And there was found in Ecbatana, which is a castle in the province of Media, a book in which this record was written.&#xA;3 In the first year of Cyrus the king: Cyrus the king decreed, that the house of God should be built, which is in Jerusalem, in the place where they may offer sacrifices, and that they lay the foundations that may support the height of threescore cubits, and the breadth of threescore cubits,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 7</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/42-ezra/chap007/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:28 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/42-ezra/chap007/</guid>
      <description>1 Now after these things in the reign of Artaxerxes king of the Persians, Esdras the son of Saraias, the son of Azarias, the son of Helcias,&#xA;2 The son of Sellum, the son of Sadoc, the son of Achitob,&#xA;3 The son of Amarias, the son of Azarias, the son of Maraioth,&#xA;4 The son of Zarahias, the son of Ozi, the son of Bocci,&#xA;5 The son of Abisue, the son of Phinees, the son of Eleazar, the son of Aaron, the priest from the beginning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 8</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/42-ezra/chap008/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:28 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/42-ezra/chap008/</guid>
      <description>1 Now these are the chief of families, and the genealogy of them, who came up with me from Babylon in the reign of Artaxerxes the king.&#xA;2 Of the sons of Phinees, Gersom. Of the sons of Ithamar, Daniel. Of the sons of David, Hattus.&#xA;3 Of the sons of Sechenias, the son of Pharos, Zacharias, and with him were numbered a hundred and fifty men.&#xA;4 Of the sons of Phahath Moab, Eleoenai the son of Zareha, and with him two hundred men.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 9</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/42-ezra/chap009/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:28 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/42-ezra/chap009/</guid>
      <description>1 And after these things were accomplished, the princes came to me, saying: The people of Israel, and the priests and Levites have not separated themselves from the people of the lands, and from their abominations, namely, of the Chanaanites, and the Hethites, and the Pherezites, and the Jebusites, and the Ammonites, and the Moabites, and the Egyptians, and the Amorrhites.&#xA;2 For they have taken of their daughters for themselves and for their sons, and they have mingled the holy seed with the people of the lands.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
