<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Psalms on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</title>
    <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Psalms on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 100</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap100/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap100/</guid>
      <description>1 A psalm for David himself. Mercy and judgment I will sing to thee, O Lord: I will sing,&#xA;2 And I will understand in the unspotted way, when thou shalt come to me. I walked in the innocence of my heart, in the midst of my house.&#xA;3 I will not set before my eyes any unjust thing: I hated the workers of iniquities.&#xA;4 The perverse heart did not cleave to me: and the malignant, that turned aside from me, I would not know.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 101</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap101/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap101/</guid>
      <description>1 The prayer of the poor man, when he was anxious, and poured out his supplication before the Lord.&#xA;2 Hear, O Lord, my prayer: and let my cry come to thee.&#xA;3 Turn not away thy face from me: in the day when I am in trouble, incline thy ear to me. In what day soever I shall call upon thee, hear me speedily.&#xA;4 For my days are vanished like smoke, and my bones are grown dry like fuel for the fire.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 102</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap102/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap102/</guid>
      <description>1 For David himself. Bless the Lord, O my soul: and let all that is within me bless his holy name.&#xA;2 Bless the Lord, O my soul, and never forget all he hath done for thee.&#xA;3 Who forgiveth all thy iniquities: who healeth all thy diseases.&#xA;4 Who redeemeth thy life from destruction: who crowneth thee with mercy and compassion.&#xA;5 Who satisfieth thy desire with good things: thy youth shall be renewed like the eagle&amp;rsquo;s.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 103</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap103/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap103/</guid>
      <description>1 For David himself. Bless the Lord, O my soul: O Lord my God, thou art exceedingly great. Thou hast put on praise and beauty:&#xA;2 And art clothed with light as with a garment. Who stretchest out the heaven like a pavilion:&#xA;3 Who coverest the higher rooms thereof with water. Who makest the clouds thy chariot: who walkest upon the wings of the winds.&#xA;4 Who makest thy angels spirits: and thy ministers a burning fire.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 104</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap104/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap104/</guid>
      <description>1 Give glory to the Lord, and call upon his name: declare his deeds among the Gentiles.&#xA;2 Sing to him, yea sing praises to him: relate all his wondrous works.&#xA;3 Glory ye in his holy name: let the heart of them rejoice that seek the Lord.&#xA;4 Seek ye the Lord, and be strengthened: seek his face evermore.&#xA;5 Remember his marvellous works which he hath done; his wonders, and the judgments of his mouth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 105</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap105/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap105/</guid>
      <description>1 Give glory to the Lord, for he is good: for his mercy endureth for ever.&#xA;2 Who shall declare the powers of the Lord? who shall set forth all his praises?&#xA;3 Blessed are they that keep judgment, and do justice at all times.&#xA;4 Remember us, O Lord, in the favour of thy people: visit us with thy salvation.&#xA;5 That we may see the good of thy chosen, that we may rejoice in the joy of thy nation: that thou mayst be praised with thy inheritance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 106</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap106/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap106/</guid>
      <description>1 Give glory to the Lord, for he is good: for his mercy endureth for ever.&#xA;2 Let them say so that have been redeemed by the Lord, whom he hath redeemed from the hand of the enemy: and gathered out of the countries.&#xA;3 From the rising and from the setting of the sun, from the north and from the sea.&#xA;4 They wandered in a wilderness, in a place without water: they found not the way of a city for their habitation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 107</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap107/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap107/</guid>
      <description>1 A canticle of a psalm for David himself.&#xA;2 My heart is ready, O God, my heart is ready: I will sing, and will give praise, with my glory.&#xA;3 Arise, my glory; arise, psaltery and harp: I will arise in the morning early.&#xA;4 I will praise thee, O Lord, among the people: and I will sing unto thee among the nations.&#xA;5 For thy mercy is great above the heavens: and thy truth even unto the clouds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 108</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap108/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap108/</guid>
      <description>1 Unto the end, a psalm for David.&#xA;2 O God, be not thou silent in my praise: for the mouth of the wicked and the mouth of the deceitful man is opened against me.&#xA;3 They have spoken against me with deceitful tongues; and they have compassed me about with words of hatred; and have fought against me without cause.&#xA;4 Instead of making me a return of love, they detracted me: but I gave myself to prayer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 109</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap109/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap109/</guid>
      <description>1 A psalm for David. The Lord said to my Lord: Sit thou at my right hand: Until I make thy enemies thy footstool.&#xA;2 The Lord will send forth the sceptre of thy power out of Sion: rule thou in the midst of thy enemies.&#xA;3 With thee is the principality in the day of thy strength: in the brightness of the saints: from the womb before the day star I begot thee.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 110</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap110/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap110/</guid>
      <description>1 I will praise thee, O Lord, with my whole heart; in the council of the just, and in the congregation.&#xA;2 Great are the works of the Lord: sought out according to all his wills.&#xA;3 His work is praise and magnificence: and his justice continueth for ever and ever.&#xA;4 He hath made a remembrance of his wonderful works, being a merciful and gracious Lord:&#xA;5 He hath given food to them that fear him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 111</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap111/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap111/</guid>
      <description>1 Blessed is the man that feareth the Lord: he shall delight exceedingly in his commandments.&#xA;2 His seed shall be mighty upon earth: the generation of the righteous shall be blessed.&#xA;3 Glory and wealth shall be in his house: and his justice remaineth for ever and ever.&#xA;4 To the righteous a light is risen up in darkness: he is merciful, and compassionate and just.&#xA;5 Acceptable is the man that sheweth mercy and lendeth: he shall order his words with judgment:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 112</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap112/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap112/</guid>
      <description>1 Praise the Lord, ye children: praise ye the name of the Lord.&#xA;2 Blessed be the name of the Lord, from henceforth now and for ever.&#xA;3 From the rising of the sun unto the going down of the same, the name of the Lord is worthy of praise.&#xA;4 The Lord is high above all nations; and his glory above the heavens.&#xA;5 Who is as the Lord our God, who dwelleth on high:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 113</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap113/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap113/</guid>
      <description>1 When Israel went out of Egypt, the house of Jacob from a barbarous people:&#xA;2 Judea was made his sanctuary, Israel his dominion.&#xA;3 The sea saw and fled: Jordan was turned back.&#xA;4 The mountains skipped like rams, and the hills like the lambs of the flock.&#xA;5 What ailed thee, O thou sea, that thou didst flee: and thou, O Jordan, that thou wast turned back?&#xA;6 Ye mountains, that ye skipped like rams, and ye hills, like lambs of the flock?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 114</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap114/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap114/</guid>
      <description>1 I have loved, because the Lord will hear the voice of my prayer.&#xA;2 Because he hath inclined his ear unto me: and in my days I will call upon him.&#xA;3 The sorrows of death have compassed me: and the perils of hell have found me. I met with trouble and sorrow:&#xA;4 And I called upon the name of the Lord. O Lord, deliver my soul.&#xA;5 The Lord is merciful and just, and our God sheweth mercy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 115</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap115/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap115/</guid>
      <description>1 I have believed, therefore have I spoken; but I have been humbled exceedingly.&#xA;2 I said in my excess: Every man is a liar.&#xA;3 What shall I render to the Lord, for all the things that he hath rendered to me?&#xA;4 I will take the chalice of salvation; and I will call upon the name of the Lord.&#xA;5 I will pay my vows to the Lord before all his people:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 116</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap116/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap116/</guid>
      <description>1 O Praise the Lord, all ye nations: praise him, all ye people.&#xA;2 For his mercy is confirmed upon us: and the truth of the Lord remaineth for ever.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 117</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap117/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap117/</guid>
      <description>1 Give praise to the Lord, for he is good: for his mercy endureth for ever.&#xA;2 Let Israel now say, that he is good: that his mercy endureth for ever.&#xA;3 Let the house of Aaron now say, that his mercy endureth for ever.&#xA;4 Let them that fear the Lord now say, that his mercy endureth for ever.&#xA;5 In my trouble I called upon the Lord: and the Lord heard me, and enlarged me.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 118</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap118/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap118/</guid>
      <description>1 Blessed are the undefiled in the way, who walk in the law of the Lord.&#xA;2 Blessed are they that search his testimonies: that seek him with their whole heart.&#xA;3 For they that work iniquity, have not walked in his ways.&#xA;4 Thou hast commanded thy commandments to be kept most diligently.&#xA;5 O! that my ways may be directed to keep thy justifications.&#xA;6 Then shall I not be confounded, when I shall look into all thy commandments.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 119</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap119/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap119/</guid>
      <description>1 In my trouble I cried to the Lord: and he heard me.&#xA;2 O Lord, deliver my soul from wicked lips, and a deceitful tongue.&#xA;3 What shall be given to thee, or what shall be added to thee, to a deceitful tongue?&#xA;4 The sharp arrows of the mighty, with coals that lay waste.&#xA;5 Woe is me, that my sojourning is prolonged! I have dwelt with the inhabitants of Cedar:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 120</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap120/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap120/</guid>
      <description>1 I have lifted up my eyes to the mountains, from whence help shall come to me.&#xA;2 My help is from the Lord, who made heaven and earth.&#xA;3 May he not suffer thy foot to be moved: neither let him slumber that keepeth thee.&#xA;4 Behold he shall neither slumber nor sleep, that keepeth Israel.&#xA;5 The Lord is thy keeper, the Lord is thy protection upon thy right hand.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 121</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap121/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap121/</guid>
      <description>1 A gradual canticle. I rejoiced at the things that were said to me: We shall go into the house of the Lord.&#xA;2 Our feet were standing in thy courts, O Jerusalem.&#xA;3 Jerusalem, which is built as a city, which is compact together.&#xA;4 For thither did the tribes go up, the tribes of the Lord: the testimony of Israel, to praise the name of the Lord.&#xA;5 Because their seats have sat in judgment, seats upon the house of David.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 122</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap122/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap122/</guid>
      <description>1 To thee have I lifted up my eyes, who dwellest in heaven.&#xA;2 Behold as the eyes of servants are on the hands of their masters, As the eyes of the handmaid are on the hands of her mistress: so are our eyes unto the Lord our God, until he have mercy on us.&#xA;3 Have mercy on us, O Lord, have mercy on us: for we are greatly filled with contempt.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 123</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap123/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap123/</guid>
      <description>1 A gradual canticle. If it had not been that the Lord was with us, let Israel now say:&#xA;2 If it had not been that the Lord was with us, When men rose up against us,&#xA;3 Perhaps they had swallowed us up alive. When their fury was enkindled against us,&#xA;4 Perhaps the waters had swallowed us up.&#xA;5 Our soul hath passed through a torrent: perhaps our soul had passed through a water insupportable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 124</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap124/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap124/</guid>
      <description>1 A gradual canticle. They that trust in the Lord shall be as mount Sion: he shall not be moved for ever that dwelleth&#xA;2 In Jerusalem. Mountains are round about it: so the Lord is round about his people from henceforth now and for ever.&#xA;3 For the Lord will not leave the rod of sinners upon the lot of the just: that the just may not stretch forth their hands to iniquity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 125</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap125/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap125/</guid>
      <description>1 A gradual canticle. When the Lord brought back the captivity of Sion, we became like men comforted.&#xA;2 Then was our mouth filled with gladness; and our tongue with joy. Then shall they say among the Gentiles: The Lord hath done great things for them.&#xA;3 The Lord hath done great things for us: we are become joyful.&#xA;4 Turn again our captivity, O Lord, as a stream in the south.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 126</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap126/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap126/</guid>
      <description>1 A gradual canticle of Solomon. Unless the Lord build the house, they labour in vain that build it. Unless the Lord keep the city, he watcheth in vain that keepeth it.&#xA;2 It is vain for you to rise before light, rise ye after you have sitten, you that eat the bread of sorrow. When he shall give sleep to his beloved,&#xA;3 Behold the inheritance of the Lord are children: the reward, the fruit of the womb.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 127</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap127/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap127/</guid>
      <description>1 A gradual canticle. Blessed are all they that fear the Lord: that walk in his ways.&#xA;2 For thou shalt eat the labours of thy hands: blessed art thou, and it shall be well with thee.&#xA;3 Thy wife as a fruitful vine, on the sides of thy house. Thy children as olive plants, round about thy table.&#xA;4 Behold, thus shall the man be blessed that feareth the Lord.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 128</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap128/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap128/</guid>
      <description>1 A gradual canticle. Often have they fought against me from my youth, let Israel now say.&#xA;2 Often have they fought against me from my youth: but they could not prevail over me.&#xA;3 The wicked have wrought upon my back: they have lengthened their iniquity.&#xA;4 The Lord who is just will cut the necks of sinners:&#xA;5 Let them all be confounded and turned back that hate Sion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 129</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap129/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap129/</guid>
      <description>1 A gradual canticle. Out of the depths I have cried to thee, O Lord:&#xA;2 Lord, hear my voice. Let thy ears be attentive to the voice of my supplication.&#xA;3 If thou, O Lord, wilt mark iniquities: Lord, who shall stand it.&#xA;4 For with thee there is merciful forgiveness: and by reason of thy law, I have waited for thee, O Lord. My soul hath relied on his word:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 130</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap130/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap130/</guid>
      <description>1 A gradual canticle of David. Lord, my heart is not exalted: nor are my eyes lofty. Neither have I walked in great matters, nor in wonderful things above me.&#xA;2 If I was not humbly minded, but exalted my soul: As a child that is weaned is towards his mother, so reward in my soul.&#xA;3 Let Israel hope in the Lord, from henceforth now and for ever.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 131</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap131/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap131/</guid>
      <description>1 A gradual canticle. O Lord, remember David, and all his meekness.&#xA;2 How he swore to the Lord, he vowed a vow to the God of Jacob:&#xA;3 If I shall enter into the tabernacle of my house: if I shall go up into the bed wherein I lie:&#xA;4 If I shall give sleep to my eyes, or slumber to my eyelids,&#xA;5 Or rest to my temples: until I find out a place for the Lord, a tabernacle for the God of Jacob.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 132</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap132/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap132/</guid>
      <description>1 A gradual canticle of David. Behold how good and how pleasant it is for brethren to dwell together in unity:&#xA;2 Like the precious ointment on the head, that ran down upon the beard, the beard of Aaron, Which ran down to the skirt of his garment:&#xA;3 As the dew of Hermon, which descendeth upon mount Sion. For there the Lord hath commanded blessing, and life for evermore.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 133</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap133/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap133/</guid>
      <description>1 A gradual canticle. Behold now bless ye the Lord, all ye servants of the Lord: Who stand in the house of the Lord, in the courts of the house of our God.&#xA;2 In the nights lift up your hands to the holy places, and bless ye the Lord.&#xA;3 May the Lord out of Sion bless thee, he that made heaven and earth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 134</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap134/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap134/</guid>
      <description>1 Alleluia. Praise ye the name of the Lord: O you his servants, praise the Lord:&#xA;2 You that stand in the house of the Lord, in the courts of the house of our God.&#xA;3 Praise ye the Lord, for the Lord is good: sing ye to his name, for it is sweet.&#xA;4 For the Lord hath chosen Jacob unto himself: Israel for his own possession.&#xA;5 For I have known that the Lord is great, and our God is above all gods.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 135</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap135/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap135/</guid>
      <description>1 Alleluia. Praise the Lord, for he is good: for his mercy endureth for ever.&#xA;2 Praise ye the God of gods: for his mercy endureth for ever.&#xA;3 Praise ye the Lord of lords: for his mercy endureth for ever.&#xA;4 Who alone doth great wonders: for his mercy endureth for ever.&#xA;5 Who made the heavens in understanding: for his mercy endureth for ever.&#xA;6 Who established the earth above the waters: for his mercy endureth for ever.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 136</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap136/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap136/</guid>
      <description>1 Upon the rivers of Babylon, there we sat and wept: when we remembered Sion:&#xA;2 On the willows in the midst thereof we hung up our instruments.&#xA;3 For there they that led us into captivity required of us the words of songs. And they that carried us away, said: Sing ye to us a hymn of the songs of Sion.&#xA;4 How shall we sing the song of the Lord in a strange land?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 137</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap137/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap137/</guid>
      <description>1 For David himself. I will praise thee, O Lord, with my whole heart: for thou hast heard the words of my mouth. I will sing praise to thee in the sight of the angels:&#xA;2 I will worship towards thy holy temple, and I will give glory to thy name. For thy mercy, and for thy truth: for thou hast magnified thy holy name above all.&#xA;3 In what day soever I shall call upon thee, hear me: thou shalt multiply strength in my soul.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 138</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap138/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap138/</guid>
      <description>1 Unto the end, a psalm of David. Lord, thou hast proved me, and known me:&#xA;2 Thou hast known my sitting down, and my rising up.&#xA;3 Thou hast understood my thoughts afar off: my path and my line thou hast searched out.&#xA;4 And thou hast foreseen all my ways: for there is no speech in my tongue.&#xA;5 Behold, O Lord, thou hast known all things, the last and those of old: thou hast formed me, and hast laid thy hand upon me.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 139</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap139/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap139/</guid>
      <description>1 Unto the end, a psalm of David.&#xA;2 Deliver me, O Lord, from the evil man: rescue me from the unjust man.&#xA;3 Who have devised iniquities in their hearts: all the day long they designed battles.&#xA;4 They have sharpened their tongues like a serpent: the venom of asps is under their lips.&#xA;5 Keep me, O Lord, from the hand of the wicked: and from unjust men deliver me.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 140</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap140/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap140/</guid>
      <description>1 I have cried to thee, O Lord, hear me: hearken to my voice, when I cry to thee.&#xA;2 Let my prayer be directed as incense in thy sight; the lifting up of my hands, as evening sacrifice.&#xA;3 Set a watch, O Lord, before my mouth: and a door round about my lips.&#xA;4 Incline not my heart to evil words; to make excuses in sins. With men that work iniquity: and I will not communicate with the choicest of them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 141</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap141/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap141/</guid>
      <description>1 Of understanding for David, A prayer when he was in the cave.&#xA;2 I cried to the Lord with my voice: with my voice I made supplication to the Lord.&#xA;3 In his sight I pour out my prayer, and before him I declare my trouble:&#xA;4 When my spirit failed me, then thou knewest my paths. In this way wherein I walked, they have hidden a snare for me.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 142</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap142/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap142/</guid>
      <description>1 A psalm of David, when his son Absalom pursued him. Hear, O Lord, my prayer: give ear to my supplication in thy truth: hear me in thy justice.&#xA;2 And enter not into judgment with thy servant: for in thy sight no man living shall be justified.&#xA;3 For the enemy hath persecuted my soul: he hath brought down my life to the earth. He hath made me to dwell in darkness as those that have been dead of old:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 143</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap143/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap143/</guid>
      <description>1 Blessed be the Lord my God, who teacheth my hands to fight, and my fingers to war.&#xA;2 My mercy, and my refuge: my support, and my deliverer: My protector, and I have hoped in him: who subdueth my people under me.&#xA;3 Lord, what is man, that thou art made known to him? or the son of man, that thou makest account of him?&#xA;4 Man is like to vanity: his days pass away like a shadow.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 144</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap144/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap144/</guid>
      <description>1 Praise, for David himself. I will extol thee, O God my king: and I will bless thy name for ever; yea, for ever and ever.&#xA;2 Every day will I bless thee: and I will praise thy name for ever; yea, for ever and ever.&#xA;3 Great is the Lord, and greatly to be praised: and of his greatness there is no end.&#xA;4 Generation and generation shall praise thy works: and they shall declare thy power.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 145</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap145/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap145/</guid>
      <description>1 Alleluia, of Aggeus and Zacharias.&#xA;2 Praise the Lord, O my soul, in my life I will praise the Lord: I will sing to my God as long as I shall be. Put not your trust in princes:&#xA;3 In the children of men, in whom there is no salvation.&#xA;4 His spirit shall go forth, and he shall return into his earth: in that day all their thoughts shall perish.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 146</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap146/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap146/</guid>
      <description>1 Alleluia. Praise ye the Lord, because psalm is good: to our God be joyful and comely praise.&#xA;2 The Lord buildeth up Jerusalem: he will gather together the dispersed of Israel.&#xA;3 Who healeth the broken of heart, and bindeth up their bruises.&#xA;4 Who telleth the number of the stars: and calleth them all by their names.&#xA;5 Great is our Lord, and great is his power: and of his wisdom there is no number.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 147</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap147/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap147/</guid>
      <description>12 Praise the Lord, O Jerusalem: praise thy God, O Sion.&#xA;13 Because he hath strengthened the bolts of thy gates, he hath blessed thy children within thee.&#xA;14 Who hath placed peace in thy borders: and filleth thee with the fat of corn.&#xA;15 Who sendeth forth his speech to the earth: his word runneth swiftly.&#xA;16 Who giveth snow like wool: scattereth mists like ashes.&#xA;17 He sendeth his crystal like morsels: who shall stand before the face of his cold?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 148</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap148/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap148/</guid>
      <description>1 Praise ye the Lord from the heavens: praise ye him in the high places.&#xA;2 Praise ye him, all his angels, praise ye him, all his hosts.&#xA;3 Praise ye him, O sun and moon: praise him, all ye stars and light.&#xA;4 Praise him, ye heavens of heavens: and let all the waters that are above the heavens&#xA;5 Praise the name of the Lord. For he spoke, and they were made: he commanded, and they were created.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 149</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap149/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap149/</guid>
      <description>1 Sing ye to the Lord a new canticle: let his praise be in the church of the saints.&#xA;2 Let Israel rejoice in him that made him: and let the children of Sion be joyful in their king.&#xA;3 Let them praise his name in choir: let them sing to him with the timbrel and the psaltery.&#xA;4 For the Lord is well pleased with his people: and he will exalt the meek unto salvation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 150</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap150/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap150/</guid>
      <description>1 Praise ye the Lord in his holy places: praise ye him in the firmament of his power.&#xA;2 Praise ye him for his mighty acts: praise ye him according to the multitude of his greatness.&#xA;3 Praise him with the sound of trumpet: praise him with psaltery and harp.&#xA;4 Praise him with timbrel and choir: praise him with strings and organs.&#xA;5 Praise him on high sounding cymbals: praise him on cymbals of joy: let every spirit praise the Lord.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 18</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap018/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap018/</guid>
      <description>1 Unto the end. A Psalm for David.&#xA;2 The heavens shew forth the glory of God, and the firmament declareth the work of his hands.&#xA;3 Day to day uttereth speech, and night to night sheweth knowledge.&#xA;4 There are no speeches nor languages, where their voices are not heard.&#xA;5 Their sound hath gone forth into all the earth: and their words unto the ends of the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 19</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap019/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap019/</guid>
      <description>1 Unto the end. A psalm for David.&#xA;2 May the Lord hear thee in the day of tribulation: may the name of the God of Jacob protect thee.&#xA;3 May he send thee help from the sanctuary: and defend thee out of Sion.&#xA;4 May he be mindful of all thy sacrifices: and may thy whole burntoffering be made fat.&#xA;5 May he give thee according to thy own heart; and confirm all thy counsels.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 20</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap020/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap020/</guid>
      <description>1 Unto the end. A psalm for David.&#xA;2 In thy strength, O Lord, the king shall joy; and in thy salvation he shall rejoice exceedingly.&#xA;3 Thou hast given him his heart&amp;rsquo;s desire: and hast not withholden from him the will of his lips.&#xA;4 For thou hast prevented him with blessings of sweetness: thou hast set on his head a crown of precious stones.&#xA;5 He asked life of thee: and thou hast given him length of days for ever and ever.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 21</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap021/</guid>
      <description>1 Unto the end, for the morning protection, a psalm for David.&#xA;2 O God my God, look upon me: why hast thou forsaken me? Far from my salvation are the words of my sins.&#xA;3 O my God, I shall cry by day, and thou wilt not hear: and by night, and it shall not be reputed as folly in me.&#xA;4 But thou dwellest in the holy place, the praise of Israel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 22</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap022/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap022/</guid>
      <description>1 A psalm for David. The Lord ruleth me: and I shall want nothing.&#xA;2 He hath set me in a place of pasture. He hath brought me up, on the water of refreshment:&#xA;3 He hath converted my soul. He hath led me on the paths of justice, for his own name&amp;rsquo;s sake.&#xA;4 For though I should walk in the midst of the shadow of death, I will fear no evils, for thou art with me.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 23</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap023/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap023/</guid>
      <description>1 On the first day of the week, a psalm for David. The earth is the Lord&amp;rsquo;s and the fulness thereof: the world, and all they that dwell therein.&#xA;2 For he hath founded it upon the seas; and hath prepared it upon the rivers.&#xA;3 Who shall ascend into the mountain of the Lord: or who shall stand in his holy place?&#xA;4 The innocent in hands, and clean of heart, who hath not taken his soul in vain, nor sworn deceitfully to his neighbour.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 24</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap024/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap024/</guid>
      <description>1 Unto the end, a psalm for David. To thee, O Lord, have I lifted up my soul.&#xA;2 In thee, O my God, I put my trust; let me not be ashamed.&#xA;3 Neither let my enemies laugh at me: for none of them that wait on thee shall be confounded.&#xA;4 Let all them be confounded that act unjust things without cause. Shew, O Lord, thy ways to me, and teach me thy paths.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 25</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap025/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap025/</guid>
      <description>1 Unto the end, a psalm for David. Judge me, O Lord, for I have walked in my innocence: and I have put my trust in the Lord, and shall not be weakened.&#xA;2 Prove me, O Lord, and try me; burn my reins and my heart.&#xA;3 For thy mercy is before my eyes; and I am well pleased with thy truth.&#xA;4 I have not sat with the council of vanity: neither will I go in with the doers of unjust things.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 26</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap026/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap026/</guid>
      <description>1 The psalm of David before he was anointed. The Lord is my light and my salvation, whom shall I fear? The Lord is the protector of my life: of whom shall I be afraid?&#xA;2 Whilst the wicked draw near against me, to eat my flesh. My enemies that trouble me, have themselves been weakened, and have fallen.&#xA;3 If armies in camp should stand together against me, my heart shall not fear.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 27</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap027/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap027/</guid>
      <description>1 A psalm for David himself. Unto thee will I cry, O Lord: O my God, be not thou silent to me: lest if thou be silent to me, I become like them that go down into the pit.&#xA;2 Hear, O Lord, the voice of my supplication, when I pray to thee; when I lift up my hands to thy holy temple.&#xA;3 Draw me not away together with the wicked; and with the workers of iniquity destroy me not: Who speak peace with their neighbour, but evils are in their hearts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 28</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap028/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap028/</guid>
      <description>1 A psalm for David, at the finishing of the tabernacle. Bring to the Lord, O ye children of God: bring to the Lord the offspring of rams.&#xA;2 Bring to the Lord glory and honour: bring to the Lord glory to his name: adore ye the Lord in his holy court.&#xA;3 The voice of the Lord is upon the waters; the God of majesty hath thundered, The Lord is upon many waters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 29</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap029/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap029/</guid>
      <description>1 A psalm of a canticle, at the dedication of David&amp;rsquo;s house.&#xA;2 I will extol thee, O Lord, for thou hast upheld me: and hast not made my enemies to rejoice over me.&#xA;3 O Lord my God, I have cried to thee, and thou hast healed me.&#xA;4 Thou hast brought forth, O Lord, my soul from hell: thou hast saved me from them that go down into the pit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 30</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap030/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap030/</guid>
      <description>1 Unto the end, a psalm for David, in an ecstasy.&#xA;2 In thee, O Lord, have I hoped, let me never be confounded: deliver me in thy justice.&#xA;3 Bow down thy ear to me: make haste to deliver me. Be thou unto me a God, a protector, and a house of refuge, to save me.&#xA;4 For thou art my strength and my refuge; and for thy name&amp;rsquo;s sake thou wilt lead me, and nourish me.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 31</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap031/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap031/</guid>
      <description>1 To David himself, understanding. Blessed are they whose iniquities are forgiven, and whose sins are covered.&#xA;2 Blessed is the man to whom the Lord hath not imputed sin, and in whose spirit there is no guile.&#xA;3 Because I was silent my bones grew old; whilst I cried out all the day long.&#xA;4 For day and night thy hand was heavy upon me: I am turned in my anguish, whilst the thorn is fastened.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 32</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap032/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap032/</guid>
      <description>1 A psalm for David. Rejoice in the Lord, O ye just: praise becometh the upright.&#xA;2 Give praise to the Lord on the harp; sing to him with the psaltery, the instrument of ten strings.&#xA;3 Sing to him a new canticle, sing well unto him with a loud noise.&#xA;4 For the word of the Lord is right, and all his works are done with faithfulness.&#xA;5 He loveth mercy and judgment; the earth is full of the mercy of the Lord.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 33</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap033/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap033/</guid>
      <description>1 For David, when he changed his countenance before Achimelech, who dismissed him, and he went his way.&#xA;2 I will bless the Lord at all times, his praise shall be always in my mouth.&#xA;3 In the Lord shall my soul be praised: let the meek hear and rejoice.&#xA;4 O magnify the Lord with me; and let us extol his name together.&#xA;5 I sought the Lord, and he heard me; and he delivered me from all my troubles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 34</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap034/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap034/</guid>
      <description>1 For David himself. Judge thou, O Lord, them that wrong me: overthrow them that fight against me.&#xA;2 Take hold of arms and shield: and rise up to help me.&#xA;3 Bring out the sword, and shut up the way against them that persecute me: say to my soul: I am thy salvation.&#xA;4 Let them be confounded and ashamed that seek after my soul. Let them be turned back and be confounded that devise evil against me.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 35</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap035/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap035/</guid>
      <description>1 Unto the end, for the servant of God, David himself.&#xA;2 The unjust hath said within himself, that he would sin: there is no fear of God before his eyes.&#xA;3 For in his sight he hath done deceitfully, that his iniquity may be found unto hatred.&#xA;4 The words of his mouth are iniquity and guile: he would not understand that he might do well.&#xA;5 He hath devised iniquity on his bed, he hath set himself on every way that is not good: but evil he hath not hated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 36</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap036/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap036/</guid>
      <description>1 Be not emulous of evildoers; nor envy them that work iniquity.&#xA;2 For they shall shortly wither away as grass, and as the green herbs shall quickly fall.&#xA;3 Trust in the Lord, and do good, and dwell in the land, and thou shalt be fed with its riches.&#xA;4 Delight in the Lord, and he will give thee the requests of thy heart.&#xA;5 Commit thy way to the Lord, and trust in him, and he will do it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 37</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap037/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap037/</guid>
      <description>1 A psalm for David, for a remembrance of the sabbath.&#xA;2 Rebuke me not, O Lord, in thy indignation; nor chastise me in thy wrath.&#xA;3 For thy arrows are fastened in me: and thy hand hath been strong upon me.&#xA;4 There is no health in my flesh, because of thy wrath: there is no peace for my bones, because of my sins.&#xA;5 For my iniquities are gone over my head: and as a heavy burden are become heavy upon me.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 38</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap038/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap038/</guid>
      <description>1 Unto the end, for Idithun himself, a canticle of David.&#xA;2 I said: I will take heed to my ways: that I sin not with my tongue. I have set a guard to my mouth, when the sinner stood against me.&#xA;3 I was dumb, and was humbled, and kept silence from good things: and my sorrow was renewed.&#xA;4 My heart grew hot within me: and in my meditation a fire shall flame out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 39</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap039/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap039/</guid>
      <description>1 Unto the end, a psalm for David himself.&#xA;2 With expectation I have waited for the Lord, and he was attentive to me.&#xA;3 And he heard my prayers, and brought me out of the pit of misery and the mire of dregs. And he set my feet upon a rock, and directed my steps.&#xA;4 And he put a new canticle into my mouth, a song to our God.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 40</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap040/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap040/</guid>
      <description>1 Unto the end, a psalm for David himself.&#xA;2 Blessed is he that understandeth concerning the needy and the poor: the Lord will deliver him in the evil day.&#xA;3 The Lord preserve him and give him life, and make him blessed upon the earth: and deliver him not up to the will of his enemies.&#xA;4 The Lord help him on his bed of sorrow: thou hast turned all his couch in his sickness.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 41</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap041/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap041/</guid>
      <description>1 Unto the end, understanding for the sons of Core.&#xA;2 As the hart panteth after the fountains of water; so my soul panteth after thee, O God.&#xA;3 My soul hath thirsted after the strong living God; when shall I come and appear before the face of God?&#xA;4 My tears have been my bread day and night, whilst it is said to me daily: Where is thy God?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 42</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap042/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap042/</guid>
      <description>1 A psalm for David. Judge me, O God, and distinguish my cause from the nation that is not holy: deliver me from the unjust and deceitful man.&#xA;2 For thou art God my strength: why hast thou cast me off? and why do I go sorrowful whilst the enemy afflicteth me?&#xA;3 Sent forth thy light and thy truth: they have conducted me, and brought me unto thy holy hill, and into thy tabernacles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 43</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap043/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap043/</guid>
      <description>1 Unto the end, for the sons of Core, to give understanding.&#xA;2 We have heard, O God, with our ears: our fathers have declared to us, The work thou hast wrought in their days, and in the days of old.&#xA;3 Thy hand destroyed the Gentiles, and thou plantedst them: thou didst afflict the people and cast them out.&#xA;4 For they got not the possession of the land by their own sword: neither did their own arm save them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 44</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap044/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap044/</guid>
      <description>1 Unto the end, for them that shall be changed, for the sons of Core, for understanding. A canticle for the Beloved.&#xA;2 My heart hath uttered a good word: I speak my works to the king: My tongue is the pen of a scrivener that writeth swiftly.&#xA;3 Thou art beautiful above the sons of men: grace is poured abroad in thy lips; therefore hath God blessed thee for ever.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 45</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap045/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap045/</guid>
      <description>1 Unto the end, for the sons of Core, for the hidden.&#xA;2 Our God is our refuge and strength: a helper in troubles, which have found us exceedingly.&#xA;3 Therefore we will not fear, when the earth shall be troubled; and the mountains shall be removed into the heart of the sea.&#xA;4 Their waters roared and were troubled: the mountains were troubled with his strength.&#xA;5 The stream of the river maketh the city of God joyful: the most High hath sanctified his own tabernacle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 46</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap046/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap046/</guid>
      <description>1 Unto the end, for the sons of Core.&#xA;2 O clap your hands, all ye nations: shout unto God with the voice of joy,&#xA;3 For the Lord is high, terrible: a great king over all the earth.&#xA;4 He hath subdued the people under us; and the nations under our feet.&#xA;5 He hath chosen for us his inheritance, the beauty of Jacob which he hath loved.&#xA;6 God is ascended with jubilee, and the Lord with the sound of trumpet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 47</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap047/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap047/</guid>
      <description>1 A psalm of a canticle, for the sons of Core, on the second day of the week.&#xA;2 Great is the Lord, and exceedingly to be praised in the city of our God, in his holy mountain.&#xA;3 With the joy of the whole earth is mount Sion founded, on the sides of the north, the city of the great king.&#xA;4 In her houses shall God be known, when he shall protect her.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 48</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap048/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap048/</guid>
      <description>1 Unto the end, a psalm for the sons of Core.&#xA;2 Hear these things, all ye nations: give ear, all ye inhabitants of the world.&#xA;3 All you that are earthborn, and you sons of men: both rich and poor together.&#xA;4 My mouth shall speak wisdom: and the meditation of my heart understanding.&#xA;5 I will incline my ear to a parable; I will open my proposition on the psaltery.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 49</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap049/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap049/</guid>
      <description>1 A psalm for Asaph. The God of gods, the Lord hath spoken: and he hath called the earth. From the rising of the sun, to the going down thereof:&#xA;2 Out of Sion the loveliness of his beauty.&#xA;3 God shall come manifestly: our God shall come, and shall not keep silence. A fire shall burn before him: and a mighty tempest shall be round about him.&#xA;4 He shall call heaven from above, and the earth, to judge his people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 50</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap050/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap050/</guid>
      <description>1 Unto the end, a psalm of David,&#xA;2 When Nathan the prophet came to him, after he had sinned with Bethsabee.&#xA;3 Have mercy on me, O God, according to thy great mercy. And according to the multitude of thy tender mercies blot out my iniquity.&#xA;4 Wash me yet more from my iniquity, and cleanse me from my sin.&#xA;5 For I know my iniquity, and my sin is always before me.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 51</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap051/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap051/</guid>
      <description>1 Unto the end, understanding for David,&#xA;2 When Doeg the Edomite came and told Saul: David went to the house of Achimelech.&#xA;3 Why dost thou glory in malice, thou that art mighty in iniquity?&#xA;4 All the day long thy tongue hath devised injustice: as a sharp razor, thou hast wrought deceit.&#xA;5 Thou hast loved malice more than goodness: and iniquity rather than to speak righteousness.&#xA;6 Thou hast loved all the words of ruin, O deceitful tongue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 52</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap052/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap052/</guid>
      <description>1 Unto the end, for Maeleth, understandings to David. The fool said in his heart: There is no God.&#xA;2 They are corrupted, and become abominable in iniquities: there is none that doth good.&#xA;3 God looked down from heaven on the children of men: to see if there were any that did understand, or did seek God.&#xA;4 All have gone aside, they are become unprofitable together, there is none that doth good, no not one.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 53</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap053/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap053/</guid>
      <description>1 Unto the end, in verses, understanding for David.&#xA;2 When the men of Ziph had come and said to Saul: Is not David hidden with us?&#xA;3 Save me, O God, by thy name, and judge me in thy strength.&#xA;4 O God, hear my prayer: give ear to the words of my mouth.&#xA;5 For strangers have risen up against me; and the mighty have sought after my soul: and they have not set God before their eyes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 54</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap054/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap054/</guid>
      <description>1 Unto the end, in verses, understanding for David.&#xA;2 Hear, O God, my prayer, and despise not my supplication:&#xA;3 Be attentive to me and hear me. I am grieved in my exercise; and am troubled,&#xA;4 At the voice of the enemy, and at the tribulation of the sinner. For they have cast iniquities upon me: and in wrath they were troublesome to me.&#xA;5 My heart is troubled within me: and the fear of death is fallen upon me.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 55</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap055/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap055/</guid>
      <description>1 Unto the end, for a people that is removed at a distance from the sanctuary: for David, for an inscription of a title (or pillar) when the Philistines held him in Geth.&#xA;2 Have mercy on me, O God, for man hath trodden me under foot; all the day long he hath afflicted me fighting against me.&#xA;3 My enemies have trodden on me all the day long; for they are many that make war against me.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 56</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap056/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap056/</guid>
      <description>1 Unto the end, destroy not, for David, for an inscription of a title, when he fled from Saul into the cave.&#xA;2 Have mercy on me, O God, have mercy on me: for my soul trusteth in thee. And in the shadow of thy wings will I hope, until iniquity pass away.&#xA;3 I will cry to God the most high; to God who hath done good to me.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 57</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap057/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap057/</guid>
      <description>1 Unto the end, destroy not, for David, for an inscription of a title.&#xA;2 If in very deed ye speak justice: judge right things, ye sons of men.&#xA;3 For in your heart you work iniquity: your hands forge injustice in the earth.&#xA;4 The wicked are alienated from the womb; they have gone astray from the womb: they have spoken false things.&#xA;5 Their madness is according to the likeness of a serpent: like the deaf asp that stoppeth her ears:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 58</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap058/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap058/</guid>
      <description>1 Unto the end, destroy not, for David for an inscription of a title, when Saul sent and watched his house to kill him.&#xA;2 Deliver me from my enemies, O my God; and defend me from them that rise up against me.&#xA;3 Deliver me from them that work iniquity, and save me from bloody men.&#xA;4 For behold they have caught my soul: the mighty have rushed in upon me:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 59</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap059/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap059/</guid>
      <description>1 Unto the end, for them that shall be changed, for the inscription of a title, to David himself, for doctrine,&#xA;2 When he set fire to Mesopotamia of Syria and Sobal: and Joab returned and slew of Edom, in the vale of the saltpits, twelve thousand men.&#xA;3 O God, thou hast cast us off, and hast destroyed us; thou hast been angry, and hast had mercy on us.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 60</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap060/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap060/</guid>
      <description>1 Unto the end, in hymns, for David.&#xA;2 Hear, O God, my supplication: be attentive to my prayer.&#xA;3 To thee have I cried from the ends of the earth: when my heart was in anguish, thou hast exalted me on a rock. Thou hast conducted me;&#xA;4 For thou hast been my hope; a tower of strength against the face of the enemy.&#xA;5 In thy tabernacle I shall dwell for ever: I shall be protected under the covert of thy wings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 61</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap061/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap061/</guid>
      <description>1 Unto the end, for Idithun, a psalm of David.&#xA;2 Shall not my soul be subject to God? for from him is my salvation.&#xA;3 For he is my God and my saviour: he is my protector, I shall be moved no more.&#xA;4 How long do you rush in upon a man? you all kill, as if you were thrusting down a leaning wall, and a tottering fence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 62</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap062/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap062/</guid>
      <description>1 A psalm of David while he was in the desert of Edom.&#xA;2 O God, my God, to thee do I watch at break of day. For thee my soul hath thirsted; for thee my flesh, O how many ways!&#xA;3 In a desert land, and where there is no way, and no water: so in the sanctuary have I come before thee, to see thy power and thy glory.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 63</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap063/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap063/</guid>
      <description>1 Unto the end, a psalm for David.&#xA;2 Hear O God, my prayer, when I make supplication to thee: deliver my soul from the fear of the enemy.&#xA;3 Thou hast protected me from the assembly of the malignant; from the multitude of the workers of iniquity.&#xA;4 For they have whetted their tongues like a sword; they have bent their bow a bitter thing,&#xA;5 To shoot in secret the undefiled.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 64</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap064/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap064/</guid>
      <description>1 To the end, a psalm of David. The canticle of Jeremias and Ezechiel to the people of the captivity, when they began to go out.&#xA;2 A hymn, O God, becometh thee in Sion: and a vow shall be paid to thee in Jerusalem.&#xA;3 O hear my prayer: all flesh shall come to thee.&#xA;4 The words of the wicked have prevailed over us: and thou wilt pardon our transgressions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 65</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap065/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap065/</guid>
      <description>1 Unto the end, a canticle of a psalm of the resurrection. Shout with joy to God, all the earth,&#xA;2 Sing ye a psalm to his name; give glory to his praise.&#xA;3 Say unto God, How terrible are thy works, O Lord! in the multitude of thy strength thy enemies shall lie to thee.&#xA;4 Let all the earth adore thee, and sing to thee: let it sing a psalm to thy name.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 66</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap066/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap066/</guid>
      <description>1 Unto the end, in hymns, a psalm of a canticle for David.&#xA;2 May God have mercy on us, and bless us: may he cause the light of his countenance to shine upon us, and may he have mercy on us.&#xA;3 That we may know thy way upon earth: thy salvation in all nations.&#xA;4 Let people confess to thee, O God: let all people give praise to thee.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 67</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap067/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap067/</guid>
      <description>1 Unto the end, a psalm of a canticle for David himself.&#xA;2 Let God arise, and let his enemies be scattered: and let them that hate him flee from before his face.&#xA;3 As smoke vanisheth, so let them vanish away: as wax melteth before the fire, so let the wicked perish at the presence of God.&#xA;4 And let the just feast, and rejoice before God: and be delighted with gladness.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 68</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap068/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap068/</guid>
      <description>1 Unto the end, for them that shall be changed; for David.&#xA;2 Save me, O God: for the waters are come in even unto my soul.&#xA;3 I stick fast in the mire of the deep and there is no sure standing. I am come into the depth of the sea, and a tempest hath overwhelmed me.&#xA;4 I have laboured with crying; my jaws are become hoarse, my eyes have failed, whilst I hope in my God.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 69</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap069/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap069/</guid>
      <description>1 Unto the end, a psalm for David, to bring to remembrance that the Lord saved him.&#xA;2 O God, come to my assistance; O Lord, make haste to help me.&#xA;3 Let them be confounded and ashamed that seek my soul:&#xA;4 Let them be turned backward, and blush for shame that desire evils to me: Let them be presently turned away blushing for shame that say to me: &amp;lsquo;Tis well, &amp;rsquo;tis well.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 70</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap070/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap070/</guid>
      <description>1 A psalm for David. Of the sons of Jonadab, and the former captives. In thee, O Lord, I have hoped, let me never be put to confusion:&#xA;2 Deliver me in thy justice, and rescue me. Incline thy ear unto me, and save me.&#xA;3 Be thou unto me a God, a protector, and a place of strength: that thou mayst make me safe. For thou art my firmament and my refuge.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 71</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap071/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap071/</guid>
      <description>1 A psalm on Solomon.&#xA;2 Give to the king thy judgment, O God, and to the king&amp;rsquo;s son thy justice: To judge thy people with justice, and thy poor with judgment.&#xA;3 Let the mountains receive peace for the people: and the hills justice.&#xA;4 He shall judge the poor of the people, and he shall save the children of the poor: and he shall humble the oppressor.&#xA;5 And he shall continue with the sun and before the moon, throughout all generations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 72</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap072/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap072/</guid>
      <description>1 A psalm for Asaph. How good is God to Israel, to them that are of a right heart!&#xA;2 But my feet were almost moved; my steps had well nigh slipped.&#xA;3 Because I had a zeal on occasion of the wicked, seeing the prosperity of sinners.&#xA;4 For there is no regard to their death, nor is there strength in their stripes.&#xA;5 They are not in the labour of men: neither shall they be scourged like other men.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 73</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap073/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap073/</guid>
      <description>1 Understanding for Asaph. O God, why hast thou cast us off unto the end: why is thy wrath enkindled against the sheep of thy pasture?&#xA;2 Remember thy congregation, which thou hast possessed from the beginning. The sceptre of thy inheritance which thou hast redeemed: mount Sion in which thou hast dwelt.&#xA;3 Lift up thy hands against their pride unto the end; see what things the enemy hath done wickedly in the sanctuary.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 74</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap074/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap074/</guid>
      <description>1 Unto the end, corrupt not, a psalm of a canticle for Asaph.&#xA;2 We will praise thee, O God: we will praise, and we will call upon thy name. We will relate thy wondrous works:&#xA;3 When I shall take a time, I will judge justices.&#xA;4 The earth is melted, and all that dwell therein: I have established the pillars thereof.&#xA;5 I said to the wicked: Do not act wickedly: and to the sinners: Lift not up the horn.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 75</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap075/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap075/</guid>
      <description>1 Unto the end, in praises, a psalm for Asaph: a canticle to the Assyrians.&#xA;2 In Judea God is known: his name is great in Israel.&#xA;3 And his place is in peace: and his abode in Sion:&#xA;4 There hath he broken the powers of bows, the shield, the sword, and the battle.&#xA;5 Thou enlightenest wonderfully from the everlasting hills.&#xA;6 All the foolish of heart were troubled.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 76</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap076/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap076/</guid>
      <description>1 Unto the end, for Idithun, a psalm of Asaph.&#xA;2 I cried to the Lord with my voice; to God with my voice, and he gave ear to me.&#xA;3 In the days of my trouble I sought God, with my hands lifted up to him in the night, and I was not deceived. My soul refused to be comforted:&#xA;4 I remembered God, and was delighted, and was exercised, and my spirit swooned away.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 77</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap077/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap077/</guid>
      <description>1 Understanding for Asaph. Attend, O my people, to my law: incline your ears to the words of my mouth.&#xA;2 I will open my mouth in parables: I will utter propositions from the beginning.&#xA;3 How great things have we heard and known, and our fathers have told us.&#xA;4 They have not been hidden from their children, in another generation. Declaring the praises of the Lord, and his powers, and his wonders which he hath done.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 78</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap078/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap078/</guid>
      <description>1 A psalm for Asaph. O God, the heathens are come into thy inheritance, they have defiled thy holy temple: they have made Jerusalem as a place to keep fruit.&#xA;2 They have given the dead bodies of thy servants to be meat for the fowls of the air: the flesh of thy saints for the beasts of the earth.&#xA;3 They have poured out their blood as water, round about Jerusalem and there was none to bury them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 79</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap079/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap079/</guid>
      <description>1 Unto the end, for them that shall be changed, a testimony for Asaph, a psalm.&#xA;2 Give ear, O thou that rulest Israel: thou that leadest Joseph like a sheep. Thou that sittest upon the cherubims, shine forth&#xA;3 Before Ephraim, Benjamin, and Manasses. Stir up thy might, and come to save us.&#xA;4 Convert us, O God: and shew us thy face, and we shall be saved.&#xA;5 O Lord God of hosts, how long wilt thou be angry against the prayer of thy servant?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 80</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap080/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap080/</guid>
      <description>1 Unto the end, for the winepresses, a psalm for Asaph himself.&#xA;2 Rejoice to God our helper: sing aloud to the God of Jacob.&#xA;3 Take a psalm, and bring hither the timbrel: the pleasant psaltery with the harp.&#xA;4 Blow up the trumpet on the new moon, on the noted day of your solemnity.&#xA;5 For it is a commandment in Israel, and a judgment to the God of Jacob.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 81</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap081/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap081/</guid>
      <description>1 A psalm for Asaph. God hath stood in the congregation of gods: and being in the midst of them he judgeth gods.&#xA;2 How long will you judge unjustly: and accept the persons of the wicked?&#xA;3 Judge for the needy and fatherless: do justice to the humble and the poor.&#xA;4 Rescue the poor; and deliver the needy out of the hand of the sinner.&#xA;5 They have not known nor understood: they walk on in darkness: all the foundations of the earth shall be moved.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 82</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap082/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap082/</guid>
      <description>1 A canticle of a psalm for Asaph.&#xA;2 O God, who shall be like to thee? hold not thy peace, neither be thou still, O God.&#xA;3 For lo, thy enemies have made a noise: and they that hate thee have lifted up the head.&#xA;4 They have taken a malicious counsel against thy people, and have consulted against thy saints.&#xA;5 They have said: Come and let us destroy them, so that they be not a nation: and let the name of Israel be remembered no more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 83</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap083/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap083/</guid>
      <description>1 Unto the end, for the winepresses, a psalm for the sons of Core.&#xA;2 How lovely are thy tabernacles, O Lord of hosts!&#xA;3 my soul longeth and fainteth for the courts of the Lord. My heart and my flesh have rejoiced in the living God.&#xA;4 For the sparrow hath found herself a house, and the turtle a nest for herself where she may lay her young ones: Thy altars, O Lord of hosts, my king and my God.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 84</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap084/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap084/</guid>
      <description>1 Unto the end, for the sons of Core, a psalm.&#xA;2 Lord, thou hast blessed thy land: thou hast turned away the captivity of Jacob.&#xA;3 Thou hast forgiven the iniquity of thy people: thou hast covered all their sins.&#xA;4 Thou hast mitigated all thy anger: thou hast turned away from the wrath of thy indignation.&#xA;5 Convert us, O God our saviour: and turn off thy anger from us.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 85</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap085/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap085/</guid>
      <description>1 A prayer for David himself. Incline thy ear, O Lord, and hear me: for I am needy and poor.&#xA;2 Preserve my soul, for I am holy: save thy servant, O my God, that trusteth in thee.&#xA;3 Have mercy on me, O Lord, for I have cried to thee all the day.&#xA;4 Give joy to the soul of thy servant, for to thee, O Lord, I have lifted up my soul.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 86</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap086/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap086/</guid>
      <description>1 For the sons of Core, a psalm of a canticle. The foundations thereof are the holy mountains:&#xA;2 The Lord loveth the gates of Sion above all the tabernacles of Jacob.&#xA;3 Glorious things are said of thee, O city of God.&#xA;4 I will be mindful of Rahab and of Babylon knowing me. Behold the foreigners, and Tyre, and the people of the Ethiopians, these were there.&#xA;5 Shall not Sion say: This man and that man is born in her?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 87</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap087/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap087/</guid>
      <description>1 A canticle of a psalm for the sons of Core: unto the end, for Maheleth, to answer understanding of Eman the Ezrahite.&#xA;2 O Lord, the God of my salvation: I have cried in the day, and in the night before thee.&#xA;3 Let my prayer come in before thee: incline thy ear to my petition.&#xA;4 For my soul is filled with evils: and my life hath drawn nigh to hell.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 88</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap088/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap088/</guid>
      <description>1 Of understanding, for Ethan the Ezrahite.&#xA;2 The mercies of the Lord I will sing for ever. I will shew forth thy truth with my mouth to generation and generation.&#xA;3 For thou hast said: Mercy shall be built up for ever in the heavens: thy truth shall be prepared in them.&#xA;4 I have made a covenant with my elect: I have sworn to David my servant:&#xA;5 Thy seed will I settle for ever.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 89</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap089/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap089/</guid>
      <description>1 A prayer of Moses the man of God. Lord, thou hast been our refuge from generation to generation.&#xA;2 Before the mountains were made, or the earth and the world was formed; from eternity and to eternity thou art God.&#xA;3 Turn not man away to be brought low: and thou hast said: Be converted, O ye sons of men.&#xA;4 For a thousand years in thy sight are as yesterday, which is past.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 90</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap090/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap090/</guid>
      <description>1 The praise of a canticle for David. He that dwelleth in the aid of the most High, shall abide under the protection of the God of Jacob.&#xA;2 He shall say to the Lord: Thou art my protector, and my refuge: my God, in him will I trust.&#xA;3 For he hath delivered me from the snare of the hunters: and from the sharp word.&#xA;4 He will overshadow thee with his shoulders: and under his wings thou shalt trust.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 91</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap091/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap091/</guid>
      <description>1 A psalm of a canticle on the sabbath day.&#xA;2 It is good to give praise to the Lord: and to sing to thy name, O most High.&#xA;3 To shew forth thy mercy in the morning, and thy truth in the night:&#xA;4 Upon an instrument of ten strings, upon the psaltery: with a canticle upon the harp.&#xA;5 For thou hast given me, O Lord, a delight in thy doings: and in the works of thy hands I shall rejoice.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 92</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap092/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap092/</guid>
      <description>1 The Lord hath reigned, he is clothed with beauty: the Lord is clothed with strength, and hath girded himself. For he hath established the world which shall not be moved.&#xA;2 My throne is prepared from of old: thou art from everlasting.&#xA;3 The floods have lifted up, O Lord: the floods have lifted up their voice. The floods have lifted up their waves,&#xA;4 With the noise of many waters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 93</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap093/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap093/</guid>
      <description>1 The Lord is the God to whom revenge belongeth: the God of revenge hath acted freely.&#xA;2 Lift up thyself, thou that judgest the earth: render a reward to the proud.&#xA;3 How long shall sinners, O Lord: how long shall sinners glory?&#xA;4 Shall they utter, and speak iniquity: shall all speak who work injustice?&#xA;5 Thy people, O Lord, they have brought low: and they have afflicted thy inheritance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 94</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap094/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap094/</guid>
      <description>1 Come let us praise the Lord with joy: let us joyfully sing to God our saviour.&#xA;2 Let us come before his presence with thanksgiving; and make a joyful noise to him with psalms.&#xA;3 For the Lord is a great God, and a great King above all gods.&#xA;4 For in his hand are all the ends of the earth: and the heights of the mountains are his.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 95</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap095/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap095/</guid>
      <description>1 A canticle for David himself, when the house was built after the captivity. Sing ye to the Lord a new canticle: sing to the Lord, all the earth.&#xA;2 Sing ye to the Lord and bless his name: shew forth his salvation from day to day.&#xA;3 Declare his glory among the Gentiles: his wonders among all people.&#xA;4 For the Lord is great, and exceedingly to be praised: he is to be feared above all gods.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 96</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap096/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap096/</guid>
      <description>1 For the same David, when his land was restored again to him. The Lord hath reigned, let the earth rejoice: let many islands be glad.&#xA;2 Clouds and darkness are round about him: justice and judgment are the establishment of his throne.&#xA;3 A fire shall go before him, and shall burn his enemies round about.&#xA;4 His lightnings have shone forth to the world: the earth saw and trembled.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 97</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap097/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap097/</guid>
      <description>1 A psalm for David himself. Sing ye to the Lord a new canticle: because he hath done wonderful things. His right hand hath wrought for him salvation, and his arm is holy.&#xA;2 The Lord hath made known his salvation: he hath revealed his justice in the sight of the Gentiles.&#xA;3 He hath remembered his mercy and his truth toward the house of Israel. All the ends of the earth have seen the salvation of our God.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 98</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap098/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap098/</guid>
      <description>1 A psalm for David himself. The Lord hath reigned, let the people be angry: he that sitteth on the cherubims: let the earth be moved.&#xA;2 The Lord is great in Sion, and high above all people.&#xA;3 Let them give praise to thy great name: for it is terrible and holy:&#xA;4 And the king&amp;rsquo;s honour loveth judgment. Thou hast prepared directions: thou hast done judgment and justice in Jacob.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 99</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap099/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap099/</guid>
      <description>1 A psalm of praise.&#xA;2 Sing joyfully to God, all the earth: serve ye the Lord with gladness. Come in before his presence with exceeding great joy.&#xA;3 Know ye that the Lord he is God: he made us, and not we ourselves. We are his people and the sheep of his pasture.&#xA;4 Go ye into his gates with praise, into his courts with hymns: and give glory to him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 1</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap001/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap001/</guid>
      <description>1 Blessed is the man who hath not walked in the counsel of the ungodly, nor stood in the way of sinners, nor sat in the chair of pestilence:&#xA;2 But his will is in the law of the Lord, and on his law he shall meditate day and night.&#xA;3 And he shall be like a tree which is planted near the running waters, which shall bring forth its fruit, in due season.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 10</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap010/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap010/</guid>
      <description>1 Unto the end. A psalm to David.&#xA;2 In the Lord I put my trust: how then do you say to my soul: Get thee away from hence to the mountain, like a sparrow.&#xA;3 For, lo, the wicked have bent their bow: they have prepared their arrows in the quiver, to shoot in the dark the upright of heart.&#xA;4 For they have destroyed the things which thou hast made: but what has the just man done?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 11</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap011/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap011/</guid>
      <description>1 Unto the end: for the octave, a psalm for David.&#xA;2 Save me, O Lord, for there is now no saint: truths are decayed from among the children of men.&#xA;3 They have spoken vain things, every one to his neighbour: with deceitful lips, and with a double heart have they spoken.&#xA;4 May the Lord destroy all deceitful lips, and the tongue that speaketh proud things.&#xA;5 Who have said: We will magnify our tongue: our lips are our own: who is Lord over us?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 12</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap012/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap012/</guid>
      <description>1 Unto the end, a psalm for David. How long, O Lord, wilt thou forget me unto the end? how long dost thou turn away thy face from me?&#xA;2 How long shall I take counsels in my soul, sorrow in my heart all the day?&#xA;3 How long shall my enemy be exalted over me?&#xA;4 Consider, and hear me, O Lord, my God. Enlighten my eyes, that I never sleep in death:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 13</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap013/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap013/</guid>
      <description>1 Unto the end, a psalm for David. The fool hath said in his heart: There is no God. They are corrupt, and are become abominable in their ways: there is none that doth good, no not one.&#xA;2 The Lord hath looked down from heaven upon the children of men, to see if there be any that understand and seek God.&#xA;3 They are all gone aside, they are become unprofitable together: there is none that doth good: no not one.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 14</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap014/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap014/</guid>
      <description>1 A psalm for David. Lord, who shall dwell in thy tabernacle? or who shall rest in thy holy hill?&#xA;2 He that walketh without blemish, and worketh justice:&#xA;3 He that speaketh truth in his heart, who hath not used deceit in his tongue: Nor hath done evil to his neighbour: nor taken up a reproach against his neighbours.&#xA;4 In his sight the malignant is brought to nothing: but he glorifieth them that fear the Lord.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 15</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap015/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap015/</guid>
      <description>1 The inscription of a title to David himself. Preserve me, O Lord, for I have put my trust in thee.&#xA;2 I have said to the Lord, thou art my God, for thou hast no need of my goods.&#xA;3 To the saints, who are in his land, he hath made wonderful all my desires in them.&#xA;4 Their infirmities were multiplied: afterwards they made haste. I will not gather together their meetings for bloodofferings: nor will I be mindful of their names by my lips.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 16</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap016/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap016/</guid>
      <description>1 The prayer of David. Hear, O Lord, my justice: attend to my supplication. Give ear unto my prayer, which proceedeth not from deceitful lips.&#xA;2 Let my judgment come forth from thy countenance: let thy eyes behold the things that are equitable.&#xA;3 Thou hast proved my heart, and visited it by night, thou hast tried me by fire: and iniquity hath not been found in me.&#xA;4 That my mouth may not speak the works of men: for the sake of the words of thy lips, I have kept hard ways.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 17</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap017/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap017/</guid>
      <description>1 Unto the end, for David, the servant of the Lord, who spoke to the Lord the words of this canticle, in the day that the Lord delivered him from the hand of all his enemies, and from the hand of Saul: and he said:&#xA;2 I will love thee, O Lord, my strength:&#xA;3 The Lord is my firmament, my refuge, and my deliverer. My God is my helper, and in him will I put my trust.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 2</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap002/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap002/</guid>
      <description>1 Why have the Gentiles raged, and the people devised vain things?&#xA;2 The kings of the earth stood up, and the princes met together, against the Lord, and against his Christ.&#xA;3 Let us break their bonds asunder: and let us cast away their yoke from us.&#xA;4 He that dwelleth in heaven shall laugh at them: and the Lord shall deride them.&#xA;5 Then shall he speak to them in his anger, and trouble them in his rage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 3</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap003/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap003/</guid>
      <description>1 The psalm of David when he fled from the face of his son Absalom.&#xA;2 Why, O Lord, are they multiplied that afflict me? many are they who rise up against me.&#xA;3 Many say to my soul: There is no salvation for him in his God.&#xA;4 But thou, O Lord, art my protector, my glory, and the lifter up of my head.&#xA;5 I have cried to the Lord with my voice: and he hath heard me from his holy hill.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 4</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap004/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap004/</guid>
      <description>1 Unto the end, in verses. A psalm for David.&#xA;2 When I called upon him, the God of my justice heard me: when I was in distress, thou hast enlarged me. Have mercy on me: and hear my prayer.&#xA;3 O ye sons of men, how long will you be dull of heart? why do you love vanity, and seek after lying?&#xA;4 Know ye also that the Lord hath made his holy one wonderful: the Lord will hear me when I shall cry unto him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 5</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap005/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap005/</guid>
      <description>1 Unto the end, for her that obtaineth the inheritance. A psalm for David.&#xA;2 Give ear, O Lord, to my words, understand my cry.&#xA;3 Hearken to the voice of my prayer, O my King and my God.&#xA;4 For to thee will I pray: O Lord, in the morning thou shalt hear my voice.&#xA;5 In the morning I will stand before thee, and I will see: because thou art not a God that willest iniquity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 6</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap006/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap006/</guid>
      <description>1 Unto the end, in verses, a psalm for David, for the octave.&#xA;2 O Lord, rebuke me not in thy indignation, nor chastise me in thy wrath.&#xA;3 Have mercy on me, O Lord, for I am weak: heal me, O Lord, for my bones are troubled.&#xA;4 And my soul is troubled exceedingly: but thou, O Lord, how long?&#xA;5 Turn to me, O Lord, and deliver my soul: O save me for thy mercy&amp;rsquo;s sake.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 7</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap007/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap007/</guid>
      <description>1 The psalm of David, which he sung to the Lord, for the words of Chusi, the son of Jemini.&#xA;2 O Lord, my God, in thee have I put my trust; save me from all them that persecute me, and deliver me.&#xA;3 Lest at any time he seize upon my soul like a lion, while there is no one to redeem me, nor to save.&#xA;4 O Lord, my God, if I have done this thing, if there be iniquity in my hands:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 8</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap008/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap008/</guid>
      <description>1 Unto the end, for the presses: a psalm for David.&#xA;2 O Lord, our Lord, how admirable is thy name in the whole earth! For thy magnificence is elevated above the heavens.&#xA;3 Out of the mouth of infants and of sucklings thou hast perfected praise, because of thy enemies, that thou mayst destroy the enemy and the avenger.&#xA;4 For I will behold thy heavens, the works of thy fingers: the moon and the stars which thou hast founded.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 9</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap009/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/48-psalms/chap009/</guid>
      <description>1 Unto the end, for the hidden things of the Son. A psalm for David.&#xA;2 I will give praise to thee, O Lord, with my whole heart: I will relate all thy wonders.&#xA;3 I will be glad, and rejoice in thee: I will sing to thy name, O thou most high.&#xA;4 When my enemy shall be turned back: they shall be weakened, and perish before thy face.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
