<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mark on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/02-mark/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Mark on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:35 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/02-mark/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 1</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/02-mark/chap001/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:35 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/02-mark/chap001/</guid>
      <description>1 The beginning of the gospel of Jesus Christ, the Son of God.&#xA;2 As it is written in Isaias the prophet: Behold I send my angel before thy face, who shall prepare the way before thee.&#xA;3 A voice of one crying in the desert: Prepare ye the way of the Lord; make straight his paths.&#xA;4 John was in the desert, baptizing and preaching the baptism of penance, unto remission of sins.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 10</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/02-mark/chap010/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:35 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/02-mark/chap010/</guid>
      <description>1 And rising up from thence, he cometh into the coast of Judea beyond the Jordan: and the multitude flocked to him again. And as he was accustomed, he taught them again.&#xA;2 And the Pharisees coming to him asked him, tempting him: Is it lawful for a man to put away his wife?&#xA;3 But he answering, saith to them: What did Moses command you?&#xA;4 Who said: Moses permitted to write a bill of divorce and to put her away.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 11</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/02-mark/chap011/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:35 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/02-mark/chap011/</guid>
      <description>1 And when they were drawing near to Jerusalem and to Bethania, at the mount of Olives, he sendeth two of his disciples,&#xA;2 And saith to them: Go into the village that is over against you, and immediately at your coming in thither, you shall find a colt tied, upon which no man yet hath sat. Loose him and bring him.&#xA;3 And if any man shall say to you: What are you doing?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 12</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/02-mark/chap012/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:35 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/02-mark/chap012/</guid>
      <description>1 And he began to speak to them in parables: A certain man planted a vineyard and made a hedge about it and dug a place for the winefat and built a tower and let it to husbandmen: and went into a far country.&#xA;2 And at the season he sent to the husbandmen a servant to receive of the husbandmen of the fruit of the vineyard.&#xA;3 Who, having laid hands on him, beat and sent him away empty.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 13</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/02-mark/chap013/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:35 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/02-mark/chap013/</guid>
      <description>1 And as he was going out of the temple, one of his disciples said to him: Master, behold what manner of stones and what buildings are here.&#xA;2 And Jesus answering, said to him: Seest thou all these great buildings? There shall not be left a stone upon a stone, that shall not be thrown down.&#xA;3 And as he sat on the mount of Olivet over against the temple, Peter and James and John and Andrew asked him apart:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 14</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/02-mark/chap014/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:35 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/02-mark/chap014/</guid>
      <description>1 Now the feast of the pasch and of the Azymes was after two days: and the chief priests and the scribes sought how they might by some wile lay hold on him and kill him.&#xA;2 But they said: Not on the festival day, lest there should be a tumult among the people.&#xA;3 And when he was in Bethania, in the house of Simon the leper, and was at meat, there came a woman having an alabaster box of ointment of precious spikenard.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 15</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/02-mark/chap015/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:35 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/02-mark/chap015/</guid>
      <description>1 And straightway in the morning, the chief priests holding a consultation with the ancients and the scribes and the whole council, binding Jesus, led him away and delivered him to Pilate.&#xA;2 And Pilate asked him: Art thou the king of the Jews? But he answering, saith to him: Thou sayest it.&#xA;3 And the chief priests accused him in many things.&#xA;4 And Pilate again asked him, saying: Answerest thou nothing?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 16</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/02-mark/chap016/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:35 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/02-mark/chap016/</guid>
      <description>1 And when the sabbath was past, Mary Magdalen and Mary the mother of James and Salome bought sweet spices, that coming, they might anoint Jesus.&#xA;2 And very early in the morning, the first day of the week, they come to the sepulchre, the sun being now risen.&#xA;3 And they said one to another: Who shall roll us back the stone from the door of the sepulchre?&#xA;4 And looking, they saw the stone rolled back.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 2</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/02-mark/chap002/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:35 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/02-mark/chap002/</guid>
      <description>1 And again he entered into Capharnaum after some days.&#xA;2 And it was heard that he was in the house. And many came together, so that there was no room: no, not even at the door. And he spoke to them the word.&#xA;3 And they came to him, bringing one sick of the palsy, who was carried by four.&#xA;4 And when they could not offer him unto him for the multitude, they uncovered the roof where he was: and opening it, they let down the bed wherein the man sick of the palsy lay.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 3</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/02-mark/chap003/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:35 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/02-mark/chap003/</guid>
      <description>1 And he entered again into the synagogue: and there was a man there who had a withered hand.&#xA;2 And they watched him whether he would heal on the sabbath days, that they might accuse him.&#xA;3 And he said to the man who had the withered hand: Stand up in the midst.&#xA;4 And he saith to them: Is it lawful to do good on the sabbath days, or to do evil?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 4</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/02-mark/chap004/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:35 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/02-mark/chap004/</guid>
      <description>1 And again he began to teach by the sea side; and a great multitude was gathered together unto him, so that he went up into a ship and sat in the sea: and all the multitude was upon the land by the sea side.&#xA;2 And he taught them many things in parables, and said unto them in his doctrine:&#xA;3 Hear ye: Behold, the sower went out to sow.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 5</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/02-mark/chap005/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:35 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/02-mark/chap005/</guid>
      <description>1 And they came over the strait of the sea, into the country of the Gerasens.&#xA;2 And as he went out of the ship, immediately there met him out of the monuments a man with an unclean spirit,&#xA;3 Who had his dwelling in the tombs, and no man now could bind him, not even with chains.&#xA;4 For having been often bound with fetters and chains, he had burst the chains, and broken the fetters in pieces, and no one could tame him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 6</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/02-mark/chap006/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:35 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/02-mark/chap006/</guid>
      <description>1 And going out from thence, he went into his own country; and his disciples followed him.&#xA;2 And when the Sabbath was come, he began to teach in the synagogue: and many hearing him were in admiration at his doctrine, saying: How came this man by all these things? and what wisdom is this that is given to him, and such mighty works as are wrought by his hands?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 7</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/02-mark/chap007/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:35 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/02-mark/chap007/</guid>
      <description>1 And there assembled together unto him the Pharisees and some of the scribes, coming from Jerusalem.&#xA;2 And when they had seen some of his disciples eat bread with common, that is, with unwashed hands, they found fault.&#xA;3 For the Pharisees and all the Jews eat not without often washing their hands, holding the tradition of the ancients.&#xA;4 And when they come from the market, unless they be washed, they eat not: and many other things there are that have been delivered to them to observe, the washings of cups and of pots and of brazen vessels and of beds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 8</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/02-mark/chap008/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:35 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/02-mark/chap008/</guid>
      <description>1 In those days again, when there was great multitude and they had nothing to eat; calling his disciples together, he saith to them:&#xA;2 I have compassion on the multitude, for behold they have now been with me three days and have nothing to eat.&#xA;3 And if I shall send them away fasting to their home, they will faint in the way: for some of them came from afar off.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 9</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/02-mark/chap009/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:35 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/02-mark/chap009/</guid>
      <description>1 And after six days, Jesus taketh with him Peter and James and John, and leadeth them up into an high mountain apart by themselves, and was transfigured before them.&#xA;2 And his garments became shining and exceeding white as snow, so as no fuller upon earth can make white.&#xA;3 And there appeared to them Elias with Moses: and they were talking with Jesus.&#xA;4 And Peter answering, said to Jesus: Rabbi, it is good for us to be here.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
