<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Wisdom on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</title>
    <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/52-wisdom/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Wisdom on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:31 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/52-wisdom/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 1</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/52-wisdom/chap001/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:31 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/52-wisdom/chap001/</guid>
      <description>1 Love justice, you that are the judges of the earth. Think of the Lord in goodness, and seek him in simplicity of heart:&#xA;2 For he is found by them that tempt him not: and he sheweth himself to them that have faith in him.&#xA;3 For perverse thoughts separate from God: and his power, when it is tried, reproveth the unwise:&#xA;4 For wisdom will not enter into a malicious soul, nor dwell in a body subject to sins.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 10</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/52-wisdom/chap010/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:31 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/52-wisdom/chap010/</guid>
      <description>1 She preserved him, that was first formed by God, the father of the world, when he was created alone,&#xA;2 And she brought him out of his sin, and gave him power to govern all things.&#xA;3 But when the unjust went away from her in his anger, he perished by the fury wherewith he murdered his brother.&#xA;4 For whose cause, when water destroyed the earth, wisdom healed it again, directing the course of the just by contemptible wood.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 11</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/52-wisdom/chap011/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:31 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/52-wisdom/chap011/</guid>
      <description>1 She prospered their works in the hands of the holy prophet.&#xA;2 They went through wildernesses that were not inhabited, and in desert places they pitched their tents.&#xA;3 They stood against their enemies, and revenged themselves of their adversaries.&#xA;4 They were thirsty, and they called upon thee, and water was given them out of the high rock, and a refreshment of their thirst out of the hard stone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 12</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/52-wisdom/chap012/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:31 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/52-wisdom/chap012/</guid>
      <description>1 O how good and sweet is thy Spirit, O Lord, in all things!&#xA;2 And therefore thou chastisest them that err, by little and little: and admonishest them, and speakest to them, concerning the things wherein they offend: that leaving their wickedness, they may believe in thee, O Lord.&#xA;3 For those ancient inhabitants of thy holy land, whom thou didst abhor,&#xA;4 Because they did works hateful to thee by their sorceries, and wicked sacrifices,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 13</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/52-wisdom/chap013/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:31 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/52-wisdom/chap013/</guid>
      <description>1 But all men are vain, in whom there is not the knowledge of God: and who by these good things that are seen, could not understand him that is, neither by attending to the works have acknowledged who was the workman:&#xA;2 But have imagined either the fire, or the wind, or the swift air, or the circle of the stars, or the great water, or the sun and moon, to be the gods that rule the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 14</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/52-wisdom/chap014/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:31 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/52-wisdom/chap014/</guid>
      <description>1 Again, another designing to sail, and beginning to make his voyage through the raging waves, calleth upon a piece of wood more frail than the wood that carrieth him.&#xA;2 For this the desire of gain devised, and the workman built it by his skill.&#xA;3 But thy providence, O Father, governeth it: for thou hast made a way even in the sea, and a most sure path among the waves,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 15</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/52-wisdom/chap015/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:31 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/52-wisdom/chap015/</guid>
      <description>1 But thou, our God, art gracious and true, patient, and ordering all things in mercy.&#xA;2 For if we sin, we are thine, knowing thy greatness: and if we sin not, we know that we are counted with thee.&#xA;3 For to know thee is perfect justice: and to know thy justice, and thy power, is the root of immortality.&#xA;4 For the invention of mischievous men hath not deceived us, nor the shadow of a picture, a fruitless labour, a graven figure with divers colours,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 16</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/52-wisdom/chap016/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:31 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/52-wisdom/chap016/</guid>
      <description>1 For these things, and by the like things to these, they were worthily punished, and were destroyed by a multitude of beasts.&#xA;2 Instead of which punishment, dealing well with thy people, thou gavest them their desire of delicious food, of a new taste, preparing for them quails for their meat:&#xA;3 To the end, that they indeed desiring food, by means of those things that were shewn and sent among them, might loath even that which was necessary to satisfy their desire.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 17</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/52-wisdom/chap017/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:31 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/52-wisdom/chap017/</guid>
      <description>1 For thy judgments, O Lord, are great, and thy words cannot be expressed: therefore undisciplined souls have erred.&#xA;2 For while the wicked thought to be able to have dominion over the holy nation, they themselves being fettered with the bonds of darkness, and a long night, shut up in their houses, lay there exiled from the eternal providence.&#xA;3 And while they thought to lie hid in their obscure sins, they were scattered under a dark veil of forgetfullness, being horribly afraid, and troubled with exceeding great astonishment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 18</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/52-wisdom/chap018/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:31 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/52-wisdom/chap018/</guid>
      <description>1 But thy saints had a very great light, and they heard their voice indeed, but did not see their shape. And because they also did not suffer the same things, they glorified thee:&#xA;2 And they that before had been wronged, gave thanks, because they were not hurt now: and asked this gift, that there might be a difference.&#xA;3 Therefore they received a burning pillar of fire for a guide of the way which they knew not, and thou gavest them a harmless sun of a good entertainment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 19</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/52-wisdom/chap019/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:31 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/52-wisdom/chap019/</guid>
      <description>1 But as to the wicked, even to the end there came upon them wrath without mercy. For he knew before also what they would do:&#xA;2 For when they had given them leave to depart and had sent them away with great care, they repented and pursued after them.&#xA;3 For whilst they were yet mourning, and lamenting at the graves of the dead, they took up another foolish device: and pursued them as fugitives whom they had pressed to be gone:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 2</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/52-wisdom/chap002/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:31 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/52-wisdom/chap002/</guid>
      <description>1 For they have said, reasoning with themselves, but not right: The time of our life is short and tedious, and in the end of a man there is no remedy, and no man hath been known to have returned from hell:&#xA;2 For we are born of nothing, and after this we shall be as if we had not been: for the breath in our nostrils is smoke: and speech a spark to move our heart,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 3</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/52-wisdom/chap003/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:31 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/52-wisdom/chap003/</guid>
      <description>1 But the souls of the just are in the hand of God, and the torment of death shall not touch them.&#xA;2 In the sight of the unwise they seemed to die: and their departure was taken for misery:&#xA;3 And their going away from us, for utter destruction: but they are in peace.&#xA;4 And though in the sight of men they suffered torments, their hope is full of immortality.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 4</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/52-wisdom/chap004/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:31 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/52-wisdom/chap004/</guid>
      <description>1 How beautiful is the chaste generation with glory: for the memory thereof is immortal: because it is known both with God and with men.&#xA;2 When it is present, they imitate it: and they desire it, when it hath withdrawn itself, and it triumpheth crowned for ever, winning the reward of undefiled conflicts.&#xA;3 But the multiplied brood of the wicked shall not thrive, and bastard slips shall not take deep root, nor any fast foundation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 5</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/52-wisdom/chap005/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:31 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/52-wisdom/chap005/</guid>
      <description>1 Then shall the just stand with great constancy against those that have afflicted them, and taken away their labours.&#xA;2 These seeing it, shall be troubled with terrible fear, and shall be amazed at the suddenness of their unexpected salvation,&#xA;3 Saying within themselves, repenting, and groaning for anguish of spirit: These are they, whom we had sometime in derision, and for a parable of reproach.&#xA;4 We fools esteemed their life madness, and their end without honour.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 6</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/52-wisdom/chap006/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:31 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/52-wisdom/chap006/</guid>
      <description>1 Wisdom is better than strength: and a wise man is better than a strong man.&#xA;2 Hear, therefore, ye kings, and understand, learn ye that are judges of the ends of the earth.&#xA;3 Give ear, you that rule the people, and that please yourselves in multitudes of nations:&#xA;4 For power is given you by the Lord, and strength by the most High, who will examine your works: and search out your thoughts:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 7</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/52-wisdom/chap007/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:31 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/52-wisdom/chap007/</guid>
      <description>1 I myself am a mortal man, like all others, and of the race of him, that was first made of the earth, and in the womb of my mother I was fashioned to be flesh.&#xA;2 In the time of ten months I was compacted in blood, of the seed of man, and the pleasure of sleep concurring.&#xA;3 And being born, I drew in the common air, and fell upon the earth, that is made alike, and the first voice which I uttered was crying, as all others do.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 8</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/52-wisdom/chap008/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:31 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/52-wisdom/chap008/</guid>
      <description>1 She reacheth, therefore, from end to end mightily, and ordereth all things sweetly.&#xA;2 Her have I loved, and have sought her out from my youth, and have desired to take for my spouse, and I became a lover of her beauty.&#xA;3 She glorifieth her nobility by being conversant with God: yea, and the Lord of all things hath loved her.&#xA;4 For it is she that teacheth the knowledge of God and is the chooser of his works.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 9</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/52-wisdom/chap009/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:31 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/52-wisdom/chap009/</guid>
      <description>1 God of my fathers, and Lord of mercy, who hast made all things with thy word,&#xA;2 And by thy wisdom hast appointed man, that he should have dominion over the creature that was made by thee,&#xA;3 That he should order the world according to equity and justice, and execute justice with an upright heart:&#xA;4 Give me wisdom, that sitteth by thy throne, and cast me not off from among thy children:</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
