<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hosea on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</title>
    <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/60-hosea/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Hosea on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/60-hosea/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 1</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/60-hosea/chap001/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/60-hosea/chap001/</guid>
      <description>1 The word of the Lord, that came to Hosea, the son of Beeri, in the days of Ozias, Joathan, Achaz, and Ezechias, kings of Juda, and in the days of Jeroboam, the son of Joas, king of Israel.&#xA;2 The beginning of the Lord&amp;rsquo;s speaking by Hosea: and the Lord said to Hosea: Go, take thee a wife of fornications, and have of her children of fornications: for the land by fornication shall depart from the Lord.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 10</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/60-hosea/chap010/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/60-hosea/chap010/</guid>
      <description>1 Israel a vine full of branches, the fruit is agreeable to it: according to the multitude of his fruit, he hath multiplied altars, according to the plenty of his land he hath abounded with idols.&#xA;2 Their heart is divided: now they shall perish: he shall break down their idols, he shall destroy their altars.&#xA;3 For now they shall say: We have no king: because we fear not the Lord: and what shall a king do to us?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 11</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/60-hosea/chap011/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/60-hosea/chap011/</guid>
      <description>1 As the morning passeth, so hath the king of Israel passed away. Because Israel was a child, and I loved him: and I called my son out of Egypt.&#xA;2 As they called them, they went away from before their face: they offered victims to Baalim, and sacrificed to idols.&#xA;3 And I was like a foster father to Ephraim, I carried them in my arms: and they knew not that I healed them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 12</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/60-hosea/chap012/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/60-hosea/chap012/</guid>
      <description>1 Ephraim feedeth on the wind, and followeth the burning heat: all the day long he multiplied lies and desolation: and he hath made a covenant with the Assyrians, and carried oil into Egypt.&#xA;2 Therefore there is a judgment of the Lord with Juda, and a visitation for Jacob: he will render to him according to his ways, and according to his devices.&#xA;3 In the womb he supplanted his brother: and by his strength he had success with an angel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 13</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/60-hosea/chap013/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/60-hosea/chap013/</guid>
      <description>1 When Ephraim spoke, a horror seized Israel: and he sinned in Baal, and died.&#xA;2 And now they have sinned more and more: and they have made to themselves a molten thing of their silver as the likeness of idols: the whole is the work of craftsmen: to these that say: Sacrifice men, ye that adore calves.&#xA;3 Therefore they shall be as a morning cloud, and as the early dew that passeth away, as the dust that is driven with a whirlwind out of the floor, and as the smoke out of the chimney.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 14</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/60-hosea/chap014/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/60-hosea/chap014/</guid>
      <description>1 Let Samaria perish, because she hath stirred up her God to bitterness: let them perish by the sword, let their little ones be dashed, and let the women with child be ripped up.&#xA;2 Return, O Israel, to the Lord thy God: for thou hast fallen down by thy iniquity.&#xA;3 Take with you words, and return to the Lord, and say to him: Take away all iniquity, and receive the good: and we will render the calves of our lips.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 2</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/60-hosea/chap002/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/60-hosea/chap002/</guid>
      <description>1 Say ye to your brethren: You are my people: and to your sister: Thou hast obtained mercy.&#xA;2 Judge your mother, judge her: because she is not my wife, and I am not her husband. Let her put away her fornications from her face, and her adulteries from between her breasts.&#xA;3 Lest I strip her naked, and set her as in the day that she was born: and I will make her as a wilderness, and will set her as a land that none can pass through and will kill her with drought.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 3</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/60-hosea/chap003/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/60-hosea/chap003/</guid>
      <description>1 And the Lord said to me: Go yet again, and love a woman beloved of her friend, and an adulteress: as the Lord loveth the children of Israel, and they look to strange gods, and love the husks of the grapes.&#xA;2 And I bought her to me for fifteen pieces of silver, and for a core of barley, and for half a core of barley.&#xA;3 And I said to her: Thou shalt wait for me many days: thou shalt not play the harlot, and thou shalt be no man&amp;rsquo;s, and I also will wait for thee.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 4</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/60-hosea/chap004/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/60-hosea/chap004/</guid>
      <description>1 Hear the word of the Lord, ye children of Israel, for the Lord shall enter into judgment with the inhabitants of the land: for there is no truth, and there is no mercy, and there is no knowledge of God in the land.&#xA;2 Cursing, and lying, and killing, and theft, and adultery, have overflowed, and blood hath touched blood.&#xA;3 Therefore shall the land mourn, and every one that dwelleth in it shall languish with the beasts of the field, and with the fowls of the air: yea, the fishes of the sea also shall be gathered together.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 5</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/60-hosea/chap005/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/60-hosea/chap005/</guid>
      <description>1 Hear ye this, O priests, and hearken, O ye house of Israel, and give ear, O house of the king: for there is a judgment against you, because you have been a snare to them whom you should have watched over and a net spread upon Thabor.&#xA;2 And you have turned aside victims into the depth and I am the teacher of them all.&#xA;3 I know Ephraim, and Israel is not hid from me for now Ephraim hath committed fornication, Israel is defiled.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 6</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/60-hosea/chap006/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/60-hosea/chap006/</guid>
      <description>1 In their affliction they will rise early to me: Come, and let us return to the Lord.&#xA;2 For he hath taken us, and he will heal us: he will strike, and he will cure us.&#xA;3 He will revive us after two days: on the third day he will raise us up, and we shall live in his sight. We shall know, and we shall follow on, that we may know the Lord.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 7</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/60-hosea/chap007/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/60-hosea/chap007/</guid>
      <description>1 When I would have healed Israel, the iniquity of Ephraim was discovered, and the wickedness of Samaria, for they have committed falsehood, and the thief is come in to steal, the robber is without.&#xA;2 And lest they may say in their hearts, that I remember all their wickedness: their own devices now have beset them about, they have been done before my face.&#xA;3 They have made the king glad with their wickedness: and the princes with their lies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 8</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/60-hosea/chap008/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/60-hosea/chap008/</guid>
      <description>1 Let there be a trumpet in thy throat like an eagle upon the house of the Lord: because they have transgressed my covenant, and have violated my law.&#xA;2 They shall call upon me: O my God, we, Israel, know thee.&#xA;3 Israel hath cast off the thing that is good, the enemy shall pursue him.&#xA;4 They have reigned, but not by me: they have been princes, and I knew not: of their silver and their gold they have made idols to themselves, that they might perish.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 9</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/60-hosea/chap009/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/60-hosea/chap009/</guid>
      <description>1 Rejoice not, O Israel: rejoice not as the nations do: for thou hast committed fornication against thy God, thou hast loved a reward upon every cornfloor.&#xA;2 The floor and the winepress shall not feed them, and the wine shall deceive them.&#xA;3 They shall not dwell in the Lord&amp;rsquo;s land: Ephraim is returned to Egypt, and hath eaten unclean things among the Assyrians.&#xA;4 They shall not offer wine to the Lord, neither shall they please him: their sacrifices shall be like the bread of mourners: all that shall eat it shall be defiled: for their bread is life for their soul, it shall not enter into the house of the Lord.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
