<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Habakkuk on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</title>
    <link>http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/67-habakkuk/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Habakkuk on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/67-habakkuk/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 1</title>
      <link>http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/67-habakkuk/chap001/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/67-habakkuk/chap001/</guid>
      <description>1 The burden that Habakkuk the prophet saw.&#xA;2 How long, O Lord, shall I cry, and thou wilt not hear? shall I cry out to thee suffering violence, and thou wilt not save?&#xA;3 Why hast thou shewn me iniquity and grievance, to see rapine and injustice before me? and there is a judgment, but opposition is more powerful.&#xA;4 Therefore the law is torn in pieces, and judgment cometh not to the end: because the wicked prevaileth against the just, therefore wrong judgment goeth forth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 2</title>
      <link>http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/67-habakkuk/chap002/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/67-habakkuk/chap002/</guid>
      <description>1 I will stand upon my watch, and fix my foot upon the tower: and I will watch, to see what will be said to me, and what I may answer to him that reproveth me.&#xA;2 And the Lord answered me, and said: Write the vision, and make it plain upon tables: that he that readeth it may run over it.&#xA;3 For as yet the vision is far off, and it shall appear at the end, and shall not lie: if it make any delay, wait for it: for it shall surely come, and it shall not be slack.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 3</title>
      <link>http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/67-habakkuk/chap003/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/67-habakkuk/chap003/</guid>
      <description>1 A PRAYER OF Habakkuk THE PROPHET FOR IGNORANCES.&#xA;2 O Lord, I have heard thy hearing, and was afraid. O Lord, thy work, in the midst of the years bring it to life: In the midst of the years thou shalt make it known: when thou art angry, thou wilt remember mercy.&#xA;3 God will come from the south, and the holy one from mount Pharan: His glory covered the heavens, and the earth is full of his praise.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
