<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Micah on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/65-micah/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Micah on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/65-micah/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 1</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/65-micah/chap001/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/65-micah/chap001/</guid>
      <description>1 The word of the Lord, that came to Micah, the Morasthite, in the days of Joathan, Achaz, and Ezechias, kings of Juda: which he saw concerning Samaria and Jerusalem.&#xA;2 Hear, all ye people: and let the earth give ear, and all that is therein: and let the Lord God be a witness to you, the Lord from his holy temple.&#xA;3 For behold the Lord will come forth out of his place: and he will come down, and will tread upon the high places of the earth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 2</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/65-micah/chap002/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/65-micah/chap002/</guid>
      <description>1 Woe to you that devise that which is unprofitable, and work evil in your beds: in the morning light they execute it, because their hand is against God.&#xA;2 And they have coveted fields, and taken them by violence, and houses they have forcibly taken away: and oppressed a man and his house, a man and his inheritance.&#xA;3 Therefore thus saith the Lord: Behold I devise an evil against this family: from which you shall not withdraw your necks, and you shall not walk haughtily, for this is a very evil time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 3</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/65-micah/chap003/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/65-micah/chap003/</guid>
      <description>1 And I said: Hear, O ye princes of Jacob, and ye chiefs of the house of Israel: Is it not your part to know judgment,&#xA;2 You that hate good, and love evil: that violently pluck off their skins from them and their flesh from their bones?&#xA;3 Who have eaten the flesh of my people, and have flayed their skin off them: and have broken, and chopped their bones as for the kettle, and as flesh in the midst of the pot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 4</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/65-micah/chap004/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/65-micah/chap004/</guid>
      <description>1 And it shall come to pass in the last days, that the mountain of the house of the Lord shall be prepared in the top of the mountains, and high above the hills: and people shall flow to it.&#xA;2 And many nations shall come in haste, and say: Come, let us go up to the mountain of the Lord, and to the house of the God of Jacob: and he will teach us of his ways, and we will walk in his paths: for the law shall go forth out of Sion, and the word of the Lord out of Jerusalem.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 5</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/65-micah/chap005/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/65-micah/chap005/</guid>
      <description>1 Now shalt thou be laid waste, O daughter of the robber: they have laid siege against us, with a rod shall they strike the cheek of the judge of Israel.&#xA;2 And thou Bethlehem Ephrata, art a little one among the thousands of Juda, out of thee shall he come forth unto me that is to be the ruler in Israel: and his going forth is from the beginning, from the days of eternity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 6</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/65-micah/chap006/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/65-micah/chap006/</guid>
      <description>1 Hear ye what the Lord saith: Arise, contend thou in judgment against the mountains, and let the hills hear thy voice.&#xA;2 Let the mountains hear the judgment of the Lord, and the strong foundations of the earth: for the Lord will enter into judgment with his people, and he will plead against Israel.&#xA;3 O my people, what have I done to thee, or in what have I molested thee?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 7</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/65-micah/chap007/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/65-micah/chap007/</guid>
      <description>1 Woe is me, for I am become as one that gleaneth in autumn the grapes of the vintage: there is no cluster to eat, my soul desired the first ripe figs.&#xA;2 The holy man is perished out of the earth, and there is none upright among men: they all lie in wait for blood, every one hunteth his brother to death.&#xA;3 The evil of their hands they call good: the prince requireth, and the judge is for giving: and the great man hath uttered the desire of his soul, and they have troubled it.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
