<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Galatians on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</title>
    <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/09-galatians/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Galatians on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:24 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/09-galatians/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 1</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/09-galatians/chap001/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:24 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/09-galatians/chap001/</guid>
      <description>1 Paul, an apostle, not of men, neither by man, but by Jesus Christ and God the Father, who raised him from the dead:&#xA;2 And all the brethren who are with me: to the churches of Galatia.&#xA;3 Grace be to you, and peace from God the Father and from our Lord Jesus Christ,&#xA;4 Who gave himself for our sins, that he might deliver us from this present wicked world, according to the will of God and our Father:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 2</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/09-galatians/chap002/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:24 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/09-galatians/chap002/</guid>
      <description>1 Then, after fourteen years, I went up again to Jerusalem with Barnabas, taking Titus also with me.&#xA;2 And I went up according to revelation and communicated to them the gospel which I preach among the Gentiles: but apart to them who seemed to be some thing: lest perhaps I should run or had run in vain.&#xA;3 But neither Titus, who was with me, being a Gentile, was compelled to be circumcised.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 3</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/09-galatians/chap003/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:24 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/09-galatians/chap003/</guid>
      <description>1 O senseless Galatians, who hath bewitched you that you should not obey the truth: before whose eyes Jesus Christ hath been set forth, crucified among you?&#xA;2 This only would I learn of you: Did you receive the Spirit by the works of the law or by the hearing of faith?&#xA;3 Are you so foolish that, whereas you began in the Spirit, you would now be made perfect by the flesh?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 4</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/09-galatians/chap004/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:24 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/09-galatians/chap004/</guid>
      <description>1 As long as the heir is a child, he differeth nothing from a servant, though he be lord of all,&#xA;2 But is under tutors and governors until the time appointed by the father.&#xA;3 So we also, when we were children, were serving under the elements of the world.&#xA;4 But when the fulness of the time was come, God sent his Son, made of a woman, made under the law:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 5</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/09-galatians/chap005/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:24 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/09-galatians/chap005/</guid>
      <description>1 Stand fast and be not held again under the yoke of bondage.&#xA;2 Behold, I Paul tell you, that if you be circumcised, Christ shall profit you nothing.&#xA;3 And I testify again to every man circumcising himself that he is a debtor to do the whole law.&#xA;4 You are made void of Christ, you who are justified in the law: you are fallen from grace.&#xA;5 For we in spirit, by faith, wait for the hope of justice.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 6</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/09-galatians/chap006/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:24 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/09-galatians/chap006/</guid>
      <description>1 Brethren, and if a man be overtaken in any fault, you, who are spiritual, instruct such a one in the spirit of meekness, considering thyself, lest thou also be tempted.&#xA;2 Bear ye one another&amp;rsquo;s burdens: and so you shall fulfil the law of Christ.&#xA;3 For if any man think himself to be some thing, whereas he is nothing, he deceiveth himself.&#xA;4 But let every one prove his own work: and so he shall have glory in himself only and not in another.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
