<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Zechariah on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</title>
    <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/70-zechariah/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Zechariah on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:34 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/70-zechariah/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 10</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/70-zechariah/chap010/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:34 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/70-zechariah/chap010/</guid>
      <description>1 Ask ye of the Lord rain in the latter season, and the Lord will make snows, and will give them showers of rain, to every one grass in the field.&#xA;2 For the idols have spoken what was unprofitable, and the diviners have seen a lie, and the dreamers have spoken vanity: they comforted in vain: therefore they were led away as a flock: they shall be afflicted, because they have no shepherd.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 11</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/70-zechariah/chap011/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:34 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/70-zechariah/chap011/</guid>
      <description>1 Open thy gates, O Libanus, and let fire devour thy cedars.&#xA;2 Howl, thou fir tree, for the cedar is fallen, for the mighty are laid waste: howl, ye oaks of Basan, because the fenced forest is cut down.&#xA;3 The voice of the howling of the shepherds, because their glory is laid waste: the voice of the roaring of the lions, because the pride of the Jordan is spoiled.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 12</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/70-zechariah/chap012/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:34 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/70-zechariah/chap012/</guid>
      <description>1 The burden of the word of the Lord upon Israel. Thus saith the Lord, who stretcheth forth the heavens, and layeth the foundations of the earth, and formeth the spirit of man in him:&#xA;2 Behold I will make Jerusalem a lintel of surfeiting to all the people round about: and Juda also shall be in the siege against Jerusalem.&#xA;3 And it shall come to pass in that day, that I will make Jerusalem a burdensome stone to all people: all that shall lift it up shall be rent and torn, and all the kingdoms of the earth shall be gathered together against her.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 13</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/70-zechariah/chap013/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:34 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/70-zechariah/chap013/</guid>
      <description>1 In that day there shall be a fountain open to the house of David, and to the inhabitants of Jerusalem: for the washing of the sinner, and of the unclean woman.&#xA;2 And it shall come to pass in that day, saith the Lord of hosts, that I will destroy the names of idols out of the earth, and they shall be remembered no more: and I will take away the false prophets, and the unclean spirit out of the earth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 14</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/70-zechariah/chap014/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:34 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/70-zechariah/chap014/</guid>
      <description>1 Behold the days of the Lord shall come, and thy spoils shall be divided in the midst of thee.&#xA;2 And I will gather all nations to Jerusalem to battle, and the city shall be taken, and the houses shall be rifled, and the women shall be defiled: and half of the city shall go forth into captivity, and the rest of the people shall not be taken away out of the city.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 1</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/70-zechariah/chap001/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/70-zechariah/chap001/</guid>
      <description>1 In the eighth month, in the second year of king Darius, the word of the Lord came to Zechariah the son of Barachias, the son of Addo, the prophet, saying:&#xA;2 The Lord hath been exceeding angry with your fathers.&#xA;3 And thou shalt say to them: Thus saith the Lord of hosts: Turn ye to me, saith the Lord of hosts: and I will turn to you, saith the Lord of hosts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 2</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/70-zechariah/chap002/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/70-zechariah/chap002/</guid>
      <description>1 And I lifted up my eyes, and saw, and behold a man, with a measuring line in his hand.&#xA;2 And I said: Whither goest thou? and he said to me: To measure Jerusalem, and to see how great is the breadth thereof, and how great the length thereof.&#xA;3 And behold the angel that spoke in me went forth, and another angel went out to meet him.&#xA;4 And he said to him: Run, speak to this young man, saying: Jerusalem shall be inhabited without walls, by reason of the multitude of men, and of the beasts in the midst thereof.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 3</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/70-zechariah/chap003/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/70-zechariah/chap003/</guid>
      <description>1 And the Lord shewed me Jesus the high priest standing before the angel of the Lord: and Satan stood on his right hand to be his adversary.&#xA;2 And the Lord said to Satan: The Lord rebuke thee, O Satan: and the Lord that chose Jerusalem rebuke thee: Is not this a brand plucked out of the fire?&#xA;3 And Jesus was clothed with filthy garments: and he stood before the face of the angel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 4</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/70-zechariah/chap004/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/70-zechariah/chap004/</guid>
      <description>1 And the angel that spoke in me came again: and he waked me, as a man that is wakened out of his sleep.&#xA;2 And he said to me: What seest thou? And I said: I have looked, and behold a candlestick all of gold, and its lamp upon the top of it: and the seven lights thereof upon it: and seven funnels for the lights that were upon the top thereof.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 5</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/70-zechariah/chap005/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/70-zechariah/chap005/</guid>
      <description>1 And I turned and lifted up my eyes: and I saw, and behold a volume flying.&#xA;2 And he said to me: What seest thou? And I said: I see a volume flying: the length thereof is twenty cubits, and the breadth thereof ten cubits.&#xA;3 And he said to me: This is the curse that goeth forth over the face of the earth: for every thief shall be judged as is there written: and every one that sweareth in like manner shall be judged by it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 6</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/70-zechariah/chap006/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/70-zechariah/chap006/</guid>
      <description>1 And I turned, and lifted up my eyes, and saw: and behold four chariots came out from the midst of two mountains: and the mountains were mountains of brass.&#xA;2 In the first chariot were red horses, and in the second chariot black horses.&#xA;3 And in the third chariot white horses, and in the fourth chariot grisled horses, and strong ones.&#xA;4 And I answered, and said to the angel that spoke in me: What are these, my lord?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 7</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/70-zechariah/chap007/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/70-zechariah/chap007/</guid>
      <description>1 And it came to pass in the fourth year of king Darius, that the word of the Lord came to Zechariah, in the fourth day of the ninth month, which is Casleu.&#xA;2 When Sarasar, and Rogommelech, and the men that were with him, sent to the house of God, to entreat the face of the Lord:&#xA;3 To speak to the priests of the house of the Lord of hosts, and to the prophets, saying: Must I weep in the fifth month, or must I sanctify myself as I have now done for many years?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 8</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/70-zechariah/chap008/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/70-zechariah/chap008/</guid>
      <description>1 And the word of the Lord of hosts came to me, saying:&#xA;2 Thus saith the Lord of hosts: I have been jealous for Sion with a great jealousy, and with a great indignation have I been jealous for her.&#xA;3 Thus saith the Lord of hosts: I am returned to Sion, and I will dwell in the midst of Jerusalem: and Jerusalem shall be called The city of truth, and the mountain of the Lord of hosts, The sanctified mountain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 9</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/70-zechariah/chap009/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/70-zechariah/chap009/</guid>
      <description>1 The burden of the word of the Lord in the land of Hadrach, and of Damascus the rest thereof: for the eye of man, and of all the tribes of Israel is the Lord&amp;rsquo;s.&#xA;2 Emath also in the borders thereof, and Tyre, and Sidon: for they have taken to themselves to be exceeding wise.&#xA;3 And Tyre hath built herself a strong hold, and heaped together silver as earth, and gold as the mire of the streets.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
