<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Leviticus on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/30-leviticus/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Leviticus on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/30-leviticus/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 1</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/30-leviticus/chap001/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/30-leviticus/chap001/</guid>
      <description>1 And the Lord called Moses, and spoke to him from the tabernacle of the testimony, saying:&#xA;2 Speak to the children of Israel, and thou shalt say to them: The man among you that shall offer to the Lord a sacrifice of the cattle, that is, offering victims of oxen and sheep:&#xA;3 If his offering be a holocaust, and of the herd, he shall offer a male without blemish, at the door of the testimony, to make the Lord favourable to him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 10</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/30-leviticus/chap010/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/30-leviticus/chap010/</guid>
      <description>1 And Nadab and Abiu, the sons of Aaron, taking their censers, put fire therein, and incense on it, offering before the Lord strange fire: which was not commanded them.&#xA;2 And fire coming out from the Lord destroyed them: and they died before the Lord.&#xA;3 And Moses said to Aaron: This is what the Lord hath spoken. I will be sanctified in them that approach to me: and I will be glorified in the sight of all the people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 11</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/30-leviticus/chap011/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/30-leviticus/chap011/</guid>
      <description>1 And the Lord spoke to Moses and Aaron, saying:&#xA;2 Say to the children of Israel: These are the animals which you are to eat of all the living things of the earth.&#xA;3 Whatsoever hath the hoof divided, and cheweth the cud among the beasts, you shall eat.&#xA;4 But whatsoever cheweth indeed the cud, and hath a hoof, but divideth it not, as the camel, and others: that you shall not eat, but shall reckon it among the unclean.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 12</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/30-leviticus/chap012/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/30-leviticus/chap012/</guid>
      <description>1 And the Lord spoke to Moses, saying:&#xA;2 Speak to the children of Israel, and thou shalt say to them: If a woman having received seed shall bear a man child, she shall be unclean seven days, according to the days of separation of her flowers.&#xA;3 And on the eighth day the infant shall be circumcised:&#xA;4 But she shall remain three and thirty days in the blood of her purification.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 13</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/30-leviticus/chap013/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/30-leviticus/chap013/</guid>
      <description>1 And the Lord spoke to Moses and Aaron, saying:&#xA;2 The man in whose skin or flesh shall arise a different colour or a blister, or as it were something shining, that is the stroke of the leprosy, shall be brought to Aaron the priest, or any or of his sons.&#xA;3 And if he see the leprosy in his skin, and the hair turned white and the place where the leprosy appears lower than the skin and the rest of the flesh: it is the stroke of the leprosy, and upon his judgment he shall be separated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 14</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/30-leviticus/chap014/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/30-leviticus/chap014/</guid>
      <description>1 And the Lord spoke to Moses, saying:&#xA;2 This is the rite of a leper, when he is to be cleansed. He shall be brought to the priest:&#xA;3 Who going out of the camp, when he shall find that the leprosy is cleansed,&#xA;4 Shall command him that is to be purified, to offer for himself two living sparrows, which it is lawful to eat, and cedar wood, and scarlet, and hyssop.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 15</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/30-leviticus/chap015/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/30-leviticus/chap015/</guid>
      <description>1 And the Lord spoke to Moses and Aaron, saying:&#xA;2 Speak to the children of Israel, and say to them: The man that hath an issue of seed, shall be unclean.&#xA;3 And then shall he be judged subject to this evil, when a filthy humour, at every moment, cleaveth to his flesh, and gathereth there.&#xA;4 Every bed on which he sleepeth, shall be unclean, and every place on which he sitteth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 16</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/30-leviticus/chap016/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/30-leviticus/chap016/</guid>
      <description>1 And the Lord spoke to Moses, after the death of the two sons of Aaron when they were slain upon their offering strange fire:&#xA;2 And he commanded him, saying: Speak to Aaron thy brother, that he enter not at all into the sanctuary, which is within the veil before the propitiatory, with which the ark is covered, lest he die, (for I will appear in a cloud over the oracle),</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 17</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/30-leviticus/chap017/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/30-leviticus/chap017/</guid>
      <description>1 And the Lord spoke to Moses, saying:&#xA;2 Speak to Aaron and his sons, and to all the children of Israel, saying to them: This is the word, which the Lord hath commanded, saying:&#xA;3 Any man whosoever of the house of Israel, if he kill an ox, or a sheep, or a goat in the camp, or without the camp,&#xA;4 And offer it not at the door of the tabernacle an oblation to the Lord, shall be guilty of blood.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 18</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/30-leviticus/chap018/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/30-leviticus/chap018/</guid>
      <description>1 And the Lord spoke to Moses, saying:&#xA;2 Speak to the children of Israel, and thou shalt say to them: I am the Lord your God.&#xA;3 You shall not do according to the custom of the land of Egypt, in which you dwelt: neither shall you act according to the manner of the country of Chanaan, into which I will bring you. Nor shall you walk in their ordinances.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 19</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/30-leviticus/chap019/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/30-leviticus/chap019/</guid>
      <description>1 The Lord spoke to Moses, saying:&#xA;2 Speak to all the congregation of the children of Israel. And thou shalt say to them: Be ye holy, because I the Lord your God am holy.&#xA;3 Let every one fear his father, and his mother. Keep my sabbaths. I am the Lord your God.&#xA;4 Turn ye not to idols: nor make to yourselves molten gods. I am the Lord your God.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 2</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/30-leviticus/chap002/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/30-leviticus/chap002/</guid>
      <description>1 When any one shall offer an oblation of sacrifice to the Lord, his offering shall be of fine flour: and he shall pour oil upon it, and put frankincense,&#xA;2 And shall bring it to the sons of Aaron the priests. And one of them shall take a handful of the flour and oil, and all the frankincense; and shall put it a memorial upon the altar for a most sweet savour to the Lord.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 20</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/30-leviticus/chap020/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/30-leviticus/chap020/</guid>
      <description>1 And the Lord spoke to Moses, saying:&#xA;2 Thus shalt thou say to the children of Israel: If any man of the children Israel, or of the strangers that dwell in Israel, give of his seed to the idol Moloch, dying let him die. The people of the land shall stone him.&#xA;3 And I will set my face against him: and I will cut him off from the midst of his people, because he hath given of his seed to Moloch, and hath defiled my sanctuary, and profaned my holy name.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 21</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/30-leviticus/chap021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/30-leviticus/chap021/</guid>
      <description>1 The Lord said also to Moses: Speak to the priests the sons of Aaron, and thou shalt say for them: Let not a priest incur an uncleanness at the death of his citizens.&#xA;2 But only for his kin, such as are near in blood: that is to say, for his father and for his mother, and for his son, and for his daughter, for his brother also:&#xA;3 And for a maiden sister, who hath had no husband.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 22</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/30-leviticus/chap022/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/30-leviticus/chap022/</guid>
      <description>1 And the Lord spoke to Moses saying:&#xA;2 Speak to Aaron and to his sons, that they beware of those things that are consecrated of the children of Israel: and defile not the name of the things sanctified to me, which they offer. I am the Lord.&#xA;3 Say to them and to their posterity: Every man of your race, that approacheth to those things that are consecrated, and which the children of Israel have offered to the Lord, in whom there is uncleanness, shall perish before the Lord.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 23</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/30-leviticus/chap023/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/30-leviticus/chap023/</guid>
      <description>1 And the Lord spoke to Moses, saying:&#xA;2 Speak to the children of Israel, and thou shalt say to them: These are the feasts of the Lord, which you shall call holy.&#xA;3 Six days shall ye do work: the seventh day, because it is the rest of the sabbath, shall be called holy. You shall do no work on that day: it is the sabbath of the Lord in all your habitations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 24</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/30-leviticus/chap024/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/30-leviticus/chap024/</guid>
      <description>1 And the Lord spoke to Moses, saying:&#xA;2 Command the children of Israel, that they bring unto thee the finest and clearest oil of olives, to furnish the lamps continually,&#xA;3 Without the veil of the testimony in the tabernacle of the covenant. And Aaron shall set them from evening until morning before the Lord, by a perpetual service and rite in your generations.&#xA;4 They shall be set upon the most pure candlestick before the Lord continually.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 25</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/30-leviticus/chap025/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/30-leviticus/chap025/</guid>
      <description>1 And the Lord spoke to Moses in mount Sinai, saying:&#xA;2 Speak to the children of Israel, and thou shalt say to them: When you shall have entered into the land which I will give you, observe the rest of the sabbath of the Lord.&#xA;3 Six years thou shalt sow thy field and six years thou shalt prune thy vineyard, and shalt gather the fruits thereof.&#xA;4 But in the seventh year there shall be a sabbath to the land, of the resting of the Lord.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 26</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/30-leviticus/chap026/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/30-leviticus/chap026/</guid>
      <description>1 I am the Lord your God. You shall not make to yourselves any idol or graven thing: neither shall you erect pillars, nor set up a remarkable stone in your land, to adore it. For I am the Lord your God.&#xA;2 Keep my sabbaths, and reverence my sanctuary. I am the Lord.&#xA;3 If you walk in my precepts, and keep my commandments, and do them, I will give you rain in due seasons.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 27</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/30-leviticus/chap027/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/30-leviticus/chap027/</guid>
      <description>1 And the Lord spoke to Moses, saying:&#xA;2 Speak to the children of Israel, and thou shalt say to them: The man that shall have made a vow, and promised his soul to God, shall give the price according to estimation.&#xA;3 If it be a man from twenty years old unto sixty years old, he shall give fifty sicles of silver, after the weight of the sanctuary:&#xA;4 If a woman, thirty.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 3</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/30-leviticus/chap003/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/30-leviticus/chap003/</guid>
      <description>1 And if his oblation be a sacrifice of peace offerings, and he will offer of the herd, whether male or female: he shall offer them without blemish before the Lord.&#xA;2 And he shall lay his hand upon the head of his victim, which shall be slain in the entry of the tabernacle of the testimony: and the sons of Aaron the priests shall pour the blood round about upon the altar.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 4</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/30-leviticus/chap004/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/30-leviticus/chap004/</guid>
      <description>1 And the Lord spoke to Moses, saying:&#xA;2 Say to the children of Israel: The soul that sinneth through ignorance, and doth any thing concerning any of the commandments of the Lord, which he commanded not to be done:&#xA;3 If the priest that is anointed shall sin, making the people to offend, he shall offer to the Lord for his sin a calf without blemish.&#xA;4 And he shall bring it to the door of the testimony before the Lord: and shall put his hand upon the head thereof, and shall sacrifice it to the Lord.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 5</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/30-leviticus/chap005/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/30-leviticus/chap005/</guid>
      <description>1 If any one sin, and hear the voice of one swearing, and is a witness either because he himself hath seen, or is privy to it: if he do not utter it, he shall bear his iniquity.&#xA;2 Whosoever toucheth any unclean thing, either that which hath been killed by a beast, or died of itself, or any other creeping thing: and forgetteth his uncleanness, he is guilty, and hath offended.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 6</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/30-leviticus/chap006/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/30-leviticus/chap006/</guid>
      <description>1 The Lord spoke to Moses, saying:&#xA;2 Whosoever shall sin, and despising the Lord, shall deny to his neighbour the thing delivered to his keeping, which was committed to his trust; or shall by force extort any thing, or commit oppression;&#xA;3 Or shall find a thing lost, and denying it, shall also swear falsely, or shall do any other of the many things, wherein men are wont to sin:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 7</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/30-leviticus/chap007/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/30-leviticus/chap007/</guid>
      <description>1 This also is the law of the sacrifice for a trespass: it is most holy.&#xA;2 Therefore where the holocaust is immolated, the victim also for a trespass shall be slain: the blood thereof shall be poured round about the altar.&#xA;3 They shall offer thereof the rump and the fat that covereth the entrails:&#xA;4 The two little kidneys, and the fat which is by the flanks, and the caul of the liver with the little kidneys.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 8</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/30-leviticus/chap008/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/30-leviticus/chap008/</guid>
      <description>1 And the Lord spoke to Moses, saying:&#xA;2 Take Aaron with his sons, their vestments, and the oil of unction: a calf for sin, two rams, a basket with unleavened bread.&#xA;3 And thou shalt gather together all the congregation to the door of the tabernacle.&#xA;4 And Moses did as the Lord had commanded. And all the multitude being gathered together before the door of the tabernacle:&#xA;5 He said: This is the word that the Lord hath commanded to be done.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 9</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/30-leviticus/chap009/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/30-leviticus/chap009/</guid>
      <description>1 And when the eighth day was come, Moses called Aaron and his sons, and the ancients of Israel, and said to Aaron:&#xA;2 Take of the herd a calf for sin, and a ram for a holocaust, both without blemish, and offer them before the Lord.&#xA;3 And to the children of Israel thou shalt say: Take ye a he goat for sin, and a calf, and a lamb, both of a year old, and without blemish for a holocaust.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
