<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>James on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/20-james/</link>
    <description>Recent content in James on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:36 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/20-james/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 1</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/20-james/chap001/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:36 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/20-james/chap001/</guid>
      <description>1 James, the servant of God and of our Lord Jesus Christ, to the twelve tribes which are scattered abroad, greeting.&#xA;2 My brethren, count it all joy, when you shall fall into divers temptations:&#xA;3 Knowing that the trying of your faith worketh patience&#xA;4 And patience hath a perfect work: that you may be perfect and entire, failing in nothing.&#xA;5 But if any of you want wisdom, let him ask of God who giveth to all men abundantly and upbraideth not.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 2</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/20-james/chap002/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:36 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/20-james/chap002/</guid>
      <description>1 My brethren, have not the faith of our Lord Jesus Christ of glory, with respect of persons.&#xA;2 For if there shall come into your assembly a man having a golden ring, in fine apparel; and there shall come in also a poor man in mean attire:&#xA;3 And you have respect to him that is clothed with the fine apparel and shall say to him: Sit thou here well: but say to the poor man: Stand thou there, or: Sit under my footstool:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 3</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/20-james/chap003/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:36 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/20-james/chap003/</guid>
      <description>1 Be ye not many masters, my brethren, knowing that you receive the greater judgment.&#xA;2 For in many things we all offend. If any man offend not in word, the same is a perfect man. He is able also with a bridle to lead about the whole body.&#xA;3 For if we put bits into the mouths of horses, that they may obey us: and we turn about their whole body.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 4</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/20-james/chap004/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:36 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/20-james/chap004/</guid>
      <description>1 From whence are wars and contentions among you? Are they not hence, from your concupiscences, which war in your members?&#xA;2 You covet, and have not: you kill and envy and cannot obtain. You contend and war, and you have not: because you ask not.&#xA;3 You ask and receive not: because you ask amiss, that you may consume it on your concupiscences.&#xA;4 Adulterers, know you not that the friendship of this world is the enemy of God?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 5</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/20-james/chap005/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:36 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/20-james/chap005/</guid>
      <description>1 Go to now, ye rich men: weep and howl in your miseries, which shall come upon you.&#xA;2 Your riches are corrupted: and your garments are motheaten.&#xA;3 Your gold and silver is cankered: and the rust of them shall be for a testimony against you and shall eat your flesh like fire. You have stored up to yourselves wrath against the last days.&#xA;4 Behold the hire of the labourers who have reaped down your fields, which by fraud has been kept back by you, crieth: and the cry of them hath entered into the ears of the Lord of Sabaoth.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
