<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Song on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</title>
    <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/51-song/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Song on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:31 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/51-song/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 1</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/51-song/chap001/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:31 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/51-song/chap001/</guid>
      <description>1 Let him kiss me with the kiss of his mouth: for thy breasts are better than wine,&#xA;2 Smelling sweet of the best ointments. Thy name is as oil poured out: therefore young maidens have loved thee.&#xA;3 Draw me: we will run after thee to the odour of thy ointments. The king hath brought me into his storerooms: we will be glad and rejoice in thee, remembering thy breasts more than wine: the rightous love thee.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 2</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/51-song/chap002/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:31 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/51-song/chap002/</guid>
      <description>1 I am the flower of the field, and the lily of the valleys.&#xA;2 As the lily among thorns, so is my love among the daughters.&#xA;3 As the apple tree among the trees of the woods, so is my beloved among the sons. I sat down under his shadow, whom I desired: and his fruit was sweet to my palate.&#xA;4 He brought me into the cellar of wine, he set in order charity in me.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 3</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/51-song/chap003/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:31 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/51-song/chap003/</guid>
      <description>1 In my bed by night I sought him whom my soul loveth: I sought him, and found him not.&#xA;2 I will rise, and will go about the city: in the streets and the broad ways I will seek him whom my soul loveth: I sought him, and I found him not.&#xA;3 The watchmen who keep the city, found me: Have you seen him, whom my soul loveth?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 4</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/51-song/chap004/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:31 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/51-song/chap004/</guid>
      <description>1 How beautiful art thou, my love, how beautiful art thou! thy eyes are doves&amp;rsquo; eyes, besides what is hid within. Thy hair is as flocks of goats, which come up from mount Galaad.&#xA;2 Thy teeth as flocks of sheep, that are shorn, which come up from the washing, all with twins, and there is none barren among them.&#xA;3 Thy lips are as a scarlet lace: and thy speech sweet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 5</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/51-song/chap005/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:31 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/51-song/chap005/</guid>
      <description>1 Let my beloved come into his garden, and eat the fruit of his apple trees. I am come into my garden, O my sister, my spouse, I have gathered my myrrh, with my aromatical spices: I have eaten the honeycomb with my honey, I have drunk my wine with my milk: eat, O friends, and drink, and be inebriated, my dearly beloved.&#xA;2 I sleep, and my heart watcheth: the voice of my beloved knocking: Open to me, my sister, my love, my dove, my undefiled: for my head is full of dew, and my locks of the drops of the nights.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 6</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/51-song/chap006/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:31 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/51-song/chap006/</guid>
      <description>1 My beloved is gone down into his garden, to the bed of aromatical spices, to feed in the gardens, and to gather lilies.&#xA;2 I to my beloved, and my beloved to me, who feedeth among the lilies.&#xA;3 Thou art beautiful, O my love, sweet and comely as Jerusalem terrible as an army set in array.&#xA;4 Turn away thy eyes from me, for they have made me flee away.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 7</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/51-song/chap007/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:31 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/51-song/chap007/</guid>
      <description>1 What shalt thou see in the Sulamitess but the companies of camps? How beautiful are thy steps in shoes, O prince&amp;rsquo;s daughter! The joints of thy thighs are like jewels, that are made by the hand of a skilful workman.&#xA;2 Thy navel is like a round bowl never wanting cups. Thy belly is like a heap of wheat, set about with lilies.&#xA;3 Thy two breasts are like two young roes that are twins.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 8</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/51-song/chap008/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:31 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/51-song/chap008/</guid>
      <description>1 Who shall give thee to me for my brother, sucking the breasts of my mother, that I may find thee without, and kiss thee, and now no man may despise me?&#xA;2 I will take hold of thee, and bring thee into my mother&amp;rsquo;s house: there thou shalt teach me, and I will give thee a cup of spiced wine and new wine of my pomegranates.&#xA;3 His left hand under my head, and his right hand shall embrace me.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
