<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Romans on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</title>
    <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/06-romans/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Romans on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:24 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/06-romans/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 1</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/06-romans/chap001/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:24 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/06-romans/chap001/</guid>
      <description>1 Paul, a servant of Jesus Christ, called to be an apostle, separated unto the gospel of God.&#xA;2 Which he had promised before, by his prophets, in the holy scriptures,&#xA;3 Concerning his Son, who was made to him of the seed of David, according to the flesh,&#xA;4 Who was predestinated the Son of God in power, according to the spirit of sanctification, by the resurrection of our Lord Jesus Christ from the dead:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 10</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/06-romans/chap010/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:24 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/06-romans/chap010/</guid>
      <description>1 Brethren, the will of my heart, indeed and my prayer to God is for them unto salvation.&#xA;2 For I bear them witness that they have a zeal of God, but not according to knowledge.&#xA;3 For they, not knowing the justice of God and seeking to establish their own, have not submitted themselves to the justice of God.&#xA;4 For the end of the law is Christ: unto justice to everyone that believeth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 11</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/06-romans/chap011/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:24 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/06-romans/chap011/</guid>
      <description>1 I say then: Hath God cast away his people? God forbid! For I also am an Israelite of the seed of Abraham, of the tribe of Benjamin.&#xA;2 God hath not cast away his people which he foreknew. Know you not what the scripture saith of Elias, how he calleth on God against Israel?&#xA;3 Lord, they have slain thy prophets, they have dug down thy altars. And I am left alone: and they seek my life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 12</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/06-romans/chap012/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:24 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/06-romans/chap012/</guid>
      <description>1 I beseech you therefore, brethren, by the mercy of God, that you present your bodies a living sacrifice, holy, pleasing unto God, your reasonable service.&#xA;2 And be not conformed to this world: but be reformed in the newness of your mind, that you may prove what is the good and the acceptable and the perfect will of God.&#xA;3 For I say, by the grace that is given me, to all that are among you, not to be more wise than it behoveth to be wise, but to be wise unto sobriety and according as God hath divided to every one the measure of faith.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 13</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/06-romans/chap013/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:24 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/06-romans/chap013/</guid>
      <description>1 Let every soul be subject to higher powers. For there is no power but from God: and those that are ordained of God.&#xA;2 Therefore, he that resisteth the power resisteth the ordinance of God. And they that resist purchase to themselves damnation.&#xA;3 For princes are not a terror to the good work, but to the evil. Wilt thou then not be afraid of the power? Do that which is good: and thou shalt have praise from the same.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 14</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/06-romans/chap014/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:24 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/06-romans/chap014/</guid>
      <description>1 Now him that is weak in faith, take unto you: not in disputes about thoughts.&#xA;2 For one believeth that he may eat all things: but he that is weak, let him eat herbs.&#xA;3 Let not him that eateth despise him that eateth not: and he that eateth not, let him not judge him that eateth. For God hath taken him to him.&#xA;4 Who art thou that judgest another man&amp;rsquo;s servant?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 15</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/06-romans/chap015/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:24 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/06-romans/chap015/</guid>
      <description>1 Now, we that are stronger ought to bear the infirmities of the weak and not to please ourselves.&#xA;2 Let every one of you Please his neighbour unto good, to edification.&#xA;3 For Christ did not please himself: but, as it is written: The reproaches of them that reproached thee fell upon me.&#xA;4 For what things soever were written were written for our learning: that, through patience and the comfort of the scriptures, we might have hope.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 16</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/06-romans/chap016/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:24 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/06-romans/chap016/</guid>
      <description>1 And I commend to you Phebe, our sister, who is in the ministry of the church, that is in Cenchrae:&#xA;2 That you receive her in the Lord as becometh saints and that you assist her in whatsoever business she shall have need of you. For she also hath assisted many, and myself also.&#xA;3 Salute Prisca and Aquila, my helpers, in Christ Jesus&#xA;4 (Who have for my life laid down their own necks: to whom not I only give thanks, but also all the churches of the Gentiles),</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 2</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/06-romans/chap002/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:24 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/06-romans/chap002/</guid>
      <description>1 Wherefore thou art inexcusable, O man, whosoever thou art that judgest. For wherein thou judgest another, thou condemnest thyself. For thou dost the same things which thou judgest.&#xA;2 For we know that the judgment of God is, according to truth, against them that do such things.&#xA;3 And thinkest thou this, O man, that judgest them who do such things and dost the same, that thou shalt escape the judgment of God?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 3</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/06-romans/chap003/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:24 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/06-romans/chap003/</guid>
      <description>1 What advantage then hath the Jew: or what is the profit of circumcision?&#xA;2 Much every way. First indeed, because the words of God were committed to them.&#xA;3 For what if some of them have not believed? Shall their unbelief make the faith of God without effect? God forbid!&#xA;4 But God is true and every man a liar, as it is written: That thou mayest be justified in thy words and mayest overcome when thou art judged.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 4</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/06-romans/chap004/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:24 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/06-romans/chap004/</guid>
      <description>1 What shall we say then that Abraham hath found, who is our father according to the flesh?&#xA;2 For if Abraham were justified by works, he hath whereof to glory, but not before God.&#xA;3 For what saith the scripture? Abraham believed God: and it was reputed to him unto justice.&#xA;4 Now to him that worketh, the reward is not reckoned according to grace but according to debt.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 5</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/06-romans/chap005/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:24 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/06-romans/chap005/</guid>
      <description>1 Being justified therefore by faith, let us have peace with God, through our Lord Jesus Christ:&#xA;2 By whom also we have access through faith into this grace wherein we stand: and glory in the hope of the glory of the sons of God.&#xA;3 And not only so: but we glory also in tribulation, knowing that tribulation worketh patience;&#xA;4 And patience trial; and trial hope;&#xA;5 And hope confoundeth not: because the charity of God is poured forth in our hearts, by the Holy Ghost who is given to us.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 6</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/06-romans/chap006/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:24 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/06-romans/chap006/</guid>
      <description>1 What shall we say, then? Shall we continue in sin, that grace may abound?&#xA;2 God forbid! For we that are dead to sin, how shall we live any longer therein?&#xA;3 Know you not that all we who are baptized in Christ Jesus are baptized in his death?&#xA;4 For we are buried together with him by baptism into death: that, as Christ is risen from the dead by the glory of the Father, so we also may walk in newness of life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 7</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/06-romans/chap007/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:24 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/06-romans/chap007/</guid>
      <description>1 Know you not, brethren (for I speak to them that know the law) that the law hath dominion over a man as long as it liveth?&#xA;2 For the woman that hath an husband, whilst her husband liveth is bound to the law. But if her husband be dead, she is loosed from the law of her husband.&#xA;3 Therefore, whilst her husband liveth, she shall be called an adulteress, if she be with another man: but if her husband be dead, she is delivered from the law of her husband: so that she is not an adulteress, if she be with another man.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 8</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/06-romans/chap008/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:24 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/06-romans/chap008/</guid>
      <description>1 There is now therefore no condemnation to them that are in Christ Jesus, who walk not according to the flesh.&#xA;2 For the law of the spirit of life, in Christ Jesus, hath delivered me from the law of sin and of death.&#xA;3 For what the law could not do, in that it was weak through the flesh, God, sending his own Son in the likeness of sinful flesh and of sin, hath condemned sin in the flesh.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 9</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/06-romans/chap009/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:24 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/06-romans/chap009/</guid>
      <description>1 I speak the truth in Christ: I lie not, my conscience bearing me witness in the Holy Ghost:&#xA;2 That I have great sadness and continual sorrow in my heart.&#xA;3 For I wished myself to be an anathema from Christ, for my brethren: who are my kinsmen according to the flesh:&#xA;4 Who are Israelites: to whom belongeth the adoption as of children and the glory and the testament and the giving of the law and the service of God and the promises:</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
