<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Job on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/47-job/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Job on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/47-job/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 1</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/47-job/chap001/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/47-job/chap001/</guid>
      <description>1 There was a man in the land of Hus, whose name was Job, and that man was simple and upright, and fearing God, and avoiding evil.&#xA;2 And there were born to him seven sons and three daughters.&#xA;3 And his possession was seven thousand sheep, and three thousand camels, and five hundred yoke of oxen, and five hundred she asses, and a family exceedingly great: and this man was great among all the people of the east.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 10</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/47-job/chap010/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/47-job/chap010/</guid>
      <description>1 My soul is weary of my life, I will let go my speech against myself, I will speak in the bitterness of my soul.&#xA;2 I will say to God: Do not condemn me: tell me why thou judgest me so?&#xA;3 Doth it seem good to thee that thou shouldst calumniate me, and oppress me, the work of thy own hands, and help the counsel of the wicked?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 11</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/47-job/chap011/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/47-job/chap011/</guid>
      <description>1 Then Sophar the Naamathite answered, and said:&#xA;2 Shall not he that speaketh much, hear also? or shall a man full of talk be justified?&#xA;3 Shall men hold their peace to thee only? and when thou hast mocked others, shall no man confute thee?&#xA;4 For thou hast said: My word is pure, and I am clean in thy sight.&#xA;5 And I wish that God would speak with thee, and would open his lips to thee,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 12</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/47-job/chap012/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/47-job/chap012/</guid>
      <description>1 Then Job answered, and said:&#xA;2 Are you then men alone, and shall wisdom die with you?&#xA;3 I also have a heart as well as you: for who is ignorant of these things, which you know?&#xA;4 He that is mocked by his friends as I, shall call upon God and he will hear him: for the simplicity of the just man is laughed to scorn.&#xA;5 The lamp despised in the thoughts of the rich, is ready for the time appointed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 13</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/47-job/chap013/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/47-job/chap013/</guid>
      <description>1 Behold my eye hath seen all these things, and my ear hath heard them, and I have understood them all.&#xA;2 According to your knowledge I also know: neither am I inferior to you.&#xA;3 But yet I will speak to the Almighty, and I desire to reason with God.&#xA;4 Having first shewn that you are forgers of lies, and maintainers of perverse opinions.&#xA;5 And I wish you would hold your peace, that you might be thought to be wise men.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 14</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/47-job/chap014/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/47-job/chap014/</guid>
      <description>1 Man born of a woman, living for a short time, is filled with many miseries.&#xA;2 Who cometh forth like a flower, and is destroyed, and fleeth as a shadow, and never continueth in the same state.&#xA;3 And dost thou think it meet to open thy eyes upon such an one, and to bring him into judgment with thee?&#xA;4 Who can make him clean that is conceived of unclean seed?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 15</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/47-job/chap015/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/47-job/chap015/</guid>
      <description>1 And Eliphaz the Themanite, answered, and said:&#xA;2 Will a wise man answer as if he were speaking in the wind, and fill his stomach with burning heat?&#xA;3 Thou reprovest him by words, who is not equal to thee, and thou speakest that which is not good for thee.&#xA;4 As much as is in thee, thou hast made void fear, and hast taken away prayers from before God.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 16</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/47-job/chap016/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/47-job/chap016/</guid>
      <description>1 Then Job answered, and said:&#xA;2 I have often heard such things as these: you are all troublesome comforters.&#xA;3 Shall windy words have no end? or is it any trouble to thee to speak?&#xA;4 I also could speak like you: and would God your soul were for my soul.&#xA;5 I would comfort you also with words, and would wag my head over you.&#xA;6 I would strengthen you with my mouth, and would move my lips, as sparing you.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 17</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/47-job/chap017/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/47-job/chap017/</guid>
      <description>1 My spirit shall be wasted, my days shall be shortened and only the grave remaineth for me.&#xA;2 I have not sinned, and my eye abideth in bitterness.&#xA;3 Deliver me, O Lord, and set me beside thee, and let any man&amp;rsquo;s hand fight against me.&#xA;4 Thou hast set their heart far from understanding, therefore they shall not be exalted.&#xA;5 He promiseth a prey to his companions, and the eyes of his children shall fail.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 18</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/47-job/chap018/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/47-job/chap018/</guid>
      <description>1 Then Baldad the Suhite answered, and said:&#xA;2 How long will you throw out words? understand first, and so let us speak.&#xA;3 Why are we reputed as beasts, and counted vile before you?&#xA;4 Thou that destroyest thy soul in thy fury, shall the earth be forsaken for thee, and shall rocks be removed out of their place?&#xA;5 Shall not the light of the wicked be extinguished, and the flame of his fire not shine?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 19</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/47-job/chap019/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/47-job/chap019/</guid>
      <description>1 Then Job answered, and said:&#xA;2 How long do you afflict my soul, and break me in pieces with words?&#xA;3 Behold, these ten times you confound me, and are not ashamed to oppress me.&#xA;4 For if I have been ignorant, my ignorance shall be with me.&#xA;5 But you set yourselves up against me, and reprove me with my reproaches.&#xA;6 At least now understand, that God hath not afflicted me with an equal judgment, and compassed me with his scourges.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 2</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/47-job/chap002/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/47-job/chap002/</guid>
      <description>1 And it came to pass, when on a certain day the sons of God came, and stood before the Lord, and Satan came amongst them, and stood in his sight,&#xA;2 That the Lord said to Satan: Whence comest thou? And he answered, and said: I have gone round about the earth, and walked through it.&#xA;3 And the Lord said to Satan: Hast thou considered my servant, Job, that there is none like him in the earth, a man simple and upright, and fearing God, and avoiding evil, and still keeping his innocence?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 20</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/47-job/chap020/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/47-job/chap020/</guid>
      <description>1 Then Sophar the Naamathite answered, and said:&#xA;2 Therefore various thoughts succeed one another in me, and my mind is hurried away to different things.&#xA;3 The doctrine with which thou reprovest me, I will hear, and the spirit of my understanding shall answer for me.&#xA;4 This I know from the beginning, since man was placed upon the earth,&#xA;5 That the praise of the wicked is short, and the joy of the hypocrite but for a moment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 21</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/47-job/chap021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/47-job/chap021/</guid>
      <description>1 Then Job answered, and said:&#xA;2 Hear, I beseech you, my words, and do penance.&#xA;3 Suffer me, and I will speak, and after, if you please, laugh at my words.&#xA;4 Is my debate against man, that I should not have just reason to be troubled?&#xA;5 Hearken to me and be astonished, and lay your finger on your mouth.&#xA;6 As for me, when I remember, I am afraid, and trembling taketh hold on my flesh.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 22</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/47-job/chap022/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/47-job/chap022/</guid>
      <description>1 Then Eliphaz the Themanite answered, and said:&#xA;2 Can man be compared with God, even though he were of perfect knowledge?&#xA;3 What doth it profit God if thou be just? or what dost thou give him if thy way be unspotted?&#xA;4 Shall he reprove thee for fear, and come with thee into judgment:&#xA;5 And not for thy manifold wickedness and thy infinite iniquities?&#xA;6 For thou hast taken away the pledge of thy brethren without cause, and stripped them naked of their clothing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 23</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/47-job/chap023/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/47-job/chap023/</guid>
      <description>1 Then Job answered, and said:&#xA;2 Now also my words are in bitterness, and the hand of my scourge is more grievous than my mourning.&#xA;3 Who will grant me that I might know and find him, and come even to his throne?&#xA;4 I would set judgment before him, and would fill my mouth with complaints.&#xA;5 That I might know the words that he would answer me, and understand what he would say to me.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 24</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/47-job/chap024/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/47-job/chap024/</guid>
      <description>1 Times are not hid from the Almighty: but they that know him, know not his days.&#xA;2 Some have removed landmarks, have taken away flocks by force, and fed them.&#xA;3 They have driven away the ass of the fatherless, and have taken away the widow&amp;rsquo;s ox for a pledge.&#xA;4 They have overturned the way of the poor, and have oppressed together the meek of the earth.&#xA;5 Others like wild asses in the desert go forth to their work: by watching for a prey they get bread for their children.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 25</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/47-job/chap025/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/47-job/chap025/</guid>
      <description>1 Then Baldad the Suhite answered, and said:&#xA;2 Power and terror are with him, who maketh peace in his high places.&#xA;3 Is there any numbering of his soldiers? and upon whom shall not his light arise?&#xA;4 Can man be justified compared with God, or he that is born of a woman appear clean?&#xA;5 Behold even the moon doth not shine, and the stars are not pure in his sight.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 26</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/47-job/chap026/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/47-job/chap026/</guid>
      <description>1 Then Job answered, and said:&#xA;2 Whose helper art thou? is it of him that is weak? and dost thou hold up the arm of him that has no strength?&#xA;3 To whom hast thou given counsel? perhaps to him that hath no wisdom, and thou hast shewn thy very great prudence.&#xA;4 Whom hast thou desired to teach? was it not him that made life?&#xA;5 Behold the giants groan under the waters, and they that dwell with them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 27</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/47-job/chap027/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/47-job/chap027/</guid>
      <description>1 Job also added, taking up his parable, and said:&#xA;2 As God liveth, who hath taken away my judgment, and the Almighty, who hath brought my soul to bitterness,&#xA;3 As long as breath remaineth in me, and the spirit of God in my nostrils,&#xA;4 My lips shall not speak iniquity, neither shall my tongue contrive lying.&#xA;5 God forbid that I should judge you to be just: till I die I will not depart from my innocence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 28</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/47-job/chap028/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/47-job/chap028/</guid>
      <description>1 Silver hath beginnings of its veins, and gold hath a place wherein it is melted.&#xA;2 Iron is taken out of the earth, and stone melted with heat is turned into brass.&#xA;3 He hath set a time for darkness, and the end of all things he considereth, the stone also that is in the dark and the shadow of death.&#xA;4 The flood divideth from the people that are on their journey, those whom the food of the needy man hath forgotten, and who cannot be come at.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 29</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/47-job/chap029/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/47-job/chap029/</guid>
      <description>1 Job also added, taking up his parable, and said:&#xA;2 Who will grant me, that I might be according to the months past, according to the days in which God kept me?&#xA;3 When his lamp shined over my head, and I walked by his light in darkness?&#xA;4 As I was in the days of my youth, when God was secretly in my tabernacle?&#xA;5 When the Almighty was with me: and my servants round about me?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 3</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/47-job/chap003/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/47-job/chap003/</guid>
      <description>1 After this, Job opened his mouth, and cursed his day,&#xA;2 And he said:&#xA;3 Let the day perish wherein I was born, and the night in which it was said: A man child is conceived.&#xA;4 Let that day be turned into darkness, let not God regard it from above, and let not the light shine upon it.&#xA;5 Let darkness, and the shadow of death, cover it, let a mist overspread it, and let it be wrapped up in bitterness.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 30</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/47-job/chap030/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/47-job/chap030/</guid>
      <description>1 But now the younger in time scorn me, whose fathers I would not have set with the dogs of my flock:&#xA;2 The strength of whose hands was to me as nothing, and they were thought unworthy of life itself.&#xA;3 Barren with want and hunger, who gnawed in the wilderness, disfigured with calamity and misery.&#xA;4 And they ate grass, and barks of trees, and the root of junipers was their food.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 31</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/47-job/chap031/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/47-job/chap031/</guid>
      <description>1 I made a covenant with my eyes, that I would not so much as think upon a virgin.&#xA;2 For what part should God from above have in me, and what inheritance the Almighty from on high?&#xA;3 Is not destruction to the wicked, and aversion to them that work iniquity?&#xA;4 Doth not he consider my ways, and number all my steps?&#xA;5 If I have walked in vanity, and my foot hath made haste to deceit:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 32</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/47-job/chap032/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/47-job/chap032/</guid>
      <description>1 So these three men ceased to answer Job, because he seemed just to himself.&#xA;2 And Eliu the son of Barachel the Buzite of the kindred of Ram, was angry and was moved to indignation: now he was angry against Job, because he said he was just before God.&#xA;3 And he was angry with his friends, because they had not found a reasonable answer, but only had condemned Job.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 33</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/47-job/chap033/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/47-job/chap033/</guid>
      <description>1 Hear therefore, O Job, my speeches, and hearken to all my words.&#xA;2 Behold now I have opened my mouth, let my tongue speak within my jaws.&#xA;3 My words are from my upright heart, and my lips shall speak a pure sentence.&#xA;4 The spirit of God made me, and the breath of the Almighty gave me life.&#xA;5 If thou canst, answer me, and stand up against my face.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 34</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/47-job/chap034/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/47-job/chap034/</guid>
      <description>1 And Eliu continued his discourse, and said:&#xA;2 Hear ye, wise men, my words, and ye learned, hearken to me:&#xA;3 For the ear trieth words, and the mouth discerneth meats by the taste.&#xA;4 Let us choose to us judgment, and let us see among ourselves what is the best.&#xA;5 For Job hath said: I am just, and God hath overthrown my judgment.&#xA;6 For in judging me there is a lie: my arrow is violent without any sin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 35</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/47-job/chap035/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/47-job/chap035/</guid>
      <description>1 Moreover Eliu spoke these words:&#xA;2 Doth thy thought seem right to thee, that thou shouldst say: I am more just than God?&#xA;3 For thou saidst: That which is right doth not please thee: or what will it profit thee if I sin?&#xA;4 Therefore I will answer thy words, and thy friends with thee.&#xA;5 Look up to heaven and see, and behold the sky, that it is higher than thee.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 36</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/47-job/chap036/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/47-job/chap036/</guid>
      <description>1 Eliu also proceeded, and said:&#xA;2 Suffer me a little, and I will shew thee: for I have yet somewhat to speak in God&amp;rsquo;s behalf.&#xA;3 I will repeat my knowledge from the beginning, and I will prove my Maker just.&#xA;4 For indeed my words are without a lie, and perfect knowledge shall be proved to thee.&#xA;5 God doth not cast away the mighty, whereas he himself also is mighty.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 37</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/47-job/chap037/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/47-job/chap037/</guid>
      <description>1 At this my heart trembleth, and is moved out of its place.&#xA;2 Hear ye attentively the terror of his voice, and the sound that cometh out of his mouth.&#xA;3 He beholdeth under all the heavens, and his light is upon the ends of the earth.&#xA;4 After it a noise shall roar, he shall thunder with the voice of his majesty, and shall not be found out, when his voice shall be heard.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 38</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/47-job/chap038/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/47-job/chap038/</guid>
      <description>1 Then the Lord answered Job out of a whirlwind, and said:&#xA;2 Who is this that wrappeth up sentences in unskilful words?&#xA;3 Gird up thy loins like a man: I will ask thee, and answer thou me.&#xA;4 Where wast thou when I laid the foundations of the earth? tell me if thou hast understanding.&#xA;5 Who hath laid the measures thereof, if thou knowest or who hath stretched the line upon it?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 39</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/47-job/chap039/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/47-job/chap039/</guid>
      <description>1 Knowest thou the time when the wild goats bring forth among the rocks, or hast thou observed the hinds when they fawn?&#xA;2 Hast thou numbered the months of their conceiving, or knowest thou the time when they bring forth?&#xA;3 They bow themselves to bring forth young, and they cast them, and send forth roarings.&#xA;4 Their young are weaned and go to feed: they go forth, and return not to them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 4</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/47-job/chap004/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/47-job/chap004/</guid>
      <description>1 Then Eliphaz, the Themanite, answered, and said:&#xA;2 If we begin to speak to thee, perhaps thou wilt take it ill; but who can withhold the words he hath conceived?&#xA;3 Behold thou hast taught many, and thou hast strengthened the weary hands:&#xA;4 Thy words have confirmed them that were staggering, and thou hast strengthened the trembling knees:&#xA;5 But now the scourge is come upon thee, and thou faintest: It hath touched thee, and thou art troubled.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 40</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/47-job/chap040/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/47-job/chap040/</guid>
      <description>1 And the Lord answering Job out of the whirlwind, said:&#xA;2 Gird up thy loins like a man: I will ask thee, and do thou tell me.&#xA;3 Wilt thou make void my judgment: and condemn me, that thou mayst be justified?&#xA;4 And hast thou an arm like God, and canst thou thunder with a voice like him?&#xA;5 Clothe thyself with beauty, and set thyself up on high, and be glorious, and put on goodly garments.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 41</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/47-job/chap041/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/47-job/chap041/</guid>
      <description>1 I will not stir him up, like one that is cruel, for who can resist my countenance?&#xA;2 Who hath given me before that I should repay him? All things that are under heaven are mine.&#xA;3 I will not spare him, nor his mighty words, and framed to make supplication.&#xA;4 Who can discover the face of his garment? or who can go into the midst of his mouth?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 42</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/47-job/chap042/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/47-job/chap042/</guid>
      <description>1 Then Job answered the Lord, and said:&#xA;2 I know that thou canst do all things, and no thought is hid from thee.&#xA;3 Who is this that hideth counsel without knowledge? Therefore I have spoken unwisely, and things that above measure exceeded my knowledge.&#xA;4 Hear, and I will speak: I will ask thee, and do thou tell me.&#xA;5 With the hearing of the ear, I have heard thee, but now my eye seeth thee.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 5</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/47-job/chap005/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/47-job/chap005/</guid>
      <description>1 Call now, if there be any that will answer thee, and turn to some of the saints.&#xA;2 Anger indeed killeth the foolish, and envy slayeth the little one.&#xA;3 I have seen a fool with a strong root, and I cursed his beauty immediately.&#xA;4 His children shall be far from safety, and shall be destroyed in the gate, and there shall be none to deliver them.&#xA;5 Whose harvest the hungry shall eat, and the armed man shall take him by violence, and the thirsty shall drink up his riches.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 6</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/47-job/chap006/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/47-job/chap006/</guid>
      <description>1 But Job answered, and said:&#xA;2 O that my sins, whereby I have deserved wrath, and the calamity that I suffer, were weighed in a balance.&#xA;3 As the sand of the sea, this would appear heavier: therefore, my words are full of sorrow:&#xA;4 For the arrows of the Lord are in me, the rage whereof drinketh up my spirit, and the terrors of the Lord war against me.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 7</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/47-job/chap007/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/47-job/chap007/</guid>
      <description>1 The life of man upon earth is a warfare, and his days are like the days of a hireling.&#xA;2 As a servant longeth for the shade, as the hireling looketh for the end of his work;&#xA;3 So I also have had empty months, and have numbered to myself wearisome nights.&#xA;4 If I lie down to sleep, I shall say: When shall I rise? and again, I shall look for the evening, and shall be filled with sorrows even till darkness.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 8</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/47-job/chap008/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/47-job/chap008/</guid>
      <description>1 Then Baldad, the Suhite, answered, and said:&#xA;2 How long wilt thou speak these things, and how long shall the words of thy mouth be like a strong wind?&#xA;3 Doth God pervert judgment, or doth the Almighty overthrow that which is just?&#xA;4 Although thy children have sinned against him, and he hath left them in the hand of their iniquity:&#xA;5 Yet if thou wilt arise early to God, and wilt beseech the Almighty:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 9</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/47-job/chap009/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/47-job/chap009/</guid>
      <description>1 And Job answered, and said:&#xA;2 Indeed I know it is so, and that man cannot be justified, compared with God.&#xA;3 If he will contend with him, he cannot answer him one for a thousand.&#xA;4 He is wise in heart, and mighty in strength: who hath resisted him, and hath had peace?&#xA;5 Who hath removed mountains, and they whom he overthrew in his wrath, knew it not.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
