<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>1 Thessalonians on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/13-1-thessalonians/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 1 Thessalonians on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:24 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/13-1-thessalonians/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 1</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/13-1-thessalonians/chap001/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:24 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/13-1-thessalonians/chap001/</guid>
      <description>1 Paul and Sylvanus and Timothy to the church of the Thessalonians: in God the Father and in the Lord Jesus Christ.&#xA;2 Grace be to you and peace. We give thanks to God always for you all: making a remembrance of you in our prayers without ceasing,&#xA;3 Being mindful of the work of your faith and labour and charity: and of the enduring of the hope of our Lord Jesus Christ before God and our Father.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 2</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/13-1-thessalonians/chap002/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:24 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/13-1-thessalonians/chap002/</guid>
      <description>1 For yourselves know, brethren, our entrance in unto you, that it was not in vain:&#xA;2 But having suffered many things before and been shamefully treated, (as you know) at Philippi, we had confidence in our God, to speak unto you the gospel of God in much carefulness.&#xA;3 For our exhortation was not of error, nor of uncleanness, nor in deceit.&#xA;4 But as we were approved by God that the gospel should be committed to us: even so we speak, not as pleasing men but God, who proveth our hearts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 3</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/13-1-thessalonians/chap003/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:24 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/13-1-thessalonians/chap003/</guid>
      <description>1 For which cause, forbearing no longer, we thought it good to remain at Athens alone.&#xA;2 And we sent Timothy, our brother and the minister of God in the gospel of Christ, to confirm you and exhort you concerning your faith:&#xA;3 That no man should be moved in these tribulations: for yourselves know that we are appointed thereunto.&#xA;4 For even when we were with you, we foretold you that we should suffer tribulations: as also it is come to pass, and you know.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 4</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/13-1-thessalonians/chap004/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:24 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/13-1-thessalonians/chap004/</guid>
      <description>1 For the rest therefore, brethren, pray and beseech you in the Lord Jesus that, as you have received from us, how you ought to walk and to please God, so also you would walk, that you may abound the more.&#xA;2 For you know what precepts I have given to you by the Lord Jesus.&#xA;3 For this is the will of God, your sanctification: That you should abstain from fornication:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 5</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/13-1-thessalonians/chap005/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:24 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/13-1-thessalonians/chap005/</guid>
      <description>1 But of the times and moments, brethren, you need not, that we should write to you:&#xA;2 For yourselves know perfectly that the day of the Lord shall so come as a thief in the night.&#xA;3 For when they shall say: Peace and security; then shall sudden destruction come upon them, as the pains upon her that is with child, and they shall not escape.&#xA;4 But you, brethren, are not in darkness, that the day should overtake you as a thief.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
