<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Numbers on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</title>
    <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/31-numbers/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Numbers on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/31-numbers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 1</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/31-numbers/chap001/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/31-numbers/chap001/</guid>
      <description>1 And the Lord spoke to Moses in the desert of Sinai in the tabernacle of the covenant, the first day of the second month, the second year of their going out of Egypt, saying:&#xA;2 Take the sum of all the congregation of the children of Israel by their families, and houses, and the names of every one, as many as are of the male sex,&#xA;3 From twenty years old and upwards, of all the men of Israel fit for war, and you shall number them by their troops, thou and Aaron.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 10</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/31-numbers/chap010/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/31-numbers/chap010/</guid>
      <description>1 And the Lord spoke to Moses, saying:&#xA;2 Make thee two trumpets of beaten silver, wherewith thou mayest call together the multitude when the camp is to be removed.&#xA;3 And when thou shalt sound the trumpets, all the multitude shall gather unto thee to the door of the tabernacle of the covenant.&#xA;4 If thou sound but once, the princes and the heads of the multitude of Israel shall come to thee.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 11</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/31-numbers/chap011/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/31-numbers/chap011/</guid>
      <description>1 In the mean time there arose a murmuring of the people against the Lord, as it were repining at their fatigue. And when the Lord heard it he was angry. And the fire of the Lord being kindled against them, devoured them that were at the uttermost part of the camp.&#xA;2 And when the people cried to Moses, Moses prayed to the Lord, and the fire was swallowed up.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 12</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/31-numbers/chap012/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/31-numbers/chap012/</guid>
      <description>1 And Mary and Aaron spoke against Moses, because of his wife the Ethiopian,&#xA;2 And they said: Hath the Lord spoken by Moses only? Hath he not also spoken to us in like manner? And when the Lord heard this,&#xA;3 (For Moses was a man exceeding meek above all men that dwelt upon earth)&#xA;4 Immediately he spoke to him, and to Aaron and Mary: Come out you three only to the tabernacle of the covenant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 13</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/31-numbers/chap013/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/31-numbers/chap013/</guid>
      <description>1 And the people marched from Haseroth, and pitched their tents in the desert of Pharan.&#xA;2 And there the Lord spoke to Moses, saying.&#xA;3 Send men to view the land of Chanaan, which I will give to the children of Israel, one of every tribe, of the rulers.&#xA;4 Moses did what the Lord had commanded, sending from the desert of Pharan, principal men, whose names are these:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 14</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/31-numbers/chap014/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/31-numbers/chap014/</guid>
      <description>1 Therefore the whole multitude crying wept that night.&#xA;2 And all the children of Israel murmured against Moses and Aaron, saying:&#xA;3 Would God that we had died in Egypt: and would God we may die in this vast wilderness, and that the Lord may not bring us into this land, lest we fall by the sword, and our wives and children be led away captives. Is it not better to return into Egypt?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 15</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/31-numbers/chap015/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/31-numbers/chap015/</guid>
      <description>1 And the Lord spoke to Moses, saying:&#xA;2 Speak to the children of Israel and thou shalt say to them: When you shall be come unto the land of your habitation, which I will give you,&#xA;3 And shall make an offering to the Lord, for a holocaust, or a victim, paying your vows, or voluntarily offering gifts, or in your solemnities burning a sweet savour unto the Lord, of oxen or of sheep:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 16</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/31-numbers/chap016/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/31-numbers/chap016/</guid>
      <description>1 And behold Core the son of Isaar, the son of Caath, the son of Levi, and Dathan and Abiron the sons of Eliab, and Hon the son of Pheleth of the children of Ruben,&#xA;2 Rose up against Moses, and with them two hundred and fifty others of the children of Israel, leading men of the synagogue, and who in the time of assembly were called by name.&#xA;3 And when they had stood up against Moses and Aaron, they said: Let it be enough for you, that all the multitude consisteth of holy ones, and the Lord is among them: Why lift you up yourselves above the people of the Lord?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 17</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/31-numbers/chap017/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/31-numbers/chap017/</guid>
      <description>1 And the Lord spoke to Moses, saying:&#xA;2 Speak to the children of Israel, and take of every one of them a rod by their kindreds, of all the princes of the tribes, twelve rods, and write the name of every man upon his rod.&#xA;3 And the name of Aaron shall be for the tribe of Levi, and one rod shall contain all their families:&#xA;4 And thou shalt lay them up in the tabernacle of the covenant before the testimony, where I will speak to thee.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 18</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/31-numbers/chap018/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/31-numbers/chap018/</guid>
      <description>1 And the Lord said to Aaron: Thou, and thy sons, and thy father&amp;rsquo;s house with thee shall bear the iniquity of the sanctuary: and thou and thy sons with thee shall bear the sins of your priesthood.&#xA;2 And take with thee thy brethren also of the tribe of Levi, and the sceptre of thy father, and let them be ready in hand, and minister to thee: but thou and thy sons shall minister in the tabernacle of the testimony.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 19</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/31-numbers/chap019/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/31-numbers/chap019/</guid>
      <description>1 And the Lord spoke to Moses and Aaron, saying:&#xA;2 This is the observance of the victim, which the Lord hath ordained. Command the children of Israel, that they bring unto thee a red cow of full age, in which there is no blemish, and which hath not carried the yoke:&#xA;3 And you shall deliver her to Eleazar the priest, who shall bring her forth without the camp, and shall immolate her in the sight of all:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 2</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/31-numbers/chap002/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/31-numbers/chap002/</guid>
      <description>1 And the Lord spoke to Moses and Aaron, saying:&#xA;2 All the children of Israel shall camp by their troops, ensigns, and standards, and the houses of their kindreds, round about the tabernacle of the covenant.&#xA;3 On the east Juda shall pitch his tents by the bands of his army: and the prince of his sons; shall be Nahasson the son of Aminadab.&#xA;4 And the whole sum of the fighting men of his stock, were seventy-four thousand six hundred.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 20</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/31-numbers/chap020/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/31-numbers/chap020/</guid>
      <description>1 And the children of Israel, and all the multitude came into the desert of Sin, in the first month: and the people abode in Cades. And Mary died there, and was buried in the same place.&#xA;2 And the people wanting water, came together against Moses and Aaron:&#xA;3 And making a sedition, they said: Would God we had perished among our brethren before the Lord.&#xA;4 Why have you brought out the church of the Lord into the wilderness, that both we and our cattle should die?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 21</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/31-numbers/chap021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/31-numbers/chap021/</guid>
      <description>1 And when king Arad the Chanaanite, who dwelt towards the south, had heard this, to wit, that Israel was come by the way of the spies, he fought against them, and overcoming them carried off their spoils.&#xA;2 But Israel binding himself by vow to the Lord, said: If thou wilt deliver thus people into my hand, I will utterly destroy their cities.&#xA;3 And the Lord heard the prayers of Israel, and delivered up the Chanaanite, and they cut them off and destroyed their cities: and they called the name of that place Horma, that is to say, Anathema.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 22</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/31-numbers/chap022/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/31-numbers/chap022/</guid>
      <description>1 And they went forward and encamped in the plains of Moab, over against where Jericho is situate beyond the Jordan.&#xA;2 And Balac the son of Sephor, seeing all that Israel had done to the Amorrhite,&#xA;3 And that the Moabites were in great fear of him, and were not able to sustain his assault,&#xA;4 He said to the elders of Madian: So will this people destroy all that dwell in our borders, as the ox is wont to eat the grass to the very roots.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 23</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/31-numbers/chap023/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/31-numbers/chap023/</guid>
      <description>1 And Balaam said to Balac: Build me here seven altars, and prepare as many calves, and the same number of rams.&#xA;2 And when he had done according to the word of Balaam, they laid together a calf and a ram upon every altar.&#xA;3 And Balaam said to Balac: Stand a while by thy burnt offering, until I go, to see if perhaps the Lord will meet me, and whatsoever he shall command, I will speak to thee.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 24</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/31-numbers/chap024/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/31-numbers/chap024/</guid>
      <description>1 And when Balaam saw that it pleased the Lord that he should bless Israel, he went not as he had gone before, to seek divination: but setting his face towards the desert,&#xA;2 And lifting up his eyes, he saw Israel abiding in their tents by their tribes: and the spirit of God rushing upon him,&#xA;3 He took up his parable and said: Balaam the son of Beor hath said: The man hath said, whose eye is stopped up:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 25</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/31-numbers/chap025/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/31-numbers/chap025/</guid>
      <description>1 And Israel at that time abode in Settim, and the people committed fornication with the daughters of Moab,&#xA;2 Who called them to their sacrifices. And they ate of them, and adored their gods.&#xA;3 And Israel was initiated to Beelphegor: upon which the Lord being angry,&#xA;4 Said to Moses: Take all the princes of the people, and hang them up on gibbets against the sun: that my fury may be turned away from Israel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 26</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/31-numbers/chap026/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/31-numbers/chap026/</guid>
      <description>1 After the blood of the guilty was shed, the Lord said to Moses and to Eleazar the son of Aaron, the priest:&#xA;2 Number the whole sum of the children of Israel from twenty years old and upward, by their houses and kindreds, all that are able to go forth to war.&#xA;3 Moses therefore and Eleazar the priest, being in the plains of Moab upon the Jordan over against Jericho, spoke to them that were</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 27</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/31-numbers/chap027/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/31-numbers/chap027/</guid>
      <description>1 Then came the daughters of Salphaad, the son of Hepher, the son of Galaad, the son of Machir, the son of Manasses, who was the son of Joseph: and their names are Maala, and Noa, and Hegla, and Melcha, and Thersa.&#xA;2 And they stood before Moses and Eleazar the priest, and all the princes of the people at the door of the tabernacle of the covenant, and said:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 28</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/31-numbers/chap028/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/31-numbers/chap028/</guid>
      <description>1 The Lord also said to Moses:&#xA;2 Command the children of Israel, and thou shalt say to them: Offer ye my oblation and my bread, and burnt sacrifice of most sweet odour, in their due seasons.&#xA;3 These are the sacrifices which you shall offer: Two lambs of a year old without blemish every day for the perpetual holocaust:&#xA;4 One you shall offer in the mornings, and the other in the evening:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 29</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/31-numbers/chap029/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/31-numbers/chap029/</guid>
      <description>1 The first day also of the seventh month shall be venerable and holy unto you; you shall do no servile work therein, because it is the day of the sounding and of trumpets.&#xA;2 And you shall offer a holocaust for a most sweet odour to the Lord, one calf of the herd, one ram and seven lambs of a year old, without blemish.&#xA;3 And for their sacrifices, three tenths of flour tempered with oil to every calf, two tenths to a ram,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 3</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/31-numbers/chap003/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/31-numbers/chap003/</guid>
      <description>1 These are the generations of Aaron and Moses in the day that the Lord spoke to Moses in mount Sinai.&#xA;2 And these the names of the sons of Aaron: his firstborn Nadab, then Abiu, and Eleazar, and Ithamar.&#xA;3 These the names of the sons of Aaron the priests that were anointed, and whose hands were filled and consecrated, to do the functions of priesthood.&#xA;4 Now Nadab and Abiu died, without children, when they offered strange fire before the Lord, in the desert of Sinai: and Eleazar and Ithamar performed the priestly office in the presence of Aaron their father.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 30</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/31-numbers/chap030/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/31-numbers/chap030/</guid>
      <description>1 And Moses told the children of Israel all that the Lord had commanded him:&#xA;2 And he said to the princes of the tribes of the children of Israel: This is the word that the Lord hath commanded:&#xA;3 If any man make a vow to the Lord, or bind himself by an oath: he shall not make his word void but shall fulfil all that he promised.&#xA;4 If a woman vow any thing, and bind herself by an oath, being in her father&amp;rsquo;s house, and but yet a girl in age: if her father knew the vow that she hath promised, and the oath wherewith she hath bound her soul, and held his peace, she shall be bound by the vow:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 31</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/31-numbers/chap031/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/31-numbers/chap031/</guid>
      <description>1 And the Lord spoke to Moses, saying:&#xA;2 Revenge first the children of Israel on the Madianites, and so thou shalt be gathered to thy people.&#xA;3 And Moses forthwith said: Arm of you men to fight, who may take the revenge of the Lord on the Madianites.&#xA;4 Let a thousand men be chosen out of every tribe of Israel to be sent to the war.&#xA;5 And they gave a thousand of every tribe, that is to say, twelve thousand men well appointed for battle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 32</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/31-numbers/chap032/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/31-numbers/chap032/</guid>
      <description>1 And the sons of Ruben and Gad had many flocks of cattle, and their substance in beasts was infinite. And when they saw the lands of Jazer and Galaad fit for feeding cattle,&#xA;2 They came to Moses and Eleazar the priest, and the princes of the multitude, and said:&#xA;3 Ataroth, and Dibon, and Jazer, and Nemra, Hesebon, and Eleale, and Saban, and Nebo, and Beon,&#xA;4 The land, which the Lord hath conquered in the sight of the children of Israel, is a very fertile soil for the feeding of beasts: and we thy servants have very much cattle:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 33</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/31-numbers/chap033/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/31-numbers/chap033/</guid>
      <description>1 These are the mansions of the children of Israel, who went out of Egypt by their troops under the conduct of Moses and Aaron,&#xA;2 Which Moses wrote down according to the places of their encamping, which they changed by the commandment of the Lord.&#xA;3 Now the children of Israel departed from Ramesses the first month, on the fifteenth day of the first month, the day after the phase, with a mighty hand, in the sight of all the Egyptians,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 34</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/31-numbers/chap034/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/31-numbers/chap034/</guid>
      <description>1 And the Lord spoke to Moses, saying:&#xA;2 Command the children of Israel, and thou shalt say to them: When you are entered into the land of Chanaan, and it shall be fallen into your possession by lot, it shall be bounded by these limits:&#xA;3 The south side shall begin from the wilderness of Sin, which is by Edom: and shall have the most salt sea for its furthest limits eastward:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 35</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/31-numbers/chap035/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/31-numbers/chap035/</guid>
      <description>1 And the Lord spoke these things also to Moses in the plains of Moab by the Jordan, over against Jericho:&#xA;2 Command the children of Israel that they give to the Levites out of their possessions,&#xA;3 Cities to dwell in, and their suburbs round about: that they may abide in the towns, and the suburbs may be for them cattle and beasts:&#xA;4 Which suburbs shall reach from the walls of the cities outward, a thousand paces on every side:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 36</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/31-numbers/chap036/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/31-numbers/chap036/</guid>
      <description>1 And the princes of the families of Galaad, the son of Machir, the son of Manasses, of the stock of the children of Joseph, came and spoke to Moses before the princes of Israel, and said:&#xA;2 The Lord hath commanded thee, my lord, that thou shouldst divide the land by lot to the children of Israel, and that thou shouldst give to the daughters of Salphaad our brother the possession due to their father:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 4</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/31-numbers/chap004/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/31-numbers/chap004/</guid>
      <description>1 And the Lord spoke to Moses, and Aaron, saying:&#xA;2 Take the sum of the sons of Caath from the midst of the Levites, by their houses and families.&#xA;3 From thirty years old and upward, to fifty years old, of all that go in to stand and to minister in the tabernacle of the covenant.&#xA;4 This is the service of the sons of Caath:&#xA;5 When the camp is; to set forward, Aaron and his sons shall go into the tabernacle of the covenant, and the holy of holies, and shall take down the veil that hangeth before the door, and shall wrap up the ark of the testimony in it,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 5</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/31-numbers/chap005/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/31-numbers/chap005/</guid>
      <description>1 And the Lord spoke to Moses, saying:&#xA;2 Command the children of Israel, that they cast out of the camp every leper, and whosoever hath an issue of seed, or is defiled by the dead:&#xA;3 Whether it be man or woman, cast ye them out of the camp, lest they defile it when I shall dwell with you,&#xA;4 And the children of Israel did so, and they cast them forth without the camp, as the Lord had spoken to Moses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 6</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/31-numbers/chap006/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/31-numbers/chap006/</guid>
      <description>1 And the Lord spoke to Moses, saying:&#xA;2 Speak to the children of Israel, and thou shalt say to them: When a man, or woman, shall make a vow to be sanctified, and will consecrate themselves to the Lord:&#xA;3 They shall abstain from wine, and from every thing that may make a man drunk. They shall not drink vinegar of wine, or of any other drink, nor any thing that is pressed out of the grape: nor shall they eat grapes either fresh or dried.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 7</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/31-numbers/chap007/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/31-numbers/chap007/</guid>
      <description>1 And it came to pass in the day that Moses had finished the tabernacle, and set it up, and had anointed and sanctified it with all its vessels, the altar likewise and all the vessels thereof,&#xA;2 The princes of Israel and the heads of the families, in every tribe, who were the rulers of them who had been numbered, offered&#xA;3 Their gifts before the Lord, six wagons covered, and twelve oxen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 8</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/31-numbers/chap008/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/31-numbers/chap008/</guid>
      <description>1 And the Lord spoke to Moses, saying:&#xA;2 Speak to Aaron, and thou shalt say to him: When thou shalt place the seven lamps, let the candlestick be set up on the south side. Give orders therefore that the lamps look over against the north, towards the table of the loaves of proposition, over against that part shall they give light, towards which the candlestick looketh.&#xA;3 And Aaron did so, and he put the lamps upon the candlestick, as the Lord had commanded Moses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 9</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/31-numbers/chap009/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/31-numbers/chap009/</guid>
      <description>1 The Lord spoke to Moses in the desert of Sinai, the second year after they were come out of the land of Egypt, in the first month, saying:&#xA;2 Let the children of Israel make the phase in its due time,&#xA;3 The fourteenth day of this month in the evening, according to all the ceremonies and justifications thereof.&#xA;4 And Moses commanded the children of Israel that they should make the phase.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
