<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Lamentations on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</title>
    <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/56-lamentations/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Lamentations on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:32 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/56-lamentations/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 1</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/56-lamentations/chap001/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:32 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/56-lamentations/chap001/</guid>
      <description>1 Aleph. How doth the city sit solitary that was full of people! how is the mistress of the Gentiles become as a widow: the princes of provinces made tributary!&#xA;2 Beth. Weeping, she hath wept in the night, and her tears are on her cheeks: there is none to comfort her among all them that were dear to her: all her friends have despised her, and are become her enemies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 2</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/56-lamentations/chap002/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:32 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/56-lamentations/chap002/</guid>
      <description>1 Aleph. How hath the Lord covered with obscurity the daughter of Sion in his wrath! how hath he cast down from heaven to the earth the glorious one of Israel, and hath not remembered his footstool in the day of his anger.&#xA;2 Beth. The Lord hath cast down headlong, and hath not spared, all that was beautiful in Jacob: he hath destroyed in his wrath the strong holds of the virgin of Juda, and brought them down to the ground: he hath made the kingdom unclean, and the princes thereof.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 3</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/56-lamentations/chap003/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:32 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/56-lamentations/chap003/</guid>
      <description>1 Aleph. I am the man that see my poverty by the rod of his indignation.&#xA;2 Aleph. He hath led me, and brought me into darkness, and not into light.&#xA;3 Aleph. Only against me he hath turned, and turned again his hand all the day.&#xA;4 Beth. My skin and my flesh he hath made old, he hath broken my bones.&#xA;5 Beth. He hath built round about me, and he hath compassed me with gall, and labour.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 4</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/56-lamentations/chap004/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:32 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/56-lamentations/chap004/</guid>
      <description>1 Aleph. How is the gold become dim, the finest colour is changed, the stones of the sanctuary are scattered in the top of every street?&#xA;2 Beth. The noble sons of Sion, and they that were clothed with the best gold: how are they esteemed as earthen vessels, the work of the potter&amp;rsquo;s hands?&#xA;3 Ghimel. Even the sea monsters have drawn out the breast, they have given suck to their young: the daughter of my people is cruel, like the ostrich in the desert.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 5</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/56-lamentations/chap005/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:32 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/56-lamentations/chap005/</guid>
      <description>1 Remember, O Lord, what is come upon us: consider and behold our reproach.&#xA;2 Our inheritance is turned to aliens: our houses to strangers.&#xA;3 We are become orphans without a father: our mothers are as widows.&#xA;4 We have drunk our water for money: we have bought our wood.&#xA;6 We were dragged by the necks, we were weary and no rest was given us.&#xA;6 We have given our hand to Egypt, and to the Assyrians, that we might be satisfied with bread.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
