<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Proverbs on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/49-proverbs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Proverbs on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:40 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/49-proverbs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 1</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/49-proverbs/chap001/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:40 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/49-proverbs/chap001/</guid>
      <description>1 The parables of Solomon, the son of David, king of Israel,&#xA;2 To know wisdom, and instruction:&#xA;3 To understand the words of prudence: and to receive the instruction of doctrine, justice, and judgment, and equity:&#xA;4 To give subtilty to little ones, to the young man knowledge and understanding.&#xA;5 A wise man shall hear, and shall be wiser: and he that understandeth shall possess governments.&#xA;6 He shall understand a parable and the interpretation, the words of the wise, and their mysterious sayings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 10</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/49-proverbs/chap010/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:40 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/49-proverbs/chap010/</guid>
      <description>1 A wise son maketh the father glad: but a foolish son is the sorrow of his mother.&#xA;2 Treasures of wickedness shall profit nothing: but justice shall deliver from death.&#xA;3 The Lord will not afflict the soul of the just with famine, and he will disappoint the deceitful practices of the wicked.&#xA;4 The slothful hand hath wrought poverty: but the hand of the industrious getteth riches. He that trusteth to lies feedeth the winds: and the same runneth after birds, that fly away.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 11</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/49-proverbs/chap011/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:40 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/49-proverbs/chap011/</guid>
      <description>1 A deceitful balance is an abomination before the Lord: and a just weight is his will.&#xA;2 Where pride is, there also shall be reproach: but where humility is, there also is wisdom.&#xA;3 The simplicity of the just shall guide them: and the deceitfulness of the wicked shall destroy them.&#xA;4 Riches shall not profit in the day of revenge: but justice shall deliver from death.&#xA;5 The justice of the upright shall make his way prosperous: and the wicked man shall fall by his own wickedness.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 12</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/49-proverbs/chap012/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:40 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/49-proverbs/chap012/</guid>
      <description>1 He that loveth correction, loveth knowledge: but he that hateth reproof, is foolish.&#xA;2 He that is good, shall draw grace from the Lord: but he that trusteth in his own devices, doth wickedly.&#xA;3 Man shall not be strengthened by wickedness: and the root of the just shall not be moved.&#xA;4 A diligent woman is a crown to her husband: and she that doth things worthy of confusion, is as rottenness in his bones.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 13</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/49-proverbs/chap013/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:40 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/49-proverbs/chap013/</guid>
      <description>1 A wise son heareth the doctrine of his father: but he that is a scorner, heareth not when he is reproved.&#xA;2 Of the fruit of his own month shall a man be filled with good things: but the soul of transgressors is wicked.&#xA;3 He that keepeth his mouth keepeth his soul: but he that hath no guard on his speech shall meet with evils.&#xA;4 The sluggard willeth, and willeth not: but the soul of them that work, shall be made fat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 14</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/49-proverbs/chap014/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:40 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/49-proverbs/chap014/</guid>
      <description>1 A wise woman buildeth her house: but the foolish will pull down with her hands that also which is built.&#xA;2 He that walketh in the right way, and feareth God, is despised by him that goeth by an infamous way.&#xA;3 In the mouth of a fool is the rod of pride: but the lips of the wise preserve them.&#xA;4 Where there are no oxen, the crib is empty: but where there is much corn, there the strength of the ox is manifest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 15</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/49-proverbs/chap015/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:40 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/49-proverbs/chap015/</guid>
      <description>1 A mild answer breaketh wrath: but a harsh word stirreth up fury.&#xA;2 The tongue of the wise adorneth knowledge: but the mouth of fools bubbleth out folly.&#xA;3 The eyes of the Lord in every place behold the good and the evil.&#xA;4 A peaceable tongue is a tree of life: but that which is immoderate, shall crush the spirit.&#xA;5 A fool laugheth at the instruction of his father: but he that regardeth reproofs shall become prudent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 16</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/49-proverbs/chap016/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:40 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/49-proverbs/chap016/</guid>
      <description>1 It is the part of man to prepare the soul: and of the Lord to govern the tongue.&#xA;2 All the ways of a man are open to his eyes: the Lord is the weigher of spirits.&#xA;3 Lay open thy works to the Lord: and thy thoughts shall be directed.&#xA;4 The Lord hath made all things for himself: the wicked also for the evil day.&#xA;5 Every proud man is an abomination to the Lord: though hand should be joined to hand, he is not innocent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 17</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/49-proverbs/chap017/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:40 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/49-proverbs/chap017/</guid>
      <description>1 Better is a dry morsel with joy, than a house full of victims with strife.&#xA;2 A wise servant shall rule over foolish sons, and shall divide the inheritance among the brethren.&#xA;3 As silver is tried by fire, and gold in the furnace: so the Lord trieth the hearts.&#xA;4 The evil man obeyeth an unjust tongue: and the deceitful hearkeneth to lying lips.&#xA;5 He that despiseth the poor, reproacheth his maker: and he that rejoiceth at another man&amp;rsquo;s ruin, shall not be unpunished.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 18</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/49-proverbs/chap018/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:40 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/49-proverbs/chap018/</guid>
      <description>1 He that hath a mind to depart from a friend, seeketh occasions: he shall ever be subject to reproach.&#xA;2 A fool receiveth not the words of prudence: unless thou say those things which are in his heart.&#xA;3 The wicked man, when he is come into the depths of sins, contemneth: but ignominy and reproach follow him.&#xA;4 Words from the mouth of a man are as deep water: and the fountain of wisdom is an overflowing stream.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 19</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/49-proverbs/chap019/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:40 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/49-proverbs/chap019/</guid>
      <description>1 Better is the poor man, that walketh in his simplicity, than a rich man that is perverse in his lips and unwise.&#xA;2 Where there is no knowledge of the soul, there is no good: and he that is hasty with his feet shall stumble.&#xA;3 The folly of a man supplanteth his steps: and he fretteth in his mind against God.&#xA;4 Riches make many friends: but from the poor man, even they whom he had, depart.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 2</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/49-proverbs/chap002/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:40 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/49-proverbs/chap002/</guid>
      <description>1 My son, if thou wilt receive my words, and wilt hide my commandments with thee,&#xA;2 That thy ear may hearken to wisdom: incline thy heart to know prudence.&#xA;3 For if thou shalt call for wisdom, and incline thy heart to prudence:&#xA;4 If thou shalt seek her as money, and shalt dig for her as for a treasure:&#xA;5 Then shalt thou understand the fear of the Lord, and shalt find the knowledge of God:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 20</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/49-proverbs/chap020/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:40 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/49-proverbs/chap020/</guid>
      <description>1 Wine is a luxurious thing, and drunkenness riotous: whosoever is delighted therewith, shall not be wise.&#xA;2 As the roaring of a lion, so also is the dread of a king: he that provoketh him, sinneth against his own soul.&#xA;3 It is an honour for a man to separate himself from quarrels: but all fools are meddling with reproaches.&#xA;4 Because of the cold the sluggard would not plough: he shall beg therefore in the summer, and it shall not be given him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 21</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/49-proverbs/chap021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:40 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/49-proverbs/chap021/</guid>
      <description>1 As the divisions of waters, so the heart of the king is in the hand of the Lord: whithersoever he will, he shall turn it.&#xA;2 Every way of a man seemeth right to himself: but the Lord weigheth the hearts.&#xA;3 To do mercy and judgment, pleaseth the Lord more than victims.&#xA;4 Haughtiness of the eyes is the enlarging of the heart: the lamp of the wicked is sin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 22</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/49-proverbs/chap022/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:40 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/49-proverbs/chap022/</guid>
      <description>1 A good name is better than great riches: and good favour is above silver and gold.&#xA;2 The rich and poor have met one another: the Lord is the maker of them both.&#xA;3 The prudent man saw the evil, and hid himself: the simple passed on, and suffered loss.&#xA;4 The fruit of humility is the fear of the Lord, riches and glory and life.&#xA;5 Arms and swords are in the way of the perverse: but he that keepeth his own soul, departeth far from them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 23</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/49-proverbs/chap023/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:40 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/49-proverbs/chap023/</guid>
      <description>1 When thou shalt sit to eat with a prince, consider diligently what is set before thy face:&#xA;2 And put a knife to thy throat, if it be so that thou have thy soul in thy own power.&#xA;3 Be not desirous of his meats, in which is the bread of deceit.&#xA;4 Labour not to be rich: but set bounds to thy prudence.&#xA;5 Lift not up thy eyes to riches which thou canst not have: because they shall make themselves wings like those of an eagle, and shall fly towards heaven.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 24</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/49-proverbs/chap024/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:40 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/49-proverbs/chap024/</guid>
      <description>1 Seek not to be like evil men, neither desire to be with them:&#xA;2 Because their mind studieth robberies, and their lips speak deceits.&#xA;3 By wisdom the house shall be built, and by prudence it shall be strengthened.&#xA;4 By instruction the storerooms shall be filled with all precious and most beautiful wealth.&#xA;5 A wise man is strong: and a knowing man, stout and valiant.&#xA;6 Because war is managed by due ordering: and there shall be safety where there are many counsels.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 25</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/49-proverbs/chap025/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:40 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/49-proverbs/chap025/</guid>
      <description>1 These are also parables of Solomon, which the men of Ezechias, king of Juda, copied out.&#xA;2 It is the glory of God to conceal the word, and the glory of kings to search out the speech.&#xA;3 The heaven above and the earth beneath, and the heart of kings is unsearchable.&#xA;4 Take away the rust from silver, and there shall come forth a most pure vessel:&#xA;5 Take away wickedness from the face of the king, and his throne shall be established with justice.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 26</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/49-proverbs/chap026/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:40 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/49-proverbs/chap026/</guid>
      <description>1 As snow in summer, and rain in harvest, so glory is not seemly for a fool.&#xA;2 As a bird flying to other places, and a sparrow going here or there: so a curse uttered without cause shall come upon a man.&#xA;3 A whip for a horse, and a snaffle for an ass, and a rod for the back of fools.&#xA;4 Answer not a fool according to his folly, lest thou be made like him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 27</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/49-proverbs/chap027/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:40 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/49-proverbs/chap027/</guid>
      <description>1 Boast not for to morrow, for thou knowest not what the day to come may bring forth.&#xA;2 Let another praise thee, and not thy own mouth: a stranger, and not thy own lips.&#xA;3 A stone is heavy, and sand weighty: but the anger of a fool is heavier than them both.&#xA;4 Anger hath no mercy: nor fury, when it breaketh forth: and who can bear the violence of one provoked?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 28</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/49-proverbs/chap028/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:40 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/49-proverbs/chap028/</guid>
      <description>1 The wicked man fleeth, when no man pursueth: but the just, bold as a lion, shall be without dread.&#xA;2 For the sins of the land many are the princes thereof: and for the wisdom of a man, and the knowledge of those things that are said, the life of the prince shall be prolonged.&#xA;3 A poor man that oppresseth the poor, is like a violent shower, which bringeth a famine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 29</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/49-proverbs/chap029/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:40 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/49-proverbs/chap029/</guid>
      <description>1 The man that with a stiff neck despiseth him that reproveth him, shall suddenly be destroyed: and health shall not follow him.&#xA;2 When just men increase, the people shall rejoice: when the wicked shall bear rule, the people shall mourn.&#xA;3 A man that loveth wisdom, rejoiceth his father: but he that maintaineth harlots, shall squander away his substance.&#xA;4 A just king setteth up the land: a covetous man shall destroy it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 3</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/49-proverbs/chap003/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:40 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/49-proverbs/chap003/</guid>
      <description>1 My son, forget not my law, and let thy heart keep my commandments.&#xA;2 For they shall add to thee length of days, and years of life, and peace.&#xA;3 Let not mercy aud truth leave thee, put them about thy neck, and write them in the tables of thy heart.&#xA;4 And thou shalt find grace, and good understanding before God and men.&#xA;5 Have confidence in the Lord with all thy heart, and lean not upon thy own prudence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 30</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/49-proverbs/chap030/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:40 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/49-proverbs/chap030/</guid>
      <description>1 The words of Gatherer the son of Vomiter. The vision which the man spoke, with whom God is, and who being strengthened by God, abiding with him, said:&#xA;2 I am the most foolish of men, and the wisdom of men is not with me.&#xA;3 I have not learned wisdom, and have not known the science of saints.&#xA;4 Who hath ascended up into heaven, and descended? who hath held the wind in his hands?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 31</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/49-proverbs/chap031/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:40 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/49-proverbs/chap031/</guid>
      <description>1 The words of king Lamuel. The vision wherewith his mother instructed him.&#xA;2 What, O my beloved, what, O the beloved of my womb, what, O the beloved of my vows?&#xA;3 Give not thy substance to women, and thy riches to destroy kings.&#xA;4 Give not to kings, O Lamuel, give not wine to kings: because there is no secret where drunkenness reigneth:&#xA;5 And lest they drink and forget judgments, and pervert the cause of the children of the poor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 4</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/49-proverbs/chap004/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:40 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/49-proverbs/chap004/</guid>
      <description>1 Hear, ye children, the instruction of a father, and attend, that you may know prudence.&#xA;2 I will give you a good gift, forsake not my law.&#xA;3 For I also was my father&amp;rsquo;s son, tender, and as an only son in the sight of my mother:&#xA;4 And he taught me, and said: Let thy heart receive my words, keep my commandments, and thou shalt live.&#xA;5 Get wisdom, get prudence: forget not, neither decline from the words of my mouth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 5</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/49-proverbs/chap005/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:40 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/49-proverbs/chap005/</guid>
      <description>1 My son, attend to my wisdom, and incline thy ear to my prudence,&#xA;2 That thou mayst keep thoughts, and thy lips may preserve instruction. Mind not the deceit of a woman.&#xA;3 For the lips of a harlot are like a honeycomb dropping, and her throat is smoother than oil.&#xA;4 But her end is bitter as wormwood, and sharp as a two-edged sword.&#xA;5 Her feet go down into death, and her steps go in as far as hell.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 6</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/49-proverbs/chap006/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:40 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/49-proverbs/chap006/</guid>
      <description>1 My son, if thou be surety for thy friend, thou hast engaged fast thy hand to a stranger,&#xA;2 Thou art ensnared with the words of thy mouth, and caught with thy own words.&#xA;3 Do, therefore, my son, what I say, and deliver thyself: because thou art fallen into the hand of thy neighbour. Run about, make haste, stir up thy friend:&#xA;4 Give not sleep to thy eyes, neither let thy eyelids slumber.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 7</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/49-proverbs/chap007/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:40 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/49-proverbs/chap007/</guid>
      <description>1 My son, keep my words, and lay up my precepts with thee. Son,&#xA;2 Keep my commandments, and thou shalt live: and my law as the apple of thy eye:&#xA;3 Bind it upon thy fingers, write it upon the tables of thy heart.&#xA;4 Say to wisdom: Thou art my sister: and call prudence thy friend,&#xA;5 That she may keep thee from the woman that is not thine, and from the stranger who sweeteneth her words.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 8</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/49-proverbs/chap008/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:40 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/49-proverbs/chap008/</guid>
      <description>1 Doth not wisdom cry aloud, and prudence put forth her voice?&#xA;2 Standing in the top of the highest places by the way, in the midst of the paths,&#xA;3 Beside the gates of the city, in the very doors she speaketh, saying:&#xA;4 O ye men, to you I call, and my voice is to the sons of men.&#xA;5 O little ones understand subtlety, and ye unwise, take notice.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 9</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/49-proverbs/chap009/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:40 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/49-proverbs/chap009/</guid>
      <description>1 Wisdom hath built herself a house, she hath hewn her out seven pillars.&#xA;2 She hath slain her victims, mingled her wine, and set forth her table.&#xA;3 She hath sent her maids to invite to the tower, and to the walls of the city:&#xA;4 Whosoever is a little one, let him come to me. And to the unwise she said:&#xA;5 Come, eat my bread, and drink the wine which I have mingled for you.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
