<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Joshua on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</title>
    <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/33-joshua/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Joshua on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:27 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/33-joshua/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 1</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/33-joshua/chap001/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:27 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/33-joshua/chap001/</guid>
      <description>1 Now it came to pass after the death of Moses, the servant of the Lord, that the Lord spoke to Joshua, the son of Nun, the minister of Moses, and said to him:&#xA;2 Moses my servant is dead: arise, and pass over this Jordan, thou and thy people with thee, into the land which I will give to the children of Israel.&#xA;3 I will deliver to you every place that the sole of your foot shall tread upon, as I have said to Moses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 10</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/33-joshua/chap010/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:27 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/33-joshua/chap010/</guid>
      <description>1 When Adonisedec, king of Jerusalem, had heard these things, to wit, that Joshua had taken Hai, and had destroyed it, (for as he had done to Jericho and the king thereof, so did he to Hai and its king) and that the Gabaonites were gone over to Israel, and were their confederates,&#xA;2 He was exceedingly afraid. For Gabaon was a great city, and one of the royal cities, and greater than the town of Hai, and all its fighting men were most valiant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 11</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/33-joshua/chap011/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:27 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/33-joshua/chap011/</guid>
      <description>1 And when Jabin king of Asor had heard these things, he sent to Jobab king of Madon, and to the king of Semeron, and to the king of Achsaph:&#xA;2 And to the kings of the north, that dwelt in the mountains and in the plains over against the south side of Ceneroth, and in the levels and the countries of Dor by the sea side:&#xA;3 To the Chanaanites also on the east and on the west, and the Amorrhite, and the Hethite, and the Pherezite, and the Jebusite in the mountains: to the Hevite also who dwelt at the foot of Hermon in the land of Maspha.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 12</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/33-joshua/chap012/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:27 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/33-joshua/chap012/</guid>
      <description>1 These are the kings, whom the children of Israel slew and possessed their land beyond the Jordan towards the rising of the sun, from the torrent Arnon unto mount Hermon, and all the east country that looketh towards the wilderness.&#xA;2 Sehon king of the Amorrhites, who dwelt in Hesebon, and had dominion from Aroer, which is seated upon the bank of the torrent Arnon, and of the middle part in the valley, and of half Galaad, as far as the torrent Jaboc, which is the border of the children of Ammon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 13</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/33-joshua/chap013/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:27 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/33-joshua/chap013/</guid>
      <description>1 Joshua was old, and far advanced in years, and the Lord said to him: Thou art grown old, and advanced in age, and there is a very large country left, which is not yet divided by lot:&#xA;2 To wit, all Galilee, Philistia, and all Gessuri.&#xA;3 From the troubled river, that watereth Egypt, unto the border of Accaron northward: the land of Chanaan, which is divided among the lords of the Philistines, the Gazites, the Azotians, the Ascalonites, the Gethites, and the Accronites.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 14</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/33-joshua/chap014/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:27 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/33-joshua/chap014/</guid>
      <description>1 This is what the children of Israel possessed in the land of Chanaan, which Eleazar the priest, and Joshua the son of Nun, and the princes of the families by the tribes of Israel gave to them.&#xA;2 Dividing all by lot, as the Lord had commanded the hand of Moses, to the nine tribes, and the half tribe.&#xA;3 For to two tribes and a half Moses had given possession beyond the Jordan: besides the Levites, who received no land among their brethren:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 15</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/33-joshua/chap015/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:27 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/33-joshua/chap015/</guid>
      <description>1 Now the lot of the children of Juda by their kindreds was this: From the frontier of Edom, to the desert of Sin southward, and to the uttermost part of the south coast.&#xA;2 Its beginning was from the top of the most salt sea, and from the bay thereof, that looketh to the south.&#xA;3 And it goeth out towards the ascent of the Scorpion, and passeth on to Sina: and ascendeth into Cadesbarne, and reacheth into Esron, going up to Addar, and compassing Carcaa.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 16</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/33-joshua/chap016/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:27 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/33-joshua/chap016/</guid>
      <description>1 And the lot of the sons of Joseph fell from the Jordan over against Jericho and the waters thereof, on the east: the wilderness which goeth up from Jericho to the mountain of Bethel:&#xA;2 And goeth out from Bethel to Luza: and passeth the border of Archi, to Ataroth,&#xA;3 And goeth down westward, by the border of Jephleti, unto the borders of Beth-horon the nether, and to Gazer: and the countries of it are ended by the great sea:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 17</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/33-joshua/chap017/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:27 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/33-joshua/chap017/</guid>
      <description>1 And this lot fell to the tribe of Manasses for he is the firstborn of Joseph to Machir the firstborn of Manasses the father of Galaad, who was a warlike man, and had for possession Galaad and Basan.&#xA;2 And to the rest of the children of Manasses according to their families: to the children of Abiezer, and to the children of Helec, and to the children of Esriel, and to the children of Sechem, and to the children of Hepher, and to the children of Semida: these are the male children of Manasses the son of Joseph, by their kindreds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 18</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/33-joshua/chap018/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:27 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/33-joshua/chap018/</guid>
      <description>1 And all the children of Israel assembled together in Silo, and there they set up the tabernacle of the testimony, and the land was subdued before them.&#xA;2 But there remained seven tribes of the children of Israel, which as yet had not received their possessions.&#xA;3 And Joshua said to them: How long are you indolent and slack, and go not in to possess the land which the Lord the God of your fathers hath given you?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 19</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/33-joshua/chap019/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:27 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/33-joshua/chap019/</guid>
      <description>1 And the second lot came forth for the children of Simeon by their kindreds: and their inheritance was&#xA;2 In the midst of the possession of the children of Juda: Bersabee and Sabee and Molada&#xA;3 And Hasersual, Bala and Asem,&#xA;4 And Eltholad, Bethul and Harma,&#xA;5 And Siceleg and Bethmarchaboth and Hasersusa,&#xA;6 And Bethlebaoth and Sarohen: thirteen cities, and their villages.&#xA;7 And Remmon and Athor and Asan: four cities, and their villages.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 2</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/33-joshua/chap002/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:27 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/33-joshua/chap002/</guid>
      <description>1 And Joshua, the son of Nun, sent from Setim two men, to spy secretly: and said to them: Go, and view the land, and the city of Jericho. They went, and entered into the house of a woman that was a harlot, named Rahab, and lodged with her.&#xA;2 And it was told the king of Jericho, and was said: Behold there are men come in hither, by night, of the children of Israel, to spy the land.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 20</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/33-joshua/chap020/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:27 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/33-joshua/chap020/</guid>
      <description>1 And the Lord spoke to Joshua, saying: Speak to children of Israel and say to them:&#xA;2 Appoint cities of refuge, of which I spoke to you by the hand of Moses:&#xA;3 That whosoever shall kill a person unawares may flee to them, and may escape the wrath of the kinsman, who is the avenger of blood.&#xA;4 And when he shall flee to one of these cities: he shall stand before the gate of the city, and shall speak to the ancients of that city, such things as prove him innocent: and so shall they receive him, and give him a place to dwell in.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 21</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/33-joshua/chap021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:27 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/33-joshua/chap021/</guid>
      <description>1 Then the princes of the families of Levi came to Eleazar the priest, and to Joshua the son of Nun, and to the princes of the kindreds of all the tribes of the children of Israel&#xA;2 And they spoke to them in Silo in the land of Chanaan, and said: The Lord commanded by the hand of Moses, that cities should be given us to dwell in, and their suburbs to feed our cattle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 22</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/33-joshua/chap022/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:27 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/33-joshua/chap022/</guid>
      <description>1 At the same time Joshua called the Rubenites, and the Gadites, and the half tribe of Manasses,&#xA;2 And said to them: You have done all that Moses the servant of the Lord commanded you: you have also obeyed me in all things,&#xA;3 Neither have you left your brethren this long time, until this present day, keeping the commandment of the Lord your God.&#xA;4 Therefore as the Lord your God hath given your brethren rest and peace, as he promised: return, and go to your dwellings, and to the land of your possession, which Moses the servant of the Lord gave you beyond the Jordan:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 23</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/33-joshua/chap023/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:27 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/33-joshua/chap023/</guid>
      <description>1 And when a long time was passed, after that the Lord had given peace to Israel, all the nations round about being subdued. and Joshua being now old, and far advanced in years:&#xA;2 Joshua called for all Israel, and for the elders, and for the princes, and for the judges, and for the masters, and said to them: I am old, and far advanced in years,&#xA;3 And you see all that the Lord your God hath done to all the nations round about, how he himself hath fought for you:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 24</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/33-joshua/chap024/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:27 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/33-joshua/chap024/</guid>
      <description>1 And Joshua gathered together all the tribes of Israel in Sichem, and called for the ancients, and the princes and the judges, and the masters: and they stood in the sight of the Lord:&#xA;2 And he spoke thus to the people: Thus saith the Lord the God of Israel: Your fathers dwelt of old on the other side of the river, Thare the father of Abraham, and Nachor: and they served strange gods.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 3</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/33-joshua/chap003/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:27 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/33-joshua/chap003/</guid>
      <description>1 And Joshua rose before daylight, and removed the camp: and they departed from Setim, and came to the Jordan: he, and all the children of Israel, and they abode there for three days.&#xA;2 After which, the heralds went through the midst of the camp,&#xA;3 And began to proclaim: When you shall see the ark of the covenant of the Lord your God, and the priests of the race of Levi carrying it, rise you up also, and follow them as they go before:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 4</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/33-joshua/chap004/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:27 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/33-joshua/chap004/</guid>
      <description>1 And when they were passed over, the Lord said to Joshua:&#xA;2 Choose twelve men, one of every tribe:&#xA;3 And command them to take out of the midst of the Jordan, where the feet of the priests stood, twelve very hard stones, which you shall set in the place of the camp, where you shall pitch your tents this night.&#xA;4 And Joshua called twelve men, whom he had chosen out of the children of Israel, one out of every tribe,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 5</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/33-joshua/chap005/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:27 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/33-joshua/chap005/</guid>
      <description>1 Now when all the kings of the Amorrhites, who dwelt beyond the Jordan, westward, and all the kings of Chanaan, who possessed the places near the great sea, had heard that the Lord had dried up the waters of the Jordan before the children of Israel, till they passed over, their heart failed them, and there remained no spirit in them, fearing the coming in of the children of Israel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 6</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/33-joshua/chap006/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:27 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/33-joshua/chap006/</guid>
      <description>1 Now Jericho was close shut up and fenced, for fear of the children of Israel, and no man durst go out or come in.&#xA;2 And the Lord said to Joshua: Behold I have given into thy hands Jericho, and the king thereof, and all the valiant men.&#xA;3 Go round about the city all ye fighting men once a day: so shall ye do for six days.&#xA;4 And on the seventh day the priests shall take the seven trumpets, which are used in the jubilee, and shall go before the ark of the covenant: and you shall go about the city seven times, and the priests shall sound the trumpets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 7</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/33-joshua/chap007/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:27 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/33-joshua/chap007/</guid>
      <description>1 But the children of Israel transgressed the commandment, and took to their own use of that which was accursed. For Achan, the son of Charmi, the son of Zabdi, the son of Zare, of the tribe of Juda, took something of the anathema: and the Lord was angry against the children of Israel.&#xA;2 And when Joshua sent men from Jericho against Hai, which is beside Bethaven, on the east side of the town of Bethel, he said to them: Go up, and view the country: and they fulfilled his command, and viewed Hai.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 8</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/33-joshua/chap008/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:27 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/33-joshua/chap008/</guid>
      <description>1 And the Lord said to Joshua: Fear not, nor be thou dismayed: take with thee all the multitude of fighting men, arise, and go up to the town of Hai: Behold I have delivered into thy hand the king thereof, and the people, and the city, and the land.&#xA;2 And thou shalt do to the city of Hai, and to the king thereof, as thou hast done to Jericho, and to the king thereof: but the spoils, and all the cattle, you shall take for a prey to yourselves: lay an ambush for the city behind it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 9</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/33-joshua/chap009/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:27 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41727/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/33-joshua/chap009/</guid>
      <description>1 Now when these things were heard of, all the kings beyond the Jordan, that dwelt in the mountains, and in the plains, in the places near the sea, and on the coasts of the great sea, they also that dwell by Libanus, the Hethite, and the Amorrhite, the Chanaanite, the Pherezite, and the Hevite, and the Jebusite,&#xA;2 Gathered themselves together, to fight against Joshua and Israel with one mind, and one resolution.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
