<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hebrews on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</title>
    <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/19-hebrews/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Hebrews on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:25 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/19-hebrews/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 1</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/19-hebrews/chap001/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:25 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/19-hebrews/chap001/</guid>
      <description>1 God, who, at sundry times and in divers manners, spoke in times past to the fathers by the prophets, last of all,&#xA;2 In these days, hath spoken to us by his Son, whom he hath appointed heir of all things, by whom also he made the world.&#xA;3 Who being the brightness of his glory and the figure of his substance and upholding all things by the word of his power, making purgation of sins, sitteth on the right hand of the majesty on high:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 10</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/19-hebrews/chap010/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:25 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/19-hebrews/chap010/</guid>
      <description>1 For the law, having a shadow of the good things to come, not the very image of the things, by the selfsame sacrifices which they offer continually every year, can never make the comers thereunto perfect.&#xA;2 For then they would have ceased to be offered: because the worshippers once cleansed should have no conscience of sin any longer.&#xA;3 But in them there is made a commemoration of sins every year:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 11</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/19-hebrews/chap011/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:25 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/19-hebrews/chap011/</guid>
      <description>1 Now, faith is the substance of things to be hoped for, the evidence of things that appear not.&#xA;2 For by this the ancients obtained a testimony.&#xA;3 By faith we understand that the world was framed by the word of God: that from invisible things visible things might be made.&#xA;4 By faith Abel offered to God a sacrifice exceeding that of Cain, by which he obtained a testimony that he was just, God giving testimony to his gifts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 12</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/19-hebrews/chap012/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:25 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/19-hebrews/chap012/</guid>
      <description>1 And therefore we also having so great a cloud of witnesses over our head, laying aside every weight and sin which surrounds us, let us run by patience to the fight proposed to us:&#xA;2 Looking on Jesus, the author and finisher of faith, who, having joy set before him, endured the cross, despising the shame, and now sitteth on the right hand of the throne of God.&#xA;3 For think diligently upon him that endured such opposition from sinners against himself that you be not wearied, fainting in your minds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 13</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/19-hebrews/chap013/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:25 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/19-hebrews/chap013/</guid>
      <description>1 Let the charity of the brotherhood abide in you.&#xA;2 And hospitality do not forget: for by this some, being not aware of it, have entertained angels.&#xA;3 Remember them that are in bands, as if you were bound with them: and them that labour, as being yourselves also in the body.&#xA;4 Marriage honourable in all, and the bed undefiled. For fornicators and adulterers God will judge.&#xA;5 Let your manners be without covetousness, contented with such things as you have.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 2</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/19-hebrews/chap002/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:25 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/19-hebrews/chap002/</guid>
      <description>1 Therefore ought we more diligently to observe the things which we have heard lest perhaps we should let them slip.&#xA;2 For if the word spoken by angels became steadfast and every transgression and disobedience received a just recompense of reward:&#xA;3 How shall we escape if we neglect so great salvation? Which, having begun to be declared by the Lord, was confirmed unto us by them that heard him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 3</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/19-hebrews/chap003/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:25 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/19-hebrews/chap003/</guid>
      <description>1 Wherefore, holy brethren, partakers of the heavenly vocation consider the apostle and high priest of our confession, Jesus:&#xA;2 Who is faithful to him that made him, as was also Moses in all his house.&#xA;3 For this man was counted worthy of greater glory than Moses, by so much as he that hath built the house hath greater honour than the house.&#xA;4 For every house is built by some man: but he that created all things is God.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 4</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/19-hebrews/chap004/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:25 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/19-hebrews/chap004/</guid>
      <description>1 Let us fear therefore lest, the promise being left of entering into his rest, any of you should be thought to be wanting.&#xA;2 For unto us also it hath been declared in like manner as unto them. But the word of hearing did not profit them, not being mixed with faith of those things they heard.&#xA;3 For we, who have believed, shall enter into rest; as he said: As I have sworn in my wrath: If they shall enter into my rest; and this indeed when the works from the foundation of the world were finished.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 5</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/19-hebrews/chap005/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:25 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/19-hebrews/chap005/</guid>
      <description>1 For every high priest taken from among men is ordained for men in the things that appertain to God, that he may offer up gifts and sacrifices for sins:&#xA;2 Who can have compassion on them that are ignorant and that err: because he himself also is compassed with infirmity.&#xA;3 And therefore he ought, as for the people, so also for himself, to offer for sins.&#xA;4 Neither doth any man take the honour to himself, but he that is called by God, as Aaron was.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 6</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/19-hebrews/chap006/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:25 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/19-hebrews/chap006/</guid>
      <description>1 Wherefore, leaving the word of the beginning of Christ, let us go on to things more perfect: not laying again the foundation of penance from dead works and of faith towards God,&#xA;2 Of the doctrine of baptisms and imposition of hands, and of the resurrection of the dead, and of eternal judgment.&#xA;3 And this will we do, if God permit.&#xA;4 For it is impossible for those who were once illuminated, have tasted also the heavenly gift and were made partakers of the Holy Ghost,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 7</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/19-hebrews/chap007/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:25 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/19-hebrews/chap007/</guid>
      <description>1 For this Melchisedech was king of Salem, priest of the most high God, who met Abraham returning from the slaughter of the kings and blessed him:&#xA;2 To whom also Abraham divided the tithes of all: who first indeed by interpretation is king of justice: and then also king of Salem, that is, king of peace:&#xA;3 Without father, without mother, without genealogy, having neither beginning of days nor end of life, but likened unto the Son of God, continueth a priest for ever.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 8</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/19-hebrews/chap008/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:25 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/19-hebrews/chap008/</guid>
      <description>1 Now of the things which we have spoken, this is the sum: We have such an high priest who is set on the right hand of the throne of majesty in the heavens,&#xA;2 A minister of the holies and of the true tabernacle, which the Lord hath pitched, and not man.&#xA;3 For every high priest is appointed to offer gifts and sacrifices: wherefore it is necessary that he also should have some thing to offer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 9</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/19-hebrews/chap009/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:25 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/19-hebrews/chap009/</guid>
      <description>1 The former indeed had also justifications of divine service and a sanctuary.&#xA;2 For there was a tabernacle made the first, wherein were the candlesticks and the table and the setting forth of loaves, which is called the Holy.&#xA;3 And after the second veil, the tabernacle which is called the Holy of Holies:&#xA;4 Having a golden censer and the ark of the testament covered about on every part with gold, in which was a golden pot that had manna and the rod of Aaron that had blossomed and the tables of the testament.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
