<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Joel on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/61-joel/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Joel on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/61-joel/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 1</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/61-joel/chap001/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/61-joel/chap001/</guid>
      <description>1 The word of the Lord, that came to Joel, the son of Phatuel.&#xA;2 Hear this, ye old men, and give ear, all ye inhabitants of the land: did this ever happen in your days, or in the days of your fathers?&#xA;3 Tell ye of this to your children, and let your children tell their children, and their children to another generation.&#xA;4 That which the palmerworm hath left, the locust hath eaten: and that which the locust hath left, the bruchus hath eaten: and that which the bruchus hath left, the mildew hath destroyed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 2</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/61-joel/chap002/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/61-joel/chap002/</guid>
      <description>1 Blow ye the trumpet in Sion, sound an alarm in my holy mountain, let all the inhabitants of the land tremble: because the day of the Lord cometh, because it is nigh at hand.&#xA;2 A day of darkness, and of gloominess, a day of clouds and whirlwinds: a numerous and strong people as the morning spread upon the mountains: the like to it hath not been from the beginning, nor shall be after it, even to the years of generation and generation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 3</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/61-joel/chap003/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/61-joel/chap003/</guid>
      <description>1 For behold in those days, and in that time when I shall bring back the captivity of Juda, and Jerusalem:&#xA;2 I will gather together all nations and will bring them down into the valley of Josaphat: and I will plead with them there for my people, and for my inheritance, Israel, whom they have scattered among the nations, and have parted my land.&#xA;3 And they have cast lots upon my people: and the boy they have put in the stews, and the girl they have sold for wine, that they might drink.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
