<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Philippians on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</title>
    <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/11-philippians/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Philippians on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:24 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/11-philippians/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 1</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/11-philippians/chap001/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:24 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/11-philippians/chap001/</guid>
      <description>1 Paul and Timothy, the servants of Jesus Christ: to all the saints in Christ Jesus who are at Philippi, with the bishops and deacons.&#xA;2 Grace be unto you and peace, from God our Father and from the Lord Jesus Christ.&#xA;3 I give thanks to my God in every remembrance of you:&#xA;4 Always in all my prayers making supplication for you all with joy:&#xA;5 For your communication in the gospel of Christ, from the first day unto now.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 2</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/11-philippians/chap002/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:24 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/11-philippians/chap002/</guid>
      <description>1 If there be therefore any consolation in Christ, if any comfort of charity, if any society of the spirit, if any bowels of commiseration:&#xA;2 Fulfil ye my joy, that you be of one mind, having the same charity, being of one accord, agreeing in sentiment.&#xA;3 Let nothing be done through contention: neither by vain glory. But in humility, let each esteem others better than themselves:&#xA;4 Each one not considering the things that are his own, but those that are other men&amp;rsquo;s.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 3</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/11-philippians/chap003/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:24 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/11-philippians/chap003/</guid>
      <description>1 As to the rest, my brethren, rejoice in the Lord. To write the same things to you, to me indeed is not wearisome, but to you is necessary.&#xA;2 Beware of dogs: beware of evil workers: beware of the concision.&#xA;3 For we are the circumcision, who in spirit serve God and glory in Christ Jesus, not having confidence in the flesh.&#xA;4 Though I might also have confidence in the flesh.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 4</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/11-philippians/chap004/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:24 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/11-philippians/chap004/</guid>
      <description>1 Therefore my dearly beloved brethren and most desired, my joy and my crown: so stand fast in the Lord, my dearly beloved.&#xA;2 I beg of Evodia and I beseech Syntyche to be of one mind in the Lord.&#xA;3 And I entreat thee also, my sincere companion, help those women who have laboured with me in the gospel, with Clement and the rest of my fellow labourers, whose names are in the book of life.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
