<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Esther on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</title>
    <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/46-esther/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Esther on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/46-esther/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 1</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/46-esther/chap001/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/46-esther/chap001/</guid>
      <description>1 In the days of Assuerus, who reigned from India to Ethiopia over a hundred and twenty seven provinces:&#xA;2 When he sat on the throne of his kingdom, the city Susan was the capital of his kingdom.&#xA;3 Now in the third year of his reign he made a great feast for all the princes, and for his servants, for the most mighty of the Persians, and the nobles of the Medes, and the governors of the provinces in his sight,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 10</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/46-esther/chap010/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/46-esther/chap010/</guid>
      <description>1 And king Assuerus made all the land, and all the islands of the sea tributary.&#xA;2 And his strength and his empire, and the dignity and greatness wherewith he exalted Mardochai, are written in the books of the Medes, and of the Persians:&#xA;3 And how Mardochai of the race of the Jews, was next after king Assuerus: and great among the Jews, and acceptable to the people of his brethren, seeking the good of his people, and speaking those things which were for the welfare of his seed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 11</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/46-esther/chap011/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/46-esther/chap011/</guid>
      <description>1 In the fourth year of the reign of Ptolemy and Cleopatra, Dositheus, who said he was a priest, and of the Levitical race, and Ptolemy his son brought this epistle of Phurim, which they said Lysimachus the son of Ptolemy had interpreted in Jerusalem.&#xA;2 In the second year of the reign of Artaxerxes the great, in the first day of the month Nisan, Mardochai the son of Jair, the son of Semei, the son of Cis, of the tribe of Benjamin:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 12</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/46-esther/chap012/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/46-esther/chap012/</guid>
      <description>1 And he abode at that time in the king&amp;rsquo;s court with Bagatha and Thara the king&amp;rsquo;s eunuchs, who were porters of the palace.&#xA;2 And when he understood their designs, and had diligently searched into their projects, he learned that they went about to lay violent hands on king Artaxerxes, and he told the king thereof.&#xA;3 Then the king had them both examined, and after they had confessed, commanded them to be put to death.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 13</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/46-esther/chap013/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/46-esther/chap013/</guid>
      <description>1 And this was the copy of the letter: Artaxerxes the great king who reigneth from India to Ethiopia, to the princes and governors of the hundred and twenty-seven provinces, that are subject to his empire, greeting.&#xA;2 Whereas I reigned over many nations, and had brought all the world under my dominion, I was not willing to abuse the greatness of my power, but to govern my subjects with clemency and that they might live quietly without any terror, and might enjoy peace, which is desired by all men,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 14</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/46-esther/chap014/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/46-esther/chap014/</guid>
      <description>1 Queen Esther also, fearing the danger that was at hand, had recourse to the Lord.&#xA;2 And when she had laid away her royal apparel, she put on garments suitable for weeping and mourning: instead of divers precious ointments, she covered her head with ashes and dung, and she humbled her body with fasts: and all the places in which before she was accustomed to rejoice, she filled with her torn hair.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 15</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/46-esther/chap015/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/46-esther/chap015/</guid>
      <description>1 And he commanded her (no doubt but he was Mardochai) to go to the king, and petition for her people, and for her country.&#xA;2 Remember, (said he,) the days of thy low estate, how thou wast brought up by my hand, because Aman the second after the king hath spoken against us unto death.&#xA;3 And do thou call upon the Lord, and speak to the king for us, and deliver us from death.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 16</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/46-esther/chap016/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/46-esther/chap016/</guid>
      <description>1 The great king Artaxerxes, from India to Ethiopia, to the governors and princes of a hundred and twenty-seven provinces, which obey our command, sendeth greeting.&#xA;2 Many have abused unto pride the goodness of princes, and the honour that hath been bestowed upon them:&#xA;3 And not only endeavour to oppress the king&amp;rsquo;s subjects, but not bearing the glory that is given them, take in hand, to practise also against them that gave it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 2</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/46-esther/chap002/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/46-esther/chap002/</guid>
      <description>1 After this, when the wrath of king Assuerus was appeased, he remembered Vasthi, and what she had done and what she had suffered:&#xA;2 And the king&amp;rsquo;s servants and his officers said: Let young women be sought for the king, virgins and beautiful,&#xA;3 And let some persons be sent through all the provinces to look for beautiful maidens and virgins: and let them bring them to the city of Susan, and put them into the house of the women under the hand of Egeus the eunuch, who is the overseer and keeper of the king&amp;rsquo;s women: and let them receive women&amp;rsquo;s ornaments, and other things necessary for their use.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 3</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/46-esther/chap003/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/46-esther/chap003/</guid>
      <description>1 After these things, king Assuerus advanced Aman, the son of Amadathi, who was of the race of Agag: and he set his throne above all the princes that were with him.&#xA;2 And all the king&amp;rsquo;s servants, that were at the doors of the palace, bent their knees, and worshipped Aman: for so the emperor had commanded them, only Mardochai did not bend his knee, nor worship him.&#xA;3 And the king&amp;rsquo;s servants that were chief at the doors of the palace, said to him: Why dost thou alone not observe the king&amp;rsquo;s commandment?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 4</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/46-esther/chap004/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/46-esther/chap004/</guid>
      <description>1 Now when Mardochai had heard these things, he rent his garments, and put on sackcloth, strewing ashes on his head and he cried with a loud voice in the street in the midst of the city, shewing the anguish of his mind.&#xA;2 And he came lamenting in this manner even to the gate of the palace: for no one clothed with sackcloth might enter the king&amp;rsquo;s court.&#xA;3 And in all provinces, towns, and places, to which the king&amp;rsquo;s cruel edict was come, there was great mourning among the Jews, with fasting, wailing, and weeping, many using sackcloth and ashes for their bed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 5</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/46-esther/chap005/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/46-esther/chap005/</guid>
      <description>1 And on the third day Esther put on her royal apparel, and stood in the inner court of the king&amp;rsquo;s house, over against the king&amp;rsquo;s hall: now he sat upon his throne in the hall of the palace, over against the door of the house.&#xA;2 And when he saw Esther the queen standing, she pleased his eyes, and he held out toward her the golden sceptre, which he held in his hand and she drew near, and kissed the top of his sceptre.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 6</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/46-esther/chap006/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/46-esther/chap006/</guid>
      <description>1 That night the king passed without sleep, and he commanded the histories and chronicles of former times to be brought him. And when they were reading them before him,&#xA;2 They came to that place where it was written, how Mardochai had discovered the treason of Bagathan and Thares the eunuchs, who sought to kill king Assuerus.&#xA;3 And when the king heard this, he said: What honour and reward hath Mardochai received for this fidelity?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 7</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/46-esther/chap007/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/46-esther/chap007/</guid>
      <description>1 So the king and Aman went in, to drink with the queen.&#xA;2 And the king said to her again the second day, after he was warm with wine: What is thy petition, Esther, that it may be granted thee? and what wilt thou have done: although thou ask the half of my kingdom, thou shalt have it.&#xA;3 Then she answered: If I have found favour in thy sight, O king, and if it please thee, give me my life for which I ask, and my people for which I request.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 8</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/46-esther/chap008/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/46-esther/chap008/</guid>
      <description>1 On that day king Assuerus gave the house of Aman, the Jews&amp;rsquo; enemy, to queen Esther, and Mardochai came in before the king. For Esther had confessed to him that he was her uncle.&#xA;2 And the king took the ring which he had commanded to be taken again from Aman, and gave it to Mardochai. And Esther set Mardochai over her house.&#xA;3 And not content with these things, she fell down at the king&amp;rsquo;s feet and wept, and speaking to him besought him, that he would give orders that the malice of Aman the Agagite, and his most wicked devices which he had invented against the Jews, should be of no effect.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 9</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/46-esther/chap009/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/46-esther/chap009/</guid>
      <description>1 So on the thirteenth day of the twelfth month, which as we have said above is called Adar, when all the Jews were designed to be massacred, and their enemies were greedy after their blood, the case being altered, the Jews began to have the upper hand, and to revenge themselves of their adversaries.&#xA;2 And they gathered themselves together in every city, and town, and place, to lay their hands on their enemies, and their persecutors.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
