<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2 Maccabees on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/73-2-maccabees/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2 Maccabees on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:34 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/73-2-maccabees/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 1</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/73-2-maccabees/chap001/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:34 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/73-2-maccabees/chap001/</guid>
      <description>1 To the brethren, the Jews that are throughout Egypt; the brethren, the Jews that are in Jerusalem, and in the land of Judea, send health and good peace.&#xA;2 May God be gracious to you, and remember his covenant that he made with Abraham, and Isaac, and Jacob, his faithful servants:&#xA;3 And give you all a heart to worship him, and to do his will with a great heart, and a willing mind.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 10</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/73-2-maccabees/chap010/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:34 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/73-2-maccabees/chap010/</guid>
      <description>1 But Machabeus, and they that were with him, by the protection of the Lord, recovered the temple and the city again.&#xA;2 But he threw down the altars which the heathens had set up in the streets, as also the temples of the idols.&#xA;3 And having purified the temple, they made another altar: and taking fire out of the fiery stones, they offered sacrifices after two years, and set forth incense, and lamps, and the loaves of proposition.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 11</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/73-2-maccabees/chap011/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:34 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/73-2-maccabees/chap011/</guid>
      <description>1 A short time after this Lysias, the king&amp;rsquo;s lieutenant, and cousin, and who had chief charge over all the affairs, being greatly displeased with what had happened,&#xA;2 Gathered together fourscore thousand men, and all the horsemen, and came against the Jews, thinking to take the city, and make it a habitation of the Gentiles:&#xA;3 And to make a gain of the temple, as of the other temples of the Gentiles and to set the high priesthood to sale every year:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 12</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/73-2-maccabees/chap012/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:34 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/73-2-maccabees/chap012/</guid>
      <description>1 When these covenants were made, Lysias went to the king, and the Jews gave themselves to husbandry.&#xA;2 But they that were behind, viz. Timotheus, and Apollonius, the son of Genneus, also Hieronymus, and Demophon, and besides them Nicanor, the governor of Cyprus, would not suffer them to live in peace, and to be quiet.&#xA;3 The men of Joppe also were guilty of this kind of wickedness: they desired the Jews, who dwelt among them, to go with their wives and children into the boats, which they had prepared, as though they had no enmity to them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 13</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/73-2-maccabees/chap013/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:34 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/73-2-maccabees/chap013/</guid>
      <description>1 In the year one hundred and forty-nine, Judas understood that Antiochus Eupator was coming with a multitude against Judea,&#xA;2 And with him Lysias, the regent, who had charge over the affairs of the realm, having with him a hundred and ten thousand footmen, five thousand horsemen, twenty-two elephants, and three hundred chariots.&#xA;3 Menelaus also joined himself with them: and with great deceitfulness besought Antiochus, not for the welfare of his country, but in hopes that he should be appointed chief ruler.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 14</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/73-2-maccabees/chap014/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:34 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/73-2-maccabees/chap014/</guid>
      <description>1 But after the space of three years Judas, and they that were with him, understood that Demetrius, the son of Seleucus, was come up with a great power, and a navy by the haven of Tripolis, to places proper for his purpose,&#xA;2 And had made himself master of the countries against Antiochus, and his general, Lysias.&#xA;3 Now one Alcimus, who had been chief priest, but had wilfully defiled himself in the time of mingling with the heathens, seeing that there was no safety for him, nor access to the altar,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 15</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/73-2-maccabees/chap015/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:34 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/73-2-maccabees/chap015/</guid>
      <description>1 But when Nicanor understood that Judas was in the places of Samaria, he purposed to set upon him with all violence, on the sabbath day.&#xA;2 And when the Jews that were constrained to follow him, said: Do not act so fiercely and barbarously, but give honour to the day that is sanctified: and reverence him that beholdeth all things:&#xA;3 That unhappy man asked, if there were a mighty One in heaven, that had commanded the sabbath day to be kept.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 2</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/73-2-maccabees/chap002/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:34 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/73-2-maccabees/chap002/</guid>
      <description>1Now it is found in the descriptions of Jeremias, the prophet, that he commanded them that went into captivity, to take the fire, as it hath been signified, and how he gave charge to them that were carried away into captivity.&#xA;2 And how he gave them the law, that they should not forget the commandments of the Lord, and that they should not err in their minds, seeing the idols of gold, and silver, and the ornaments of them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 3</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/73-2-maccabees/chap003/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:34 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/73-2-maccabees/chap003/</guid>
      <description>1 Therefore, when the holy city was inhabited with all peace, and the laws as yet were very well kept, because of the godliness of Onias, the high priest and the hatred his soul had of evil,&#xA;2 It came to pass that even the kings themselves and the princes esteemed the place worthy of the highest honour, and glorified the temple with very great gifts:&#xA;3 So that Seleucus, king of Asia, allowed out of his revenues all the charges belonging to the ministry of the sacrifices.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 4</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/73-2-maccabees/chap004/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:34 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/73-2-maccabees/chap004/</guid>
      <description>1 But Simon, of whom we spoke before, who was the betrayer of the money, and of his country, spoke ill of Onias, as though he had incited Heliodorus to do these things, and had been the promoter of evils:&#xA;2 And he presumed to call him a traitor to the kingdom, who provided for the city, and defended his nation, and was zealous for the law of God.&#xA;3 But when the enmities proceeded so far, that murders also were committed by some of Simon&amp;rsquo;s friends:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 5</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/73-2-maccabees/chap005/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:34 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/73-2-maccabees/chap005/</guid>
      <description>1 At the same time Antiochus prepared for a second journey into Egypt.&#xA;2 And it came to pass, that through the whole city of Jerusalem, for the space of forty days, there were seen horsemen running in the air, in gilded raiment, and armed with spears, like bands of soldiers.&#xA;3 And horses set in order by ranks, running one against another, with the shakings of shields, and a multitude of men in helmets, with drawn swords, and casting of darts, and glittering of golden armour, and of harnesses of all sorts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 6</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/73-2-maccabees/chap006/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:34 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/73-2-maccabees/chap006/</guid>
      <description>1 But not long after the king sent a certain old man of Antioch, to compel the Jews to depart from the laws of their fathers and of God:&#xA;2 And to defile the temple that was in Jerusalem, and to call it the temple of Jupiter Olympius: and that in Garazim of Jupiter Hospitalis, according as they were that inhabited the place.&#xA;3 And very bad was this invasion of evils, and grievous to all.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 7</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/73-2-maccabees/chap007/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:34 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/73-2-maccabees/chap007/</guid>
      <description>1 It came to pass also, that seven brethren, together with their mother, were apprehended, and compelled by the king to eat swine&amp;rsquo;s flesh against the law, for which end they were tormented with whips and scourges.&#xA;2 But one of them, who was the eldest, said thus: What wouldst thou ask, or learn of us? we are ready to die, rather than to transgress the laws of God, received from our fathers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 8</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/73-2-maccabees/chap008/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:34 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/73-2-maccabees/chap008/</guid>
      <description>1 But Judas Machabeus, and they that were with him, went privately into the towns: and calling together their kinsmen and friends, and taking unto them such as continued in the Jews&amp;rsquo; religion, they assembled six thousand men.&#xA;2 And they called upon the Lord, that he would look upon his people that was trodden down by all and would have pity on the temple, that was defiled by the wicked:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 9</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/73-2-maccabees/chap009/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:34 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/73-2-maccabees/chap009/</guid>
      <description>1 At that time Antiochus returned with dishonour out of Persia.&#xA;2 For he had entered into the city called Persepolis, and attempted to rob the temple, and to oppress the city, but the multitude running together to arms, put them to flight: and so it fell out that Antiochus being put to flight, returned with disgrace.&#xA;3 Now when he was come about Ecbatana, he received the news of what had happened to Nicanor and Timotheus.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
