<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Matthew on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</title>
    <link>http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/01-matthew/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Matthew on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:23 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/01-matthew/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 1</title>
      <link>http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/01-matthew/chap001/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:23 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/01-matthew/chap001/</guid>
      <description>1 The book of the generation of Jesus Christ, the son of David, the son of Abraham:&#xA;2 Abraham begot Isaac. And Isaac begot Jacob. And Jacob begot Judas and his brethren.&#xA;3 And Judas begot Phares and Zara of Thamar. And Phares begot Esron. And Esron begot Aram.&#xA;4 And Aram begot Aminadab. And Aminadab begot Naasson. And Naasson begot Salmon.&#xA;5 And Salmon begot Booz of Rahab. And Booz begot Obed of Ruth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 10</title>
      <link>http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/01-matthew/chap010/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:23 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/01-matthew/chap010/</guid>
      <description>1 And having called his twelve disciples together, he gave them power over unclean spirits, to cast them out, and to heal all manner of diseases, and all manner of infirmities.&#xA;2 And the names of the twelve Apostles are these: The first, Simon who is called Peter, and Andrew his brother,&#xA;3 James the son of Zebedee, and John his brother, Philip and Bartholomew, Thomas and Matthew the publican, and James the son of Alpheus, and Thaddeus,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 11</title>
      <link>http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/01-matthew/chap011/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:23 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/01-matthew/chap011/</guid>
      <description>1 And it came to pass, when Jesus had made an end of commanding his twelve disciples, he passed from thence, to teach and to preach in their cities.&#xA;2 Now when John had heard in prison the works of Christ: sending two of his disciples he said to him:&#xA;3 Art thou he that art to come, or look we for another?&#xA;4 And Jesus making answer said to them: Go and relate to John what you have heard and seen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 12</title>
      <link>http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/01-matthew/chap012/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:23 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/01-matthew/chap012/</guid>
      <description>1 At that time Jesus went through the corn on the sabbath: and his disciples being hungry, began to pluck the ears, and to eat.&#xA;2 And the Pharisees seeing them, said to him: Behold thy disciples do that which is not lawful to do on the sabbath days.&#xA;3 But he said to them: Have you not read what David did when he was hungry, and they that were with him:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 13</title>
      <link>http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/01-matthew/chap013/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:23 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/01-matthew/chap013/</guid>
      <description>1 The same day Jesus going out of the house, sat by the sea side.&#xA;2 And great multitudes were gathered together unto him, so that he went up into a boat and sat: and all the multitude stood on the shore.&#xA;3 And he spoke to them many things in parables, saying: Behold the sower went forth to sow.&#xA;4 And whilst he soweth some fell by the way side, and the birds of the air came and ate them up.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 14</title>
      <link>http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/01-matthew/chap014/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:23 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/01-matthew/chap014/</guid>
      <description>1 At that time Herod the Tetrarch heard the fame of Jesus.&#xA;2 And he said to his servants: This is John the Baptist: he is risen from the dead, and therefore mighty works shew forth themselves in him.&#xA;3 For Herod had apprehended John and bound him, and put him into prison, because of Herodias, his brother&amp;rsquo;s wife.&#xA;4 For John said to him: It is not lawful for thee to have her.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 15</title>
      <link>http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/01-matthew/chap015/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:23 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/01-matthew/chap015/</guid>
      <description>1 Then came to him from Jerusalem scribes and Pharisees, saying:&#xA;2 Why do thy disciples transgress the tradition of the ancients? For they wash not their hands when they eat bread.&#xA;3 But he answering, said to them: Why do you also transgress the commandment of God for your tradition? For God said:&#xA;4 Honour thy father and mother: And: He that shall curse father or mother, let him die the death.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 16</title>
      <link>http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/01-matthew/chap016/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:23 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/01-matthew/chap016/</guid>
      <description>1 And there came to him the Pharisees and Sadducees tempting: and they asked him to shew them a sign from heaven.&#xA;2 But he answered and said to them: When it is evening, you say, It will be fair weather, for the sky is red.&#xA;3 And in the morning: To day there will be a storm, for the sky is red and lowering. You know then how to discern the face of the sky: and can you not know the signs of the times?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 17</title>
      <link>http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/01-matthew/chap017/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:23 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/01-matthew/chap017/</guid>
      <description>1 And after six days Jesus taketh unto him Peter and James, and John his brother, and bringeth them up into a high mountain apart:&#xA;2 And he was transfigured before them. And his face did shine as the sun: and his garments became white as snow.&#xA;3 And behold there appeared to them Moses and Elias talking with him.&#xA;4 And Peter answering, said to Jesus: Lord, it is good for us to be here: if thou wilt, let us make here three tabernacles, one for thee, and one for Moses, and one for Elias.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 18</title>
      <link>http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/01-matthew/chap018/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:23 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/01-matthew/chap018/</guid>
      <description>1 At that hour the disciples came to Jesus, saying: Who, thinkest thou, is the greater in the kingdom of heaven?&#xA;2 And Jesus, calling unto him a little child, set him in the midst of them.&#xA;3 And said: amen I say to you, unless you be converted, and become as little children, you shall not enter into the kingdom of heaven.&#xA;4 Whosoever therefore shall humble himself as this little child, he is the greater in the kingdom of heaven.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 19</title>
      <link>http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/01-matthew/chap019/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:23 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/01-matthew/chap019/</guid>
      <description>1 And it came to pass when Jesus had ended these words, he departed from Galilee and came into the coasts of Judea, beyond Jordan.&#xA;2 And great multitudes followed him: and he healed them there.&#xA;3 And there came to him the Pharisees tempting him, saying: Is it lawful for a man to put away his wife for every cause?&#xA;4 Who answering, said to them: Have ye not read, that he who made man from the beginning, made them male and female?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 2</title>
      <link>http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/01-matthew/chap002/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:23 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/01-matthew/chap002/</guid>
      <description>1 When Jesus therefore was born in Bethlehem of Juda, in the days of king Herod, behold, there came wise men from the East to Jerusalem,&#xA;2 Saying: Where is he that is born king of the Jews? For we have seen his star in the East, and are come to adore him.&#xA;3 And king Herod hearing this, was troubled, and all Jerusalem with him.&#xA;4 And assembling together all the chief priests and the scribes of the people, he inquired of them where Christ should be born.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 20</title>
      <link>http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/01-matthew/chap020/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:23 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/01-matthew/chap020/</guid>
      <description>1 The kingdom of heaven is like to an householder, who went out early in the morning to hire labourers into his vineyard.&#xA;2 And having agreed with the labourers for a penny a day, he sent them into his vineyard.&#xA;3 And going out about the third hour, he saw others standing in the marketplace idle.&#xA;4 And he said to them: Go you also into my vineyard, and I will give you what shall be just.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 21</title>
      <link>http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/01-matthew/chap021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:23 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/01-matthew/chap021/</guid>
      <description>1 And when they drew nigh to Jerusalem and were come to Bethphage, unto mount Olivet, then Jesus sent two disciples,&#xA;2 Saying to them: Go ye into the village that is over against you: and immediately you shall find an ass tied and a colt with her. Loose them and bring them to me.&#xA;3 And if any man shall say anything to you, say ye that the Lord hath need of them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 22</title>
      <link>http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/01-matthew/chap022/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:23 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/01-matthew/chap022/</guid>
      <description>1 And Jesus answering, spoke again in parables to them, saying:&#xA;2 The kingdom of heaven is likened to a king who made a marriage for his son.&#xA;3 And he sent his servants to call them that were invited to the marriage: and they would not come.&#xA;4 Again he sent other servants, saying: Tell them that were invited, Behold, I have prepared my dinner: my beeves and fatlings are killed, and all things are ready.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 23</title>
      <link>http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/01-matthew/chap023/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:23 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/01-matthew/chap023/</guid>
      <description>1 Then Jesus spoke to the multitudes and to his disciples,&#xA;2 Saying: The scribes and the Pharisees have sitten on the chair of Moses.&#xA;3 All things therefore whatsoever they shall say to you, observe and do: but according to their works do ye not. For they say, and do not.&#xA;4 For they bind heavy and insupportable burdens and lay them on men&amp;rsquo;s shoulders: but with a finger of their own they will not move them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 24</title>
      <link>http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/01-matthew/chap024/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:23 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/01-matthew/chap024/</guid>
      <description>1 And Jesus being come out of the temple, went away. And his disciples came to shew him the buildings of the temple.&#xA;2 And he answering, said to them: Do you see all these things? Amen I say to you, there shall not be left here a stone upon a stone that shall not be destroyed.&#xA;3 And when he was sitting on mount Olivet, the disciples came to him privately, saying: Tell us when shall these things be?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 25</title>
      <link>http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/01-matthew/chap025/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:23 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/01-matthew/chap025/</guid>
      <description>1 Then shall the kingdom of heaven be like to ten virgins, who taking their lamps went out to meet the bridegroom and the bride.&#xA;2 And five of them were foolish and five wise.&#xA;3 But the five foolish, having taken their lamps, did not take oil with them.&#xA;4 But the wise took oil in their vessels with the lamps.&#xA;5 And the bridegroom tarrying, they all slumbered and slept.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 26</title>
      <link>http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/01-matthew/chap026/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:23 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/01-matthew/chap026/</guid>
      <description>1 And it came to pass, when Jesus had ended all these words, he said to his disciples:&#xA;2 You know that after two days shall be the pasch: and the Son of man shall be delivered up to be crucified.&#xA;3 Then were gathered together the chief priests and ancients of the people, into the court of the high priest, who was called Caiphas:&#xA;4 And they consulted together that by subtilty they might apprehend Jesus and put him to death.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 27</title>
      <link>http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/01-matthew/chap027/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:23 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/01-matthew/chap027/</guid>
      <description>1 And when morning was come, all the chief priests and ancients of the people took counsel against Jesus, that they might put him to death.&#xA;2 And they brought him bound and delivered him to Pontius Pilate the governor.&#xA;3 Then Judas, who betrayed him, seeing that he was condemned, repenting himself, brought back the thirty pieces of silver to the chief priests and ancients,&#xA;4 Saying: I have sinned in betraying innocent blood.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 28</title>
      <link>http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/01-matthew/chap028/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:23 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/01-matthew/chap028/</guid>
      <description>1 And in the end of the sabbath, when it began to dawn towards the first day of the week, came Mary Magdalen and the other Mary, to see the sepulchre.&#xA;2 And behold there was a great earthquake. For an angel of the Lord descended from heaven and coming rolled back the stone and sat upon it.&#xA;3 And his countenance was as lightning and his raiment as snow.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 3</title>
      <link>http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/01-matthew/chap003/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:23 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/01-matthew/chap003/</guid>
      <description>1 And in those days cometh John the Baptist preaching in the desert of Judea.&#xA;2 And saying: Do penance: for the kingdom of heaven is at hand.&#xA;3 For this is he that was spoken of by Isaias the prophet, saying: A voice of one crying in the desert, Prepare ye the way of the Lord, make straight his paths.&#xA;4 And the same John had his garment of camel&amp;rsquo;s hair, and a leathern girdle about his loins: and his meat was locusts and wild honey.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 4</title>
      <link>http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/01-matthew/chap004/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:23 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/01-matthew/chap004/</guid>
      <description>1 Then Jesus was led by the spirit into the desert, to be tempted by the devil.&#xA;2 And when he had fasted forty days and forty nights, afterwards he was hungry.&#xA;3 And the tempter coming said to him: If thou be the Son of God, command that these stones be made bread.&#xA;4 Who answered and said: It is written, Not in bread alone doth man live, but in every word that proceedeth from the mouth of God.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 5</title>
      <link>http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/01-matthew/chap005/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:23 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/01-matthew/chap005/</guid>
      <description>1 And seeing the multitudes, he went up into a mountain, and when he was set down, his disciples came unto him.&#xA;2 And opening his mouth he taught them, saying:&#xA;3 Blessed are the poor in spirit: for theirs is the kingdom of heaven.&#xA;4 Blessed are the meek: for they shall possess the land.&#xA;5 Blessed are they that mourn: for they shall be comforted.&#xA;6 Blessed are they that hunger and thirst after justice: for they shall have their fill.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 6</title>
      <link>http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/01-matthew/chap006/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:23 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/01-matthew/chap006/</guid>
      <description>1 Take heed that you do not your justice before men, to be seen by them: otherwise you shall not have a reward of your Father who is in heaven.&#xA;2 Therefore when thou dost an alms-deed, sound not a trumpet before thee, as the hypocrites do in the synagogues and in the streets, that they may be honoured by men. Amen I say to you, they have received their reward.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 7</title>
      <link>http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/01-matthew/chap007/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:23 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/01-matthew/chap007/</guid>
      <description>1 Judge not, that you may not be judged.&#xA;2 For with what judgment you judge, you shall be judged: and with what measure you mete, it shall be measured to you again.&#xA;3 And why seest thou the mote that is in thy brother&amp;rsquo;s eye; and seest not the beam that is in thy own eye?&#xA;4 Or how sayest thou to thy brother: Let me cast the mote out of thy eye; and behold a beam is in thy own eye?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 8</title>
      <link>http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/01-matthew/chap008/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:23 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/01-matthew/chap008/</guid>
      <description>1 And when he was come down from the mountain, great multitudes followed him:&#xA;2 And behold a leper came and adored him, saying: Lord, if thou wilt, thou canst make me clean.&#xA;3 And Jesus stretching forth his hand, touched him, saying: I will, be thou made clean. And forthwith his leprosy was cleansed.&#xA;4 And Jesus saith to him: See thou tell no man: but go, shew thyself to the priest, and offer the gift which Moses commanded, for a testimony unto them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 9</title>
      <link>http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/01-matthew/chap009/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:23 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:46169/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/01-matthew/chap009/</guid>
      <description>1 And entering into a boat, he passed over the water and came into his own city.&#xA;2 And behold they brought to him one sick of the palsy lying in a bed. And Jesus, seeing their faith, said to the man sick of the palsy: Be of good heart, son, thy sins are forgiven thee.&#xA;3 And behold some of the scribes said within themselves: He blasphemeth.&#xA;4 And Jesus seeing their thoughts, said: Why do you think evil in your hearts?</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
