<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Malachi on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/71-malachi/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Malachi on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:34 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/71-malachi/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 1</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/71-malachi/chap001/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:34 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/71-malachi/chap001/</guid>
      <description>2 I have loved you, saith the Lord: and you have said: Wherein hast thou loved us? Was not Esau brother to Jacob, saith the Lord, and I have loved Jacob,&#xA;3 But have hated Esau? and I have made his mountains a wilderness, and given his inheritance to the dragons of the desert.&#xA;4 But if Edom shall say: We are destroyed, but we will return and build up what hath been destroyed: thus saith the Lord of hosts: They shall build up, and I will throw down: and they shall be called the borders of wickedness, and the people with whom the Lord is angry for ever.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 2</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/71-malachi/chap002/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:34 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/71-malachi/chap002/</guid>
      <description>1 And now, O ye priests, this commandment is to you.&#xA;2 If you will not hear, and if you will not lay it to heart, to give glory to my name, saith the Lord of hosts: I will send poverty upon you, and will curse your blessings, yea I will curse them, because you have not laid it to heart.&#xA;3 Behold, I will cast the shoulder to you, and will scatter upon your face the dung of your solemnities, and it shall take you away with it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 3</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/71-malachi/chap003/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:34 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/71-malachi/chap003/</guid>
      <description>1 Behold I send my angel, and he shall prepare the way before my face. And presently the Lord, whom you seek, and the angel of the testament, whom you desire, shall come to his temple. Behold, he cometh, saith the Lord of hosts.&#xA;2 And who shall be able to think of the day of his coming? and who shall stand to see him? for he is like a refining fire, and like the fuller&amp;rsquo;s herb:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 4</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/71-malachi/chap004/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:34 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/71-malachi/chap004/</guid>
      <description>1 For behold the day shall come kindled as a furnace: and all the proud, and all that do wickedly shall be stubble: and the day that cometh shall set them on fire, saith the Lord of hosts, it shall not leave them root, nor branch.&#xA;2 But unto you that fear my name, the Sun of justice shall arise, and health in his wings: and you shall go forth, and shall leap like calves of the herd.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
