<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Revelation on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/27-revelation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Revelation on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:36 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/27-revelation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 1</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/27-revelation/chap001/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:36 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/27-revelation/chap001/</guid>
      <description>1 The Revelation of Jesus Christ, which God gave unto him, to make known to his servants the things which must shortly come to pass: and signified, sending by his angel to his servant John,&#xA;2 Who hath given testimony to the word of God and the testimony of Jesus Christ, what things soever he hath seen.&#xA;3 Blessed is he that readeth and heareth the words of this prophecy: and keepeth those things which are written in it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 10</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/27-revelation/chap010/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:36 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/27-revelation/chap010/</guid>
      <description>1 And I saw another mighty angel come down from heaven, clothed with a cloud. And a rainbow was on his head: and his face, as the sun, and his feet as pillars of fire.&#xA;2 And he had in his hand a little book, open. And he set his right foot upon the sea, and his left foot upon the earth.&#xA;3 And he cried with a loud voice as when a lion roareth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 11</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/27-revelation/chap011/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:36 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/27-revelation/chap011/</guid>
      <description>1 And there was given me a reed, like unto a rod. And it was said to me: Arise, and measure the temple of God and the altar and them that adore therein.&#xA;2 But the court which is without the temple, cast out and measure it not: because it is given unto the Gentiles. And the holy city they shall tread under foot, two and forty months:&#xA;3 And I will give unto my two witnesses: and they shall prophesy, a thousand two hundred sixty days, clothed in sackcloth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 12</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/27-revelation/chap012/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:36 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/27-revelation/chap012/</guid>
      <description>1 And a great sign appeared in heaven: A woman clothed with the sun, and the moon under her feet, and on her head a crown of twelve stars.&#xA;2 And being with child, she cried travailing in birth: and was in pain to be delivered.&#xA;3 And there was seen another sign in heaven. And behold a great red dragon, having seven heads and ten horns and on his heads seven diadems.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 13</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/27-revelation/chap013/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:36 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/27-revelation/chap013/</guid>
      <description>1 And I saw a beast coming up out the sea, having seven heads and ten horns: and upon his horns, ten diadems: and upon his heads, names of blasphemy.&#xA;2 And the beast which I saw was like to a leopard: and his feet were as the feet of a bear, and his mouth as the mouth of a lion. And the dragon gave him his own strength and great power.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 14</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/27-revelation/chap014/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:36 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/27-revelation/chap014/</guid>
      <description>1 And I beheld: and lo a Lamb stood upon mount Sion, and with him an hundred forty-four thousand, having his name and the name of his Father written on their foreheads.&#xA;2 And I heard a voice from heaven, as the noise of many waters and as the voice of great thunder. And the voice which I heard was as the voice of harpers, harping on their harps.&#xA;3 And they sung as it were a new canticle, before the throne and before the four living creatures and the ancients: and no man could say the canticle, but those hundred forty-four thousand who were purchased from the earth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 15</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/27-revelation/chap015/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:36 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/27-revelation/chap015/</guid>
      <description>1 And I saw another sign in heaven, great and wonderful: seven angels having the seven last plagues. For in them is filled up the wrath of God.&#xA;2 And I saw as it were a sea of glass mingled with fire: and them that had overcome the beast and his image and the number of his name, standing on the sea of glass, having the harps of God:&#xA;3 And singing the canticle of Moses, the servant of God, and the canticle of the Lamb, saying: Great and wonderful are thy works, O Lord God Almighty.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 16</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/27-revelation/chap016/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:36 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/27-revelation/chap016/</guid>
      <description>1 And I heard a great voice out of the temple, saying to the seven angels: Go and pour out the seven vials of the wrath of God upon the earth.&#xA;2 And the first went and poured out his vial upon the earth. And there fell a sore and grievous wound upon men who had the character of the beast: and upon them that adored the image thereof.&#xA;3 And the second angel poured out his vial upon the sea.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 17</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/27-revelation/chap017/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:36 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/27-revelation/chap017/</guid>
      <description>1 And there came one of the seven angels who had the seven vials and spoke with me, saying: Come, I will shew thee the condemnation of the great harlot, who sitteth upon many waters:&#xA;2 With whom the kings of the earth have committed fornication. And they who inhabit the earth have been made drunk with the wine of her whoredom.&#xA;3 And he took me away in spirit into the desert.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 18</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/27-revelation/chap018/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:36 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/27-revelation/chap018/</guid>
      <description>1 And after these things, I saw another angel come down from heaven, having great power: and the earth was enlightened with his glory.&#xA;2 And he cried out with a strong voice, saying: Babylon the great is fallen, is fallen: and is become the habitation of devils and the hold of every unclean spirit and the hold of every unclean and hateful bird:&#xA;3 Because all nations have drunk of the wine of the wrath of her fornication: and the kings of the earth have committed fornication with her; And the merchants of the earth have been made rich by the power of her delicacies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 19</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/27-revelation/chap019/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:36 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/27-revelation/chap019/</guid>
      <description>1 After these things, I heard as it were the voice of much people in heaven, saying: Alleluia. Salvation and glory and power is to our God.&#xA;2 For true and just are his judgments, who hath judged the great harlot which corrupted the earth with her fornication and hath revenged the blood of his servants, at her hands.&#xA;3 And again they said: Alleluia. And her smoke ascendeth for ever and ever.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 2</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/27-revelation/chap002/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:36 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/27-revelation/chap002/</guid>
      <description>1 Unto the angel of the church of Ephesus write: These things saith he who holdeth the seven stars in his right hand, who walketh in the midst of the seven golden candlesticks:&#xA;2 I know thy works and thy labour and thy patience and how thou canst not bear them that are evil. And thou hast tried them who say they are apostles and are not: and hast found them liars:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 20</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/27-revelation/chap020/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:36 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/27-revelation/chap020/</guid>
      <description>1 And I saw an angel coming down from heaven, having the key of the bottomless pit and a great chain in his hand.&#xA;2 And he laid hold on the dragon, the old serpent, which is the devil and Satan, and bound him for a thousand years.&#xA;3 And he cast him into the bottomless pit and shut him up and set a seal upon him, that he should no more seduce the nations till the thousand years be finished.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 21</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/27-revelation/chap021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:36 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/27-revelation/chap021/</guid>
      <description>1 I saw a new heaven and a new earth. For the first heaven and the first earth was gone: and the sea is now no more.&#xA;2 And I, John, saw the holy city, the new Jerusalem, coming down out of heaven from God, prepared as a bride adorned for her husband.&#xA;3 And I heard a great voice from the throne, saying: Behold the tabernacle of God with men: and he will dwell with them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 22</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/27-revelation/chap022/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:36 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/27-revelation/chap022/</guid>
      <description>1 And he shewed me a river of water of life, clear as crystal, proceeding from the throne of God and of the Lamb.&#xA;2 In the midst of the street thereof, and on both sides of the river, was the tree of life, bearing twelve fruits, yielding its fruits every month: the leaves of the tree for the healing of the nations.&#xA;3 And there shall be no curse any more: but the throne of God and of the Lamb shall be in it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 3</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/27-revelation/chap003/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:36 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/27-revelation/chap003/</guid>
      <description>1 And to the angel of the church of Sardis write: These things saith he that hath the seven spirits of God and the seven stars: I know thy works, and that thou hast the name of being alive. And thou art dead.&#xA;2 Be watchful and strengthen the things that remain, which are ready to die. For I find not thy works full before my God.&#xA;3 Have in mind therefore in what manner thou hast received and heard: and observe and do penance: If then thou shalt not watch, I will come to thee as a thief: and thou shalt not know at what hour I will come to thee.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 4</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/27-revelation/chap004/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:36 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/27-revelation/chap004/</guid>
      <description>1 After these things I looked, and behold a door was opened in heaven, and the first voice which I heard, as it were, of a trumpet speaking with me, said: Come up hither, and I will shew thee the things which must be done hereafter.&#xA;2 And immediately I was in the spirit. And behold, there was a throne set in heaven, and upon the throne one sitting.&#xA;3 And he that sat was to the sight like the jasper and the sardine stone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 5</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/27-revelation/chap005/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:36 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/27-revelation/chap005/</guid>
      <description>1 And I saw, in the right hand of him that sat on the throne, a book, written within and without, sealed with seven seals.&#xA;2 And I saw a strong angel, proclaiming with a loud voice: Who is worthy to open the book and to loose the seals thereof?&#xA;3 And no man was able, neither in heaven nor on earth nor under the earth, to open the book, nor to look on it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 6</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/27-revelation/chap006/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:36 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/27-revelation/chap006/</guid>
      <description>1 And I saw that the Lamb had opened one of the seven seals: and I heard one of the four living creatures, as it were the voice of thunder, saying: Come and see.&#xA;2 And I saw: and behold a white horse, and he that sat on him had a bow, and there was a crown given him, and he went forth conquering that he might conquer.&#xA;3 And when he had opened the second seal, I heard the second living creature saying: Come and see.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 7</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/27-revelation/chap007/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:36 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/27-revelation/chap007/</guid>
      <description>1 After these things, I saw four angels standing on the four corners of the earth, holding the four winds of the earth, that they should not blow upon the earth nor upon the sea nor on any tree.&#xA;2 And I saw another angel ascending from the rising of the sun, having the sign of the living God. And he cried with a loud voice to the four angels to whom it was given to hurt the earth and the sea,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 8</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/27-revelation/chap008/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:36 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/27-revelation/chap008/</guid>
      <description>1 And when he had opened the seventh seal, there was silence in heaven, as it were for half an hour.&#xA;2 And I saw seven angels standing in the presence of God: and there were given to them seven trumpets.&#xA;3 And another angel came and stood before the altar, having a golden censer: and there was given to him much incense, that he should offer of the prayers of all saints, upon the golden altar which is before the throne of God.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 9</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/27-revelation/chap009/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:36 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/27-revelation/chap009/</guid>
      <description>1 And the fifth angel sounded the trumpet: and I saw a star fall from heaven upon the earth. And there was given to him the key of the bottomless pit.&#xA;2 And he opened the bottomless pit: and the smoke of the pit arose, as the smoke of a great furnace. And the sun and the air were darkened with the smoke of the pit.&#xA;3 And from the smoke of the pit there came out locusts upon the earth.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
