<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Exodus on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/29-exodus/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Exodus on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/29-exodus/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 1</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/29-exodus/chap001/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/29-exodus/chap001/</guid>
      <description>1 These are the names of the children of Israel, that went into Egypt with Jacob: they went in every man with his household:&#xA;2 Ruben, Simeon, Levi, Juda,&#xA;3 Issachar, Zabulon, and Benjamin,&#xA;4 Dan, and Nephthali, Gad and Aser.&#xA;5 And all the souls that came out of Jacob&amp;rsquo;s thigh, were seventy: but Joseph was in Egypt.&#xA;6 After he was dead, and all his brethren, and all that generation,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 10</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/29-exodus/chap010/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/29-exodus/chap010/</guid>
      <description>1 And the Lord said to Moses: Go in to Pharao; for I have hardened his heart, and the heart of his servants: that I may work these my signs in him,&#xA;2 And thou mayst tell in the ears of thy sons, and of thy grandsons, how often I have plagued the Egyptians, and wrought my signs amongst them: and you may know that I am the Lord.&#xA;3 Therefore Moses and Aaron went in to Pharao, and said to him: Thus saith the Lord God of the Hebrews: How long refusest thou to submit to me?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 11</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/29-exodus/chap011/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/29-exodus/chap011/</guid>
      <description>1 And the Lord said to Moses: Yet one plague more will I bring upon Pharao and Egypt, and after that he shall let you go, and thrust you out.&#xA;2 Therefore thou shalt tell all the people, that every man ask of his friend, and every woman of her neighbour, vessels of silver and of gold.&#xA;3 And the Lord will give favour to his people in the sight of the Egyptians.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 12</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/29-exodus/chap012/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/29-exodus/chap012/</guid>
      <description>1 And the Lord said to Moses and Aaron in the land of Egypt:&#xA;2 This month shall be to you the beginning of months; it shall be the first in the months of the year.&#xA;3 Speak ye to the whole assembly of the children of Israel, and say to them: On the tenth day of this month let every man take a lamb by their families and houses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 13</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/29-exodus/chap013/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/29-exodus/chap013/</guid>
      <description>1 And the Lord spoke to Moses, saying:&#xA;2 Sanctify unto me every firstborn that openeth the womb among the children of Israel, as well of men as of beasts: for they are all mine.&#xA;3 And Moses said to the people: Remember this day in which you came forth out of Egypt, and out of the house of bondage, for with a strong hand hath the Lord brought you forth out of this place: that you eat no leavened bread.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 14</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/29-exodus/chap014/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/29-exodus/chap014/</guid>
      <description>1 And the Lord spoke to Moses, saying:&#xA;2 Speak to the children of Israel: Let them turn and encamp over against Phihahiroth, which is between Magdal and the sea over against Beelsephon: you shall encamp before it upon the sea.&#xA;3 And Pharao will say of the children of Israel: They are straitened in the land, the desert hath shut them in.&#xA;4 And I shall harden his heart and he will pursue you: and I shall be glorified in Pharao, and in all his army: and the Egyptians shall know that I am the Lord.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 15</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/29-exodus/chap015/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/29-exodus/chap015/</guid>
      <description>1 Then Moses and the children of Israel sung this canticle to the Lord, and said: Let us sing to the Lord: for he is gloriously magnified, the horse and the rider he hath thrown into the sea.&#xA;2 The Lord is my strength and my praise, and he is become salvation to me: he is my God, and I will glorify him: the God of my father, and I will exalt him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 16</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/29-exodus/chap016/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/29-exodus/chap016/</guid>
      <description>1 And they set forward from Elim, and all the multitude of the children of Israel came into the desert of Sin, which is between Elim and Sinai: the fifteenth day of the second month, after they came out of the land of Egypt.&#xA;2 And all the congregation of the children of Israel murmured against Moses and Aaron in the wilderness.&#xA;3 And the children of Israel said to them: Would to God we had died by the hand of the Lord in the land of Egypt, when we sat over the fleshpots, and ate bread to the full: Why have you brought us into this desert, that you might destroy all the multitude with famine?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 17</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/29-exodus/chap017/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/29-exodus/chap017/</guid>
      <description>1 Then all the multitude of the children of Israel setting forward from the desert of Sin, by their mansions, according to the word of the Lord, encamped in Raphidim, where there was no water for the people to drink.&#xA;2 And they chode with Moses, and said: Give us water, that we may drink. And Moses answered them: Why chide you with me? Wherefore do you tempt the Lord?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 18</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/29-exodus/chap018/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/29-exodus/chap018/</guid>
      <description>1 And when Jethro the priest of Madian, the kinsman of Moses, had heard all the things that God had done to Moses, and to Israel his people, and that the Lord had brought forth Israel out of Egypt:&#xA;2 He took Sephora, the wife of Moses, whom he had sent back:&#xA;3 And her two sons, of whom one was called Gersam: his father saying, I have been a stranger in a foreign country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 19</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/29-exodus/chap019/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/29-exodus/chap019/</guid>
      <description>1 In the third month of the departure of Israel out of the land of Egypt, on this day they came into the wilderness of Sinai:&#xA;2 For departing out of Raphidim, and coming to the desert of Sinai, they camped in the same place, and there Israel pitched their tents over against the mountain.&#xA;3 And Moses went up to God; and the Lord called unto him from the mountain, and said: Thus shalt thou say to the house of Jacob, and tell the children of Israel:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 2</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/29-exodus/chap002/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/29-exodus/chap002/</guid>
      <description>1 After this there went a man of the house of Levi; and took a wife of his own kindred.&#xA;2 And she conceived, and bore a son: and seeing him a goodly child, hid him three months.&#xA;3 And when she could hide him no longer, she took a basket made of bulrushes, and daubed it with slime and pitch: and put the little babe therein, and laid him in the sedges by the river&amp;rsquo;s brink,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 20</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/29-exodus/chap020/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/29-exodus/chap020/</guid>
      <description>1 And the Lord spoke all these words:&#xA;2 I am the Lord thy God, who brought thee out of the land of Egypt, out of the house of bondage.&#xA;3 Thou shalt not have strange gods before me.&#xA;4 Thou shalt not make to thyself a graven thing, nor the likeness of any thing that is in heaven above, or in the earth beneath, nor of those things that are in the waters under the earth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 21</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/29-exodus/chap021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/29-exodus/chap021/</guid>
      <description>1 These are the judgments which thou shalt set before them.&#xA;2 If thou buy a Hebrew servant, six years shall he serve thee; in the seventh he shall go out free for nothing.&#xA;3 With what raiment he came in, with the like let him go out: if having a wife, his wife also shall go out with him.&#xA;4 But if his master gave him a wife, and she hath borne sons and daughters; the woman and her children shall be her master&amp;rsquo;s: but he himself shall go out with his raiment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 22</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/29-exodus/chap022/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/29-exodus/chap022/</guid>
      <description>1 If any man steal an ox or a sheep, and kill or sell it: he shall restore five oxen for one ox, and four sheep for one sheep.&#xA;2 If a thief be found breaking open a house or undermining it, and be wounded so as to die: he that slew him shall not be guilty of blood.&#xA;3 But if he did this when the sun is risen, he hath committed murder, and he shall die.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 23</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/29-exodus/chap023/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/29-exodus/chap023/</guid>
      <description>1 Thou shalt not receive the voice of a lie: neither shalt thou join thy hand to bear false witness for a wicked person.&#xA;2 Thou shalt not follow the multitude to do evil: neither shalt thou yield in judgment, to the opinion of the most part, to stray from the truth.&#xA;3 Neither shalt thou favour a poor man in judgment.&#xA;4 If thou meet thy enemy&amp;rsquo;s ox or ass going astray, bring it back to him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 24</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/29-exodus/chap024/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/29-exodus/chap024/</guid>
      <description>1 And he said to Moses: Come up to the Lord, thou, and Aaron, Nadab and Abiu, and seventy of the ancients of Israel, and you shall adore afar off.&#xA;2 And Moses alone shall come up to the Lord, but they shall not come nigh; neither shall the people come up with him.&#xA;3 So Moses came and told the people all the words of the Lord, and all the judgments: and all the people answered with one voice: We will do all the words of the Lord, which he hath spoken.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 25</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/29-exodus/chap025/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/29-exodus/chap025/</guid>
      <description>1 And the Lord spoke to Moses, saying:&#xA;2 Speak to the children of Israel, that they bring firstfruits to me: of every man that offereth of his own accord, you shall take them.&#xA;3 And these are the things you must take: Gold, and silver, and brass,&#xA;4 Violet and purple, and scarlet twice dyed, and fine linen, and goats&amp;rsquo; hair,&#xA;5 And rams&amp;rsquo; skins dyed red, and violet skins, and setim wood:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 26</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/29-exodus/chap026/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/29-exodus/chap026/</guid>
      <description>1 And thou shalt make the tabernacle in this manner: Thou shalt make ten curtains of fine twisted linen, and violet and purple, and scarlet twice dyed, diversified with embroidery.&#xA;2 The length of one curtain shall be twenty-eight cubits; the breadth shall be four cubits. All the curtains shall be of one measure.&#xA;3 Five curtains shall be joined one to another, and the other five shall be coupled together in like manner.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 27</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/29-exodus/chap027/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/29-exodus/chap027/</guid>
      <description>1 Thou shalt make also an altar of setim wood, which shall be five cubits long, and as many broad, that is four square, and three cubits high.&#xA;2 And there shall be horns at the four corners of the same: and thou shalt cover it with brass.&#xA;3 And thou shalt make for the uses thereof pans to receive the ashes, and tongs and fleshhooks, and firepans: all its vessels thou shalt make of brass.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 28</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/29-exodus/chap028/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/29-exodus/chap028/</guid>
      <description>1 Take unto thee also Aaron thy brother with his sons, from among the children of Israel, that they may minister to me in the priest&amp;rsquo;s office: Aaron, Nadab, and Abiu, Eleazar, and Ithamar.&#xA;2 And thou shalt make a holy vesture for Aaron, thy brother, for glory and for beauty.&#xA;3 And thou shalt speak to all the wise of heart, whom I have filled with the spirit of wisdom, that they may make Aaron&amp;rsquo;s vestments, in which he being consecrated, may minister to me.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 29</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/29-exodus/chap029/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/29-exodus/chap029/</guid>
      <description>1 And thou shalt also do this, that they may be consecrated to me in priesthood. Take a calf from the herd, and two rams without blemish,&#xA;2 And unleavened bread, and a cake without leaven, tempered with oil, wafers also unleavened, anointed with oil: thou shalt make them all of wheaten flour.&#xA;3 And thou shalt put them in a basket, and offer them: and the calf and the two rams.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 3</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/29-exodus/chap003/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/29-exodus/chap003/</guid>
      <description>1 Now Moses fed the sheep of Jethro, his father in law, the priest of Madian: and he drove the flock to the inner parts of the desert, and came to the mountain of God, Horeb.&#xA;2 And the Lord appeared to him in a flame of fire out of the midst of a bush: and he saw that the bush was on fire, and was not burnt.&#xA;3 And Moses said: I will go, and see this great sight, why the bush is not burnt.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 30</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/29-exodus/chap030/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/29-exodus/chap030/</guid>
      <description>1 Thou shalt make also an altar to burn incense, of setim wood.&#xA;2 It shall be a cubit in length, and another in breadth, that is, four square, and two in height. Horns shall go out of the same.&#xA;3 And thou shalt overlay it with the purest gold, as well the grate thereof, as the walls round about, and the horns. And thou shalt make to it a crown of gold round about,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 31</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/29-exodus/chap031/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/29-exodus/chap031/</guid>
      <description>1 And the Lord spoke to Moses, saying:&#xA;2 Behold, I have called by name Beseleel the son of Uri, the son of Hur, of the tribe of Juda,&#xA;3 And I have filled him with the spirit of God, with wisdom and understanding, and knowledge in all manner of work,&#xA;4 To devise whatsoever may be artificially made of gold, and silver, and brass,&#xA;5 Of marble, and precious stones, and variety of wood.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 32</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/29-exodus/chap032/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/29-exodus/chap032/</guid>
      <description>1 And the people seeing that Moses delayed to come down from the mount, gathering together against Aaron, said: Arise, make us gods, that may go before us: For as to this Moses, the man that brought us out of the land of Egypt, we know not what has befallen him.&#xA;2 And Aaron said to them: Take the golden earrings from the ears of your wives, and your sons and daughters, and bring them to me.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 33</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/29-exodus/chap033/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/29-exodus/chap033/</guid>
      <description>1 And the Lord spoke to Moses, saying: Go, get thee up from this place, thou and thy people which thou hast brought out of the land of Egypt, into the land concerning which I swore to Abraham, Isaac, and Jacob, saying: To thy seed I will give it:&#xA;2 And I will send an angel before thee, that I may cast out the Chanaanite, and the Amorrhite, and the Hethite, and the Pherezite, and the Hevite, and the Jebusite,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 34</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/29-exodus/chap034/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/29-exodus/chap034/</guid>
      <description>1 And after this he said: Hew thee two tables of stone like unto the former, and I will write upon them the words, which were in the tables, which thou brokest.&#xA;2 Be ready in the morning, that thou mayst forthwith go up into Mount Sinai, and thou shalt stand with me upon the top of the mount.&#xA;3 Let no man go up with thee, and let not any man be seen throughout all the mount; neither let the oxen nor the sheep feed over against it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 35</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/29-exodus/chap035/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/29-exodus/chap035/</guid>
      <description>1 And all the multitude of the children of Israel being gathered together, he said to them: These are the things which the Lord hath commanded to be done:&#xA;2 Six days you shall do work; the seventh day shall be holy unto you, the sabbath and the rest of the Lord: he that shall do any work on it, shall be put to death.&#xA;3 You shall kindle no fire in any of your habitations on the sabbath day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 36</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/29-exodus/chap036/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/29-exodus/chap036/</guid>
      <description>1 Beseleel therefore, and Ooliab, and every wise man, to whom the Lord gave wisdom and understanding, to know how to work artificially, made the things that are necessary for the uses of the sanctuary, and which the Lord commanded.&#xA;2 And when Moses had called them, and every skilful man, to whom the Lord had given wisdom, and such as of their own accord had offered themselves to the making of the work,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 37</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/29-exodus/chap037/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/29-exodus/chap037/</guid>
      <description>1 And Beseleel made also, the ark of setim wood: it was two cubits and a half in length, and a cubit and a half in breadth, and the height was of one cubit and a half: and he overlaid it with the purest gold within and without.&#xA;2 And he made to it a crown of gold round about,&#xA;3 Casting four rings of gold at the four corners thereof: two rings in one side, and two in the other.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 38</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/29-exodus/chap038/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/29-exodus/chap038/</guid>
      <description>1 He made also the altar of holocaust of setim wood, five cubits square, and three in height:&#xA;2 The horns whereof went out from the corners, and he overlaid it with plates of brass.&#xA;3 And for the uses thereof, he prepared divers vessels of brass, cauldrons, tongs, fleshhooks, pothooks and firepans.&#xA;4 And he made the grate thereof of brass, in manner of a net, and under it in the midst of the altar a hearth,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 39</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/29-exodus/chap039/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/29-exodus/chap039/</guid>
      <description>1 And he made, of violet and purple, scarlet and fine linen, the vestments for Aaron to wear when he ministered in the holy places, as the Lord commanded Moses.&#xA;2 So he made an ephod of gold, violet, and purple, and scarlet twice dyed, and fine twisted linen,&#xA;3 With embroidered work, and he cut thin plates of gold, and drew them small into threads, that they might be twisted with the woof of the foresaid colours,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 4</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/29-exodus/chap004/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/29-exodus/chap004/</guid>
      <description>1 Moses answered, and said: They will not believe me, nor hear my voice, but they will say: The Lord hath not appeared to thee.&#xA;2 Then he said to him: What is that thou holdest in thy hand? He answered: A rod.&#xA;3 And the Lord said: Cast it down upon the ground. He cast it down, and it was turned into a serpent, so that Moses fled from it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 40</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/29-exodus/chap040/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/29-exodus/chap040/</guid>
      <description>1 And the Lord spoke to Moses, saying:&#xA;2 The first month, the first day of the month, thou shalt set up the tabernacle of the testimony,&#xA;3 And shalt put the ark in it, and shalt let down the veil before it:&#xA;4 And thou shalt bring in the table, and set upon it the things that are commanded according to the rite. The candlestick shall stand with its lamps,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 5</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/29-exodus/chap005/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/29-exodus/chap005/</guid>
      <description>1 After these things, Moses and Aaron went in, and said to Pharao: Thus saith the Lord God of Israel: Let my people go, that they may sacrifice to me in the desert.&#xA;2 But he answered: Who is the Lord, that I should hear his voice, and let Israel go? I know not the Lord, neither will I let Israel go.&#xA;3 And they said: The God of the Hebrews hath called us, to go three days&amp;rsquo; journey into the wilderness, and to sacrifice to the Lord our God; lest a pestilence or the sword fall upon us.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 6</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/29-exodus/chap006/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/29-exodus/chap006/</guid>
      <description>1 And the Lord said to Moses: Now thou shalt see what I will do to Pharao: for by a mighty hand shall he let them go, and with a strong hand shall he cast them out of his land.&#xA;2 And the Lord spoke to Moses, saying: I am the Lord&#xA;3 That appeared to Abraham, to Isaac, and to Jacob, by the name of God Almighty: and my name ADONAI I did not shew them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 7</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/29-exodus/chap007/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/29-exodus/chap007/</guid>
      <description>1 And the Lord said to Moses: Behold, I have appointed thee the god of Pharao; and Aaron, thy brother, shall be thy prophet.&#xA;2 Thou shalt speak to him all that I command thee; and he shall speak to Pharao, that he let the children of Israel go out of his land.&#xA;3 But I shall harden his heart, and shall multiply my signs and wonders in the land of Egypt.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 8</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/29-exodus/chap008/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/29-exodus/chap008/</guid>
      <description>1 And the Lord said to Moses: Go in to Pharao, and thou shalt say to him: Thus saith the Lord: Let my people go to sacrifice to me.&#xA;2 But if thou wilt not let them go, behold I will strike all thy coasts with frogs.&#xA;3 And the river shall bring forth an abundance of frogs; which shall come up and enter into thy house, and thy bedchamber, and upon thy bed, and into the houses of thy servants, and to thy people, and into thy ovens, and into the remains of thy meats:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 9</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/29-exodus/chap009/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/29-exodus/chap009/</guid>
      <description>1 And the Lord said to Moses: Go in to Pharao, and speak to him: Thus saith the Lord God of the Hebrews: Let my people go to sacrifice to me.&#xA;2 But if thou refuse, and withhold them still:&#xA;3 Behold my hand shall be upon thy fields; and a very grievous murrain upon thy horses, and asses, and camels, and oxen, and sheep.&#xA;4 And the Lord will make a wonderful difference between the possessions of Israel and the possessions of the Egyptians, that nothing at all shall die of those things that belong to the children of Israel.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
