<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2 Chronicles on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</title>
    <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/41-2-chronicles/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2 Chronicles on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:28 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/41-2-chronicles/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 1</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/41-2-chronicles/chap001/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:28 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/41-2-chronicles/chap001/</guid>
      <description>1 And Solomon the son of David was strengthened in his kingdom, and the Lord his God was with him, and magnified him to a high degree.&#xA;2 And Solomon gave orders to all Israel, to the captains of thousands, and of hundreds, and to the rulers, and to the judges of all Israel, and the heads of the families:&#xA;3 And he went with all the multitude to the high place of Gabaon, where was the tabernacle of the covenant of the Lord, which Moses the servant of God made, in the wilderness.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 10</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/41-2-chronicles/chap010/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:28 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/41-2-chronicles/chap010/</guid>
      <description>1 And Roboam went to Sichem: for thither all Israel were assembled, to make him king.&#xA;2 And when Jeroboam the son of Nabat, who was in Egypt, (for he was fled thither from Solomon,) heard it, forthwith he returned.&#xA;3 And they sent for him, and he came with all Israel, and they spoke to Roboam, saying:&#xA;4 Thy father oppressed with a most grievous yoke, do thou govern us with a lighter hand than thy father, who laid upon us a heavy servitude, and ease some thing of the burden, that we may serve thee.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 11</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/41-2-chronicles/chap011/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:28 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/41-2-chronicles/chap011/</guid>
      <description>1 And Roboam came to Jerusalem, and called together all the house of Juda and of Benjamin, a hundred and fourscore thousand chosen men and warriors, to fight against Israel, and to bring back his kingdom to him.&#xA;2 And the word of the Lord came to Semeias the man of God, saying:&#xA;3 Speak to Roboam the son of Solomon the king of Juda, and to all Israel, in Juda and Benjamin:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 12</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/41-2-chronicles/chap012/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:28 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/41-2-chronicles/chap012/</guid>
      <description>1 And when the kingdom of Roboam was strengthened and fortified, he forsook the law of the Lord, and all Israel with him.&#xA;2 And in the fifth year of the reign of Roboam, Sesac king of Egypt came up against Jerusalem (because they had sinned against the Lord)&#xA;3 With twelve hundred chariots and threescore thousand horsemen: and the people were without number that came with him out of Egypt, to wit, Libyans, and Troglodites, and Ethiopians.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 13</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/41-2-chronicles/chap013/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:28 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/41-2-chronicles/chap013/</guid>
      <description>1 In the eighteenth year of king Jeroboam, Abia reigned over Juda.&#xA;2 Three years he reigned in Jerusalem, and his mother&amp;rsquo;s name was Michaia, the daughter of Uriel of Gabaa: and there was war between Abia and Jeroboam.&#xA;3 And when Abia had begun battle, and had with him four hundred thousand most valiant and chosen men, Jeroboam put his army in array against him, eight hundred thousand men, who were also chosen and most valiant for war.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 14</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/41-2-chronicles/chap014/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:28 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/41-2-chronicles/chap014/</guid>
      <description>1 And Abia slept with his fathers, and they buried him in the city of David: an Asa his son reigned in his stead: in his days the land was quiet ten years.&#xA;2 And Asa did that which was good and pleasing in the sight of his God, and he destroyed the altars of foreign worship, and the high places.&#xA;3 And broke the statues, and cut down the groves.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 15</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/41-2-chronicles/chap015/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:28 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/41-2-chronicles/chap015/</guid>
      <description>1 And the spirit of God came upon Azarias the son of Oded,&#xA;2 And he went out to meet Asa, and said to him: Hear ye me, Asa, and all Juda and Benjamin: The Lord is with you, because you have been with him. If you seek him, you shall find: but if you forsake him, he will forsake you.&#xA;3 And many days shall pass in Israel, without the true God, and without a priest a teacher, and without the law.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 16</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/41-2-chronicles/chap016/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:28 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/41-2-chronicles/chap016/</guid>
      <description>1 And in the six and thirtieth year of his kingdom, Baasa the king of Israel came up against Juda, and built a wall about Rama, that no one might safely go out or come in of the kingdom of Asa.&#xA;2 Then Asa brought out silver and gold out of the treasures of the house of the Lord, and of the king&amp;rsquo;s treasures, and sent to Benadad king of Syria, who dwelt in Damascus, saying:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 17</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/41-2-chronicles/chap017/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:28 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/41-2-chronicles/chap017/</guid>
      <description>1 And Josaphat his son reigned in his stead, and grew strong against Israel.&#xA;2 And he placed numbers of soldiers in all the fortified cities of Juda. And he put garrisons in the land of Juda, and in the cities of Ephraim, which Asa his father had taken.&#xA;3 And the Lord was with Josaphat, because he walked in the first ways of David his father: and trusted not in Baalim,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 18</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/41-2-chronicles/chap018/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:28 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/41-2-chronicles/chap018/</guid>
      <description>1 Now Josaphat was rich and very glorious, and was joined by affinity to Achab.&#xA;2 And he went down to him after some years to Samaria: and Achab at his coming killed sheep and oxen in abundance for him and the people that came with him: and he persuaded him to go up to Ramoth Galaad.&#xA;3 And Achab king of Israel said to Josaphat king of Juda: Come with me to Ramoth Galaad.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 19</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/41-2-chronicles/chap019/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:28 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/41-2-chronicles/chap019/</guid>
      <description>1 And Josaphat king of Juda returned to his house in peace to Jerusalem.&#xA;2 And Jehu the son of Hanani the seer met him, and said to him: Thou helpest the ungodly, and thou art joined in friendship with them that hate the Lord, and therefore thou didst deserve indeed the wrath of the Lord:&#xA;3 But good works are found in thee, because thou hast taken away the groves out of the land of Juda, and hast prepared thy heart to seek the Lord the God of thy fathers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 2</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/41-2-chronicles/chap002/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:28 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/41-2-chronicles/chap002/</guid>
      <description>1 And Solomon determined to build a house to the name of the Lord, and a palace for himself.&#xA;2 And he numbered out seventy thousand men to bear burdens, and eighty thousand to hew stones in the mountains, and three thousand six hundred to oversee them.&#xA;3 He sent also to Hiram king of Tyre, saying: As thou didst with David my father, and didst send him cedars, to build him a house, in which he dwelt:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 20</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/41-2-chronicles/chap020/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:28 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/41-2-chronicles/chap020/</guid>
      <description>1 After this the children of Moab, and the children of Ammon, and with them of the Ammonites, were gathered together to fight against Josaphat.&#xA;2 And there came messengers, and told Josaphat, saying: There cometh a great multitude against thee from beyond the sea, and out of Syria, and behold they are in Asasonthamar, which is Engaddi.&#xA;3 And Josaphat being seized with fear betook himself wholly to pray to the Lord, and he proclaimed a fast for all Juda.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 21</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/41-2-chronicles/chap021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:28 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/41-2-chronicles/chap021/</guid>
      <description>1 And Josaphat slept with his fathers, and was buried with them in the city of David: and Joram his son reigned in his stead.&#xA;2 And he had brethren the sons of Josaphat, Azarias, and Jahiel, and Zacharias, and Azaria, and Michael, and Saphatias, all these were the sons of Josaphat king of Juda.&#xA;3 And their father gave them great gifts of silver, and of gold, and pensions, with strong cities in Juda: but the kingdom he gave to Joram, because he was the eldest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 22</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/41-2-chronicles/chap022/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:28 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/41-2-chronicles/chap022/</guid>
      <description>1 And the inhabitants of Jerusalem made Ochozias his youngest son king in his place: for the rovers of the Arabians, who had broke in upon the camp, had killed all that were his elder brothers. So Ochozias the son of Joram king of Juda reigned.&#xA;2 Ochozias was forty-two years old when he began to reign, and he reigned one year in Jerusalem, and the name of his mother was Athalia the daughter of Amri.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 23</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/41-2-chronicles/chap023/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:28 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/41-2-chronicles/chap023/</guid>
      <description>1 And in the seventh year Joiada being encouraged, took the captains of hundreds, to wit, Azarias the son of Jeroham, and Ismahel the son of Johanan, and Azarias the son of Obed, and Maasias the son of Adaias, and Elisaphat the son of Zechri: and made a covenant with them.&#xA;2 And they went about Juda, and gathered together the Levites out of all the cities of Juda, and the chiefs of the families of Israel, and they came to Jerusalem.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 24</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/41-2-chronicles/chap024/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:28 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/41-2-chronicles/chap024/</guid>
      <description>1 Joas was seven years old when he began to reign: and he reigned forty years in Jerusalem: the name of his mother was Sebia of Bersabee.&#xA;2 And he did that which is good before the Lord all the days of Joiada the priest.&#xA;3 And Joiada took for him two wives, by whom he had sons and daughters.&#xA;4 After this Joas had a mind to repair the house of the Lord.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 25</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/41-2-chronicles/chap025/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:28 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/41-2-chronicles/chap025/</guid>
      <description>1 Amasias was five and twenty years old when he began to reign, and he reigned nine and twenty years in Jerusalem, the name of his mother was Joadan of Jerusalem.&#xA;2 And he did what was good in the sight of the Lord: but yet not with a perfect heart.&#xA;3 And when he saw himself strengthened in his kingdom, he put to death the servants that had slain the king his father.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 26</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/41-2-chronicles/chap026/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:28 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/41-2-chronicles/chap026/</guid>
      <description>1 And all the people of Juda took his son Ozias, who was sixteen years old, and made him king in the room of Amasias his father.&#xA;2 He built Ailath, and restored it to the dominion of Juda, after that the king slept with his fathers.&#xA;3 Ozias was sixteen years old when he began to reign, and he reigned two and fifty years in Jerusalem: the name of his mother was Jechelia of Jerusalem.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 27</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/41-2-chronicles/chap027/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:28 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/41-2-chronicles/chap027/</guid>
      <description>1 Joatham was five and twenty years old when he began to reign, and he reigned sixteen years in Jerusalem: the name of his mother was Jerusa the daughter of Sadoc.&#xA;2 And he did that which was right before the Lord, according to all that Ozias his father had done, only that he entered not into the temple of the Lord, and the people still transgressed.&#xA;3 He built the high gate of the house of the Lord, and on the wall of Ophel he built much.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 28</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/41-2-chronicles/chap028/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:28 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/41-2-chronicles/chap028/</guid>
      <description>1 Achaz was twenty years old when he began to reign, and he reigned sixteen years in Jerusalem: he did not that which was right in the sight of the Lord as David his father had done,&#xA;2 But walked in the ways of the kings of Israel; moreover also he cast statues for Baalim.&#xA;3 It was he that burnt incense in the valley of Benennom, and consecrated his sons in the fire according to the manner of the nations, which the Lord slew at the coming of the children of Israel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 29</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/41-2-chronicles/chap029/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:28 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/41-2-chronicles/chap029/</guid>
      <description>1 Now Ezechias began to reign, when he was five and twenty years old, and he reigned nine and twenty years in Jerusalem: the name of his mother was Abia, the daughter of Zacharias.&#xA;2 And he did that which was pleasing in the sight of the Lord, according to all that David his father had done.&#xA;3 In the first year and month of his reign he opened the doors of the house of the Lord, and repaired them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 3</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/41-2-chronicles/chap003/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:28 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/41-2-chronicles/chap003/</guid>
      <description>1 And Solomon began to build the house of the Lord in Jerusalem, in mount Moria, which had been shewn to David his father, in the place which David had prepared in the thrashingfloor of Ornan the Jebusite.&#xA;2 And he began to build in the second month, in the fourth year of his reign.&#xA;3 Now these are the foundations, which Solomon laid, to build the house of God, the length by the first measure sixty cubits, the breadth twenty cubits.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 30</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/41-2-chronicles/chap030/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:28 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/41-2-chronicles/chap030/</guid>
      <description>1 And Ezechias sent to all Israel and Juda: and he wrote letters to Ephraim and Manasses, that they should come to the house of the Lord in Jerusalem, and keep the phase to the Lord the God of Israel,&#xA;2 For the king, taking counsel, and the princes, and all the assembly of Jerusalem, decreed to keep the phase the second month.&#xA;3 For they could not keep it in its time; because there were not priests enough sanctified, and the people was not as yet gathered together to Jerusalem.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 31</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/41-2-chronicles/chap031/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:28 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/41-2-chronicles/chap031/</guid>
      <description>1 And when these things had been duly celebrated, all Israel that were found in the cities of Juda, went out, and they broke the idols, and cut down the groves, demolished the high places, and destroyed the altars, not only out of all Juda and Benjamin, but out of Ephraim also and Manasses, till they had utterly destroyed them: then all the children of Israel returned to their possessions and cities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 32</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/41-2-chronicles/chap032/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:28 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/41-2-chronicles/chap032/</guid>
      <description>1 After these things, and this truth, Sennacherib king of the Assyrians came and entered into Juda, and besieged the fenced cities, desiring to take them.&#xA;2 And when Ezechias saw that Sennacherib was come, and that the whole force of the war was turning against Jerusalem,&#xA;3 He took counsel with the princes, and the most valiant men, to stop up the heads of the springs, that were without the city: and as they were all of this mind,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 33</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/41-2-chronicles/chap033/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:28 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/41-2-chronicles/chap033/</guid>
      <description>1 Manasses was twelve years old when he began to reign, and he reigned fifty-five years in Jerusalem.&#xA;2 And he did evil before the Lord, according to all the abominations of the nations, which the Lord cast out before the children of Israel:&#xA;3 And he turned, and built again the high places which Ezechias his father had destroyed: and he built altars to Baalim, and made groves, and he adored all the host of heaven, and worshipped them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 34</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/41-2-chronicles/chap034/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:28 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/41-2-chronicles/chap034/</guid>
      <description>1 Josias was eight years old when he began to reign, and he reigned one and thirty years in Jerusalem.&#xA;2 And he did that which was right in the sight of the Lord, and walked in the ways of David his father: he declined not, neither to the right hand, nor to the left.&#xA;3 And in the eighth year of his reign, when he was yet a boy, he began to seek the God of his father David: and in the twelfth year after he began to reign, he cleansed Juda and Jerusalem from the high places, and the groves, and the idols, and the graven things.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 35</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/41-2-chronicles/chap035/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:28 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/41-2-chronicles/chap035/</guid>
      <description>1 And Josias kept a phase to the Lord in Jerusalem, and it was sacrificed on the fourteenth day of the first month.&#xA;2 And he set the priests in their offices, and exhorted them to minister in the house of the Lord.&#xA;3 And he spoke to the Levites, by whose instruction all Israel was sanctified to the Lord, saying: Put the ark in the sanctuary of the temple, which Solomon the son of David king of Israel built: for you shall carry it no more: but minister now to the Lord your God, and to his people Israel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 36</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/41-2-chronicles/chap036/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:28 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/41-2-chronicles/chap036/</guid>
      <description>1 Then the people of the land took Joachaz the son of Josias, and made him king instead of his father in Jerusalem.&#xA;2 Joachaz was three and twenty years old when he began to reign, and he reigned three months in Jerusalem.&#xA;3 And the king of Egypt came to Jerusalem, and deposed him, and condemned the land in a hundred talents of silver, and a talent of gold.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 4</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/41-2-chronicles/chap004/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:28 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/41-2-chronicles/chap004/</guid>
      <description>1 He made also an altar of brass twenty cubits long, and twenty cubits broad, and ten cubits high.&#xA;2 Also a molten sea of ten cubits from brim to brim, round in compass: it was five cubits high, and a line of thirty cubits compassed it round about.&#xA;3 And under it there was the likeness of oxen, and certain engravings on the outside of ten cubits compassed the belly of the sea, as it were with two rows.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 5</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/41-2-chronicles/chap005/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:28 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/41-2-chronicles/chap005/</guid>
      <description>1 Then Solomon brought in all those things that David his father had vowed, the silver, and the gold, and all the vessels he put among the treasures of the house of God.&#xA;2 And after this he gathered together the ancients of Israel and all the princes of the tribes, and the heads of the families, of the children of Israel to Jerusalem, to bring the ark of the covenant of the Lord out of the city of David, which is Sion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 6</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/41-2-chronicles/chap006/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:28 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/41-2-chronicles/chap006/</guid>
      <description>1 Then Solomon said: The Lord promised that he would dwell in a cloud.&#xA;2 But I have built a house to his name, that he might dwell there for ever.&#xA;3 And the king turned his face, and blessed all the multitude of Israel for all the multitude stood attentive and he said:&#xA;4 Blessed be the Lord the God of Israel, who hath accomplished in deed that which he spoke to David my father, saying:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 7</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/41-2-chronicles/chap007/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:28 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/41-2-chronicles/chap007/</guid>
      <description>1 And when Solomon had made an end of his prayer, fire came down from heaven, and consumed the holocausts and the victims: and the majesty of the Lord filled the house.&#xA;2 Neither could the priests enter into the temple of the Lord, because the majesty of the Lord had filled the temple of the Lord.&#xA;3 Moreover all the children of Israel saw the fire coming down, and the glory of the Lord upon the house: and falling down with their faces to the ground, upon the stone pavement, they adored and praised the Lord: because he is good, because his mercy endureth for ever.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 8</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/41-2-chronicles/chap008/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:28 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/41-2-chronicles/chap008/</guid>
      <description>1 And at the end of twenty years after Solomon had built the house of the Lord and his own house:&#xA;2 He built the cities which Hiram had given to Solomon, and caused the children of Israel to dwell there.&#xA;3 He went also into Emath Suba, and possessed it.&#xA;4 And he built Palmira in the desert, and he built other strong cities in Emath.&#xA;5 And he built Beth-horon the upper, and Beth-horon the nether, walled cities with gates and bars and locks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 9</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/41-2-chronicles/chap009/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:28 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/41-2-chronicles/chap009/</guid>
      <description>1 And when the queen of Saba heard of the fame of Solomon, she came to try him with hard questions at Jerusalem, with great riches, and camels, which carried spices, and abundance of gold, and precious stones. And when she was come to Solomon, she proposed to him all that was in her heart.&#xA;2 And Solomon explained to her all that she proposed: and there was not any thing that he did not make clear unto her.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
