<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>1 John on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/23-1-john/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 1 John on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:36 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/23-1-john/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 1</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/23-1-john/chap001/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:36 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/23-1-john/chap001/</guid>
      <description>1 That which was from the beginning, which we have heard, which we have seen with our eyes, which we have looked upon and our hands have handled, of the word of life.&#xA;2 For the life was manifested: and we have seen and do bear witness and declare unto you the life eternal, which was with the Father and hath appeared to us.&#xA;3 That which we have seen and have heard, we declare unto you: that you also may have fellowship with us and our fellowship may be with the Father and with his Son Jesus Christ.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 2</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/23-1-john/chap002/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:36 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/23-1-john/chap002/</guid>
      <description>1 My little children, these things I write to you, that you may not sin. But if any man sin, we have an advocate with the Father, Jesus Christ the just.&#xA;2 And he is the propitiation for our sins: and not for ours only, but also for those of the whole world.&#xA;3 And by this we know that we have known him, if we keep his commandments.&#xA;4 He who saith that he knoweth him and keepeth not his commandments is a liar: and the truth is not in him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 3</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/23-1-john/chap003/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:36 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/23-1-john/chap003/</guid>
      <description>1 Behold what manner of charity the Father hath bestowed upon us, that we should be called and should be the sons of God. Therefore the world knoweth not us, because it knew not him.&#xA;2 Dearly beloved, we are now the sons of God: and it hath not yet appeared what we shall be. We know that when he shall appear we shall be like to him: because we shall see him as he is.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 4</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/23-1-john/chap004/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:36 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/23-1-john/chap004/</guid>
      <description>1 Dearly beloved, believe not every spirit, but try the spirits if they be of God: because many false prophets are gone out into the world.&#xA;2 By this is the spirit of God known. Every spirit which confesseth that Jesus Christ is come in the flesh is of God:&#xA;3 And every spirit that dissolveth Jesus is not of God. And this is Antichrist, of whom you have heard that he cometh: and he is now already in the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 5</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/23-1-john/chap005/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 18:40:36 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/23-1-john/chap005/</guid>
      <description>1 Whosoever believeth that Jesus is the Christ, is born of God. And every one that loveth him who begot, loveth him also who is born of him.&#xA;2 In this we know that we love the children of God: when we love God and keep his commandments.&#xA;3 For this is the charity of God: That we keep his commandments. And his commandments are not heavy.&#xA;4 For whatsoever is born of God overcometh the world.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
