<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Nehemiah on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</title>
    <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/43-nehemiah/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Nehemiah on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/43-nehemiah/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 10</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/43-nehemiah/chap010/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/43-nehemiah/chap010/</guid>
      <description>1 And the subscribers were Nehemiah, Athersatha the son of Hachelai, and Sedecias,&#xA;2 Saraias, Azarias, Jeremias,&#xA;3 Pheshur, Amarias, Melchias,&#xA;4 Hattus, Sebenia, Melluch,&#xA;5 Harem, Merimuth, Obdias,&#xA;6 Daniel, Genthon, Baruch,&#xA;7 Mosollam, Abia, Miamin,&#xA;8 Maazia, Belgia, Semeia: these were priests.&#xA;9 And the Levites, Josue the son of Azanias, Bennui of the sons of Henadad, Cedmihel,&#xA;10 And their brethren, Sebenia, Oduia, Celita, Phalaia, Hanan,&#xA;11 Micha, Rohob, Hasebia,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 11</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/43-nehemiah/chap011/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/43-nehemiah/chap011/</guid>
      <description>1 And the princes of the people dwelt at Jerusalem: but the rest of the people cast lots, to take one part in ten to dwell in Jerusalem the holy city, and nine parts in the other cities.&#xA;2 And the people blessed all the men that willingly offered themselves to dwell in Jerusalem.&#xA;3 These therefore are the chief men of the province, who dwelt in Jerusalem, and in the cities of Juda.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 12</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/43-nehemiah/chap012/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/43-nehemiah/chap012/</guid>
      <description>1 Now these are the priests and the Levites, that went up with Zorobabel the son of Salathiel, and Josue: Saraia, Jeremias, Esdras,&#xA;2 Amaria, Melluch, Hattus,&#xA;3 Sebenias, Rheum, Merimuth,&#xA;4 Addo, Genthon, Abia,&#xA;5 Miamin, Madia, Belga,&#xA;6 Semeia, and Joiarib, Idaia, Sellum Amoc, Helcias,&#xA;7 Idaia. These were the chief of the priests, and of their brethren in the days of Josue.&#xA;8 And the Levites, Jesua, Bennui, Cedmihel, Sarebia, Juda, Mathanias, they and their brethren were over the hymns:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 13</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/43-nehemiah/chap013/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/43-nehemiah/chap013/</guid>
      <description>1 And on that day they read in the book of Moses in the hearing of the people: and therein was found written, that the Ammonites and the Moabites should not come in to the church of God for ever:&#xA;2 Because they met not the children of Israel with bread and water: and they hired against them Balaam, to curse them, and our God turned the curse into blessing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 4</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/43-nehemiah/chap004/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/43-nehemiah/chap004/</guid>
      <description>1 And it came to pass, that when Sanaballat heard that we were building the wall he was angry: and being moved exceedingly he scoffed at the Jews.&#xA;2 And said before his brethren, and the multitude of the Samaritans: What are the silly Jews doing? Will the Gentiles let them alone? will they sacrifice and make an end in a day? are they able to raise stones out of the heaps of the rubbish, which are burnt?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 5</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/43-nehemiah/chap005/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/43-nehemiah/chap005/</guid>
      <description>1 Now there was a great cry of the people, and of their wives against their brethren the Jews.&#xA;2 And there were some that said: Our sons and our daughters are very many: let us take up corn for the price of them, and let us eat and live.&#xA;3 And there were some that said: Let us mortgage our lands, and our vineyards, and our houses, and let us take corn because of the famine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 6</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/43-nehemiah/chap006/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/43-nehemiah/chap006/</guid>
      <description>1 And it came to pass, when Sanaballat, and Tobias, and Gossem the Arabian, and the rest of our enemies, heard that I had built the wall, and that there was no breach left in it, (though at that time I had not set up the doors in the gates,)&#xA;2 Sanaballat and Gossem sent to me, saying: Come, and let us make a league together in the villages, in the plain of Ono.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 7</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/43-nehemiah/chap007/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/43-nehemiah/chap007/</guid>
      <description>1 Now after the wall was built, and I had set up the doors, and numbered the porters and singing men, and Levites:&#xA;2 I commanded Hanani my brother, and Hananias ruler of the house of Jerusalem, (for he seemed as a sincere man, and one that feared God above the rest,)&#xA;3 And I said to them: Let not the gates of Jerusalem be opened till the sun be hot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 8</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/43-nehemiah/chap008/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/43-nehemiah/chap008/</guid>
      <description>1 And the seventh month came: and the children of Israel were in their cities. And all the people were gathered together as one man to the street which is before the water gate, and they spoke to Esdras the scribe, to bring the book of the law of Moses, which the Lord had commanded to Israel.&#xA;2 Then Esdras the priest brought the law before the multitude of men and women, and all those that could understand, in the first day of the seventh month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 9</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/43-nehemiah/chap009/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/43-nehemiah/chap009/</guid>
      <description>1 And in the four and twentieth day of the month the children of Israel came together with fasting and with sackcloth, and earth upon them.&#xA;2 And the seed of the children of Israel separated themselves from every stranger: and they stood, and confessed their sins, and the iniquities of their fathers.&#xA;3 And they rose up to stand: and they read in the book of the law of the Lord their God, four times in the day, and four times they confessed, and adored the Lord their God.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 1</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/43-nehemiah/chap001/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:28 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/43-nehemiah/chap001/</guid>
      <description>1 The words of Nehemiah the son of Helchias. And it came to pass in the month of Casleu, in the twentieth year, as I was in the castle of Susa,&#xA;2 That Hanani one of my brethren came, he and some men of Juda; and I asked them concerning the Jews, that remained and were left of the captivity, and concerning Jerusalem.&#xA;3 And they said to me: They that have remained, and are left of the captivity there in the province, are in great affliction, and reproach: and the wall of Jerusalem is broken down, and the gates thereof are burnt with fire.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 2</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/43-nehemiah/chap002/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:28 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/43-nehemiah/chap002/</guid>
      <description>1 And it came to pass in the month of Nisan, in the twentieth year of Artaxerxes the king: that wine was before him, and I took up the wine, and gave it to the king: and I was as one languishing away before his face.&#xA;2 And the king said to me: Why is thy countenance sad, seeing thou dost not appear to be sick? this is not without cause, but some evil, I know not what, is in thy heart.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 3</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/43-nehemiah/chap003/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:28 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/43-nehemiah/chap003/</guid>
      <description>1 Then Eliasib the high priest arose, and his brethren the priests, and they built the flock gate: they sanctified it, and set up the doors thereof, even unto the tower of a hundred cubits they sanctified it unto the tower of Hananeel.&#xA;2 And next to him the men of Jericho built: and next to them built Zachur the son of Amri.&#xA;3 But the fish gate the sons of Asnaa built: they covered it, and set up the doors thereof, and the locks, and the bars.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
