<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Judges on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</title>
    <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/34-judges/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Judges on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:27 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/34-judges/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 1</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/34-judges/chap001/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:27 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/34-judges/chap001/</guid>
      <description>1 After the death of Joshua, the children of Israel consulted the Lord, saying: Who shall go up before us against the Chanaanite, and shall be the leader of the war?&#xA;2 And the Lord said: Juda shall go up: behold I have delivered the land into his hands.&#xA;3 And Juda said to Simeon, his brother: Come up with me into my lot, and fight against the Chanaanite, that I also may go along with thee into thy lot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 10</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/34-judges/chap010/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:27 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/34-judges/chap010/</guid>
      <description>1 After Abimelech, there arose a ruler in Israel, Thola, son of Phua, the uncle of Abimelech, a man of Issachar, who dwelt in Samir of mount Ephraim:&#xA;2 And he judged Israel three and twenty years, and he died, and was buried in Samir.&#xA;3 To him succeeded Jair, the Galaadite, who judged Israel for two and twenty years,&#xA;4 Having thirty sons, that rode on thirty ass colts, and were princes of thirty cities, which from his name were called Havoth Jair, that is, the towns of Jair, until this present day, in the land of Galaad.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 11</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/34-judges/chap011/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:27 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/34-judges/chap011/</guid>
      <description>1 There was at that time Jephte, the Galaadite, a most valiant man, and a warrior, the son of a woman that was a harlot, and his father was Galaad.&#xA;2 Now Galaad had a wife of whom he had sons: who, after they were grown up, thrust out Jephte, saying: Thou canst not inherit in the house of our father, because thou art born of another mother.&#xA;3 Then he fled and avoided them, and dwelt in the land of Tob: and there were gathered to him needy men and robbers, and they followed him as their prince.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 12</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/34-judges/chap012/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:27 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/34-judges/chap012/</guid>
      <description>1 But behold there arose a sedition in Ephraim. And passing towards the north, they said to Jephte: When thou wentest to fight against the children of Ammon, why wouldst thou not call us, that we might go with thee? Therefore we will burn thy house.&#xA;2 And he answered them: I and my people were at great strife with the children of Ammon: and I called you to assist me, and you would not do it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 13</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/34-judges/chap013/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:27 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/34-judges/chap013/</guid>
      <description>1 And the children of Israel did evil again in the sight of the Lord: and he delivered them into the hands of the Philistines forty years.&#xA;2 Now there was a certain man of Saraa, and of the race of Dan, whose name was Manue, and his wife was barren.&#xA;3 And an angel of the Lord appeared to her, and said: Thou art barren and without children: but thou shalt conceive and bear a son.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 14</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/34-judges/chap014/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:27 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/34-judges/chap014/</guid>
      <description>1 Then Samson went down to Thamnatha, and seeing there a woman of the daughters of the Philistines,&#xA;2 He came up, and told his father and his mother, saying: I saw a woman in Thamnatha of the daughters of the Philistines: I beseech you, take her for me to wife.&#xA;3 And his father and mother said to him: Is there no woman among the daughters of thy brethren, or among all my people, that thou wilt take a wife of the Philistines, who are uncircumcised?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 15</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/34-judges/chap015/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:27 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/34-judges/chap015/</guid>
      <description>1 And a while after, when the days of the wheat harvest were at hand, Samson came, meaning to visit his wife, and he brought her a kid of the flock. And when he would have gone into her chamber, as usual, her father would not suffer him, saying:&#xA;2 I thought thou hadst hated her, and therefore I gave her to thy friend: but she hath a sister, who is younger and fairer than she, take her to wife instead of her.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 16</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/34-judges/chap016/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:27 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/34-judges/chap016/</guid>
      <description>1 He went also into Gaza, and saw there a woman, a harlot, and went in unto her.&#xA;2 And when the Philistines had heard this, and it was noised about among them, that Samson was come into the city, they surrounded him, setting guards at the gate of the city, and watching there all the night in silence, that in the morning they might kill him as he went out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 17</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/34-judges/chap017/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:27 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/34-judges/chap017/</guid>
      <description>1 There was at that time a man of mount Ephraim, whose name was Michas.&#xA;2 Who said to his mother: The eleven hundred pieces of silver, which thou hadst put aside for thyself, and concerning which thou didst swear in my hearing, behold I have, and they are with me. And she said to him. Blessed be my son by the Lord.&#xA;3 So he restored them to his mother, who said to him: I have consecrated and vowed this silver to the Lord, that my son may receive it at my hand, and make a graven and a molten god; so now I deliver it to thee.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 18</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/34-judges/chap018/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:27 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/34-judges/chap018/</guid>
      <description>1 In those days there was no king in Israel, and the tribe of Dan sought them an inheritance to dwell in: for unto that day they had not received their lot among the other tribes.&#xA;2 So the children of Dan sent five most valiant men, of their stock and family, from Saraa and Esthaol, to spy out the land, and to view it diligently: and they said to them: Go, and view the land.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 19</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/34-judges/chap019/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:27 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/34-judges/chap019/</guid>
      <description>1 There was a certain Levite, who dwelt on the side of mount Ephraim, who took a wife of Bethlehem Juda:&#xA;2 And she left him, and returned to her father&amp;rsquo;s house in Bethlehem, and abode with him four months.&#xA;3 And her husband followed her, willing to be reconciled with her, and to speak kindly to her, and to bring her back with him, having with him a servant and two asses: and she received him, and brought him into her father&amp;rsquo;s house.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 2</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/34-judges/chap002/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:27 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/34-judges/chap002/</guid>
      <description>1 And an angel of the Lord went up from Galgal to the place of weepers, and said: I made you go out of Egypt, and have brought you into the land for which I swore to your fathers: and I promised that I would not make void my covenant with you for ever:&#xA;2 On condition that you should not make a league with the inhabitants of this land, but should throw down their altars: and you would not hear my voice: why have you done this?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 20</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/34-judges/chap020/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:27 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/34-judges/chap020/</guid>
      <description>1 Then all the children of Israel went out, and gathered together as one man, from Dan to Bersabee, with the land of Galaad, to the Lord in Maspha:&#xA;2 And all the chiefs of the people, and all the tribes of Israel, met together in the assembly of the people of God, four hundred thousand footmen fit for war.&#xA;3 (Nor were the children of Benjamin ignorant that the children of Israel were come up to Maspha.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 21</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/34-judges/chap021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:27 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/34-judges/chap021/</guid>
      <description>1 Now the children of Israel had also sworn in Maspha, saying: None of us shall give of his daughters to the children of Benjamin to wife.&#xA;2 And they all came to the house of God in Silo, and sitting before him till the evening, lifted up their voices, and began to lament and weep, saying:&#xA;3 O Lord God of Israel, why is so great an evil come to pass in thy people, that this day one tribe should be taken away from among us?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 3</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/34-judges/chap003/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:27 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/34-judges/chap003/</guid>
      <description>1 These are the nations which the Lord left, that by them he might instruct Israel, and all that had not known the wars of the Chanaanites:&#xA;2 That afterwards their children might learn to fight with their enemies, and to be trained up to war:&#xA;3 The five princes of the Philistines, and all the Chanaanites, and the Sidonians, and the Hevites that dwelt in Mount Libanus, from Mount Baal Hermon to the entering into Emath.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 4</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/34-judges/chap004/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:27 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/34-judges/chap004/</guid>
      <description>1 And the children of Israel again did evil in the sight of the Lord after the death of Aod:&#xA;2 And the Lord delivered them up into the hands of Jabin, king of Chanaan, who reigned in Asor: and he had a general of his army named Sisara, and he dwelt in Haroseth of the Gentiles.&#xA;3 And the children of Israel cried to the Lord: for he had nine hundred chariots set with scythes and for twenty years had grievously oppressed them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 5</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/34-judges/chap005/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:27 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/34-judges/chap005/</guid>
      <description>1 In that day Debbora and Barac, son of Abinoem, sung, and said:&#xA;2 O you of Israel, that have willingly offered your lives to danger, bless the Lord.&#xA;3 Hear, O ye kings, give ear, O ye princes: It is I, it is I, that will sing to the Lord, I will sing to the Lord, the God of Israel.&#xA;4 O Lord, when thou wentest out of Seir, and passedst by the regions of Edom, the earth trembled, and the heavens and clouds dropped water.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 6</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/34-judges/chap006/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:27 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/34-judges/chap006/</guid>
      <description>1 And the children of Israel again did evil in the sight of the Lord: and he delivered them into the hand of Madian seven years,&#xA;2 And they were grievously oppressed by them. And they made themselves dens and caves in the mountains, and strong holds to resist.&#xA;3 And when Israel had sown, Madian and Amalec, and the rest of the eastern nations, came up:&#xA;4 And pitching their tents among them, wasted all things as they were in the blade, even to the entrance of Gaza: and they left nothing at all in Israel for sustenance of life, nor sheep, nor oxen, nor asses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 7</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/34-judges/chap007/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:27 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/34-judges/chap007/</guid>
      <description>1 Then Jerobaal, who is the same as Gedeon, rising up early, and all the people with him, came to the fountain that is called Harad. Now the camp of Madian was in the valley, on the north side of the high hill.&#xA;2 And the Lord said to Gedeon: The people that are with thee are many, and Madian shall not be delivered into their hands: lest Israel should glory against me, and say: I was delivered by my own strength.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 8</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/34-judges/chap008/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:27 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/34-judges/chap008/</guid>
      <description>1 And the men of Ephraim said to him: What is this that thou meanest to do, that thou wouldst not call us, when thou wentest to fight against Madian? And they chid him sharply, and almost offered violence.&#xA;2 And he answered them: What could I have done like to that which you have done? Is not one bunch of grapes of Ephraim better than the vintages of Abiezer?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 9</title>
      <link>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/34-judges/chap009/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:27 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:42213/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/34-judges/chap009/</guid>
      <description>1 And Abimelech, the son of Jerobaal, went to Sichem, to his mother&amp;rsquo;s brethren, and spoke to them, and to all the kindred of his mother&amp;rsquo;s father, saying:&#xA;2 Speak to all the men of Sichem: whether is better for you that seventy men, all the sons of Jerobaal, should rule over you, or that one man should rule over you? And withal, consider that I am your bone, and your flesh.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
