<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Acts on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</title>
    <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/05-acts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Acts on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:24 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/05-acts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 1</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/05-acts/chap001/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:24 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/05-acts/chap001/</guid>
      <description>1 The former treatise I made, O Theophilus, of all things which Jesus began to do and to teach,&#xA;2 Until the day on which, giving commandments by the Holy Ghost to the apostles whom he had chosen, he was taken up.&#xA;3 To whom also he shewed himself alive after his passion, by many proofs, for forty days appearing to them, and speaking of the kingdom of God.&#xA;4 And eating together with them, he commanded them, that they should not depart from Jerusalem, but should wait for the promise of the Father, which you have heard (saith he) by my mouth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 10</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/05-acts/chap010/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:24 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/05-acts/chap010/</guid>
      <description>1 And there was a certain man in Caesarea, named Cornelius, a centurion of that which is called the Italian band:&#xA;2 A religious man, and fearing God with all his house, giving much alms to the people and always praying to God.&#xA;3 This man saw in a vision manifestly, about the ninth hour of the day, an angel of God coming in unto him and saying to him: Cornelius.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 11</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/05-acts/chap011/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:24 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/05-acts/chap011/</guid>
      <description>1 And the apostles and brethren, who were in Judea, heard that the Gentiles also had received the word of God.&#xA;2 And when Peter was come up to Jerusalem, they that were of the circumcision contended with him,&#xA;3 Saying: Why didst thou go in to men uncircumcised and didst eat with them?&#xA;4 But Peter began and declared to them the matter in order, saying:&#xA;5 I was in the city of Joppe praying: and I saw in an ecstasy of mind a vision, a certain vessel descending, as it were a great sheet let down from heaven by four corners.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 12</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/05-acts/chap012/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:24 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/05-acts/chap012/</guid>
      <description>1 And at the same time, Herod the king stretched forth his hands, to afflict some of the church.&#xA;2 And he killed James, the brother of John, With the sword.&#xA;3 And seeing that it pleased the Jews, he proceeded to take up Peter also. Now it was in the days of the Azymes.&#xA;4 And when he had apprehended him, he cast him into prison, delivering him to four files of soldiers, to be kept, intending, after the pasch, to bring him forth to the people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 13</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/05-acts/chap013/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:24 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/05-acts/chap013/</guid>
      <description>1 Now there were in the church which was at Antioch prophets and doctors, among whom was Barnabas and Simon who was called Niger, and Lucius of Cyrene and Manahen who was the foster brother of Herod the tetrarch, and Saul.&#xA;2 And as they were ministering to the Lord and fasting, the Holy Ghost said to them: Separate me Saul and Barnabas, for the work whereunto I have taken them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 14</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/05-acts/chap014/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:24 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/05-acts/chap014/</guid>
      <description>1 And it came to pass in Iconium that they entered together into the synagogue of the Jews and so spoke that a very great multitude both of the Jews and of the Greeks did believe.&#xA;2 But the unbelieving Jews stirred up and incensed the minds of the Gentiles against the brethren.&#xA;3 A long time therefore they abode there, dealing confidently in the Lord, who gave testimony to the word of his grace, granting signs and wonders to be done by their hands.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 15</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/05-acts/chap015/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:24 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/05-acts/chap015/</guid>
      <description>1 And some, coming down from Judea, taught the brethren: That, except you be circumcised after the manner of Moses, you cannot be saved.&#xA;2 And when Paul and Barnabas had no small contest with them, they determined that Paul and Barnabas and certain others of the other side should go up to the apostles and priests to Jerusalem, about this question.&#xA;3 They therefore, being brought on their way by the church, passed through Phenice and Samaria, relating the conversion of the Gentiles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 16</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/05-acts/chap016/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:24 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/05-acts/chap016/</guid>
      <description>1 And he came to Derbe and Lystra. And behold, there was a certain disciple there named Timothy, the son of a Jewish woman that believed: but his father was a Gentile.&#xA;2 To this man the brethren that were in Lystra and Iconium gave a good testimony.&#xA;3 Him Paul would have to go along with him: and taking him, he circumcised him, because of the Jews who were in those places.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 17</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/05-acts/chap017/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:24 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/05-acts/chap017/</guid>
      <description>1 And when they had passed through Amphipolis and Apollonia, they came to Thessalonica, where there was a synagogue of the Jews.&#xA;2 And Paul, according to his custom, went in unto them. And for three sabbath days he reasoned with them out of the scriptures:&#xA;3 Declaring and insinuating that the Christ was to suffer and to rise again from the dead; and that this is Jesus Christ, whom I preach to you.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 18</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/05-acts/chap018/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:24 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/05-acts/chap018/</guid>
      <description>1 After these things, departing from Athens, he came to Corinth.&#xA;2 And finding a certain Jew, named Aquila, born in Pontus, lately come from Italy, with Priscilla his wife (because that Claudius had commanded all Jews to depart from Rome), he came to them.&#xA;3 And because he was of the same trade, he remained with them and wrought. (Now they were tentmakers by trade.)&#xA;4 And he reasoned in the synagogue every sabbath, bringing in the name of the Lord Jesus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 19</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/05-acts/chap019/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:24 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/05-acts/chap019/</guid>
      <description>1 And it came to pass, while Apollo was at Corinth, that Paul, having passed through the upper coasts, came to Ephesus and found certain disciples.&#xA;2 And he said to them: Have you received the Holy Ghost since ye believed? But they said to him: We have not so much as heard whether there be a Holy Ghost.&#xA;3 And he said: In what then were you baptized? Who said: In John&amp;rsquo;s baptism.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 2</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/05-acts/chap002/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:24 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/05-acts/chap002/</guid>
      <description>1 And when the days of the Pentecost were accomplished, they were all together in one place:&#xA;2 And suddenly there came a sound from heaven, as of a mighty wind coming: and it filled the whole house where they were sitting.&#xA;3 And there appeared to them parted tongues, as it were of fire: and it sat upon every one of them.&#xA;4 And they were all filled with the Holy Ghost: and they began to speak with divers tongues, according as the Holy Ghost gave them to speak.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 20</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/05-acts/chap020/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:24 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/05-acts/chap020/</guid>
      <description>1 And after the tumult was ceased, Paul calling to him the disciples and exhorting them, took his leave and set forward to go into Macedonia.&#xA;2 And when he had gone over those parts and had exhorted them with many words, he came into Greece:&#xA;3 Where, when he had spent three months, the Jews laid wait for him, as he was about to sail into Syria. So he took a resolution to return through Macedonia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 21</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/05-acts/chap021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:24 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/05-acts/chap021/</guid>
      <description>1 And when it came to pass that, being parted from them, we set sail, we came with a straight course to Coos, and the day following to Rhodes: and from thence to Patara.&#xA;2 And when we had found a ship sailing over to Phenice, we went aboard and set forth.&#xA;3 And when we had discovered Cyprus, leaving it on the left hand, we sailed into Syria, and came to Tyre: for there the ship was to unlade her burden.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 22</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/05-acts/chap022/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:24 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/05-acts/chap022/</guid>
      <description>1 Men, brethren and fathers, hear ye the account which I now give unto you.&#xA;2 (And when they heard that he spoke to them in the Hebrew tongue, they kept the more silence.)&#xA;3 And he saith: I am a Jew, born at Tarsus in Cilicia, but brought up in this city, at the feet of Gamaliel, taught according to the truth of the law of the fathers, zealous for the law, as also all you are this day:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 23</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/05-acts/chap023/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:24 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/05-acts/chap023/</guid>
      <description>1 And Paul, looking upon the council, said: Men, brethren, I have conversed with all good conscience before God until this present day.&#xA;2 And the high priest, Ananias, commanded them that stood by him to strike him on the mouth.&#xA;3 Then Paul said to him: God shall strike thee, thou whited wall. For, sittest thou to judge me according to the law and, contrary to the law, commandest me to be struck?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 24</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/05-acts/chap024/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:24 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/05-acts/chap024/</guid>
      <description>1 And after five days, the high priest, Ananias, came down with some ancients and one Tertullus, an orator, who went to the governor against Paul.&#xA;2 And Paul being called for, Tertullus began to accuse him, saying: Whereas, through thee we live in much peace and many things are rectified by thy providence,&#xA;3 We accept it always and in all places, most excellent Felix, with all thanksgiving.&#xA;4 But that I be no further tedious to thee, I desire thee of thy clemency to hear us in a few words.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 25</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/05-acts/chap025/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:24 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/05-acts/chap025/</guid>
      <description>1 Now when Festus was come into the province, after three days, he went up to Jerusalem from Cesarea.&#xA;2 And the chief priests and principal men of the Jews went unto him against Paul: and they besought him,&#xA;3 Requesting favour against him, that he would command him to be brought to Jerusalem, laying wait to kill him in the way.&#xA;4 But Festus answered: That Paul was kept in Caesarea: and that he himself would very shortly depart thither.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 26</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/05-acts/chap026/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:24 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/05-acts/chap026/</guid>
      <description>1 Then Agrippa said to Paul: Thou art permitted to speak for thyself. Then Paul, stretching forth his hand, began to make his answer.&#xA;2 I think myself happy, O king Agrippa, that I am to answer for myself this day before thee, touching all the things whereof I am accused by the Jews.&#xA;3 Especially as thou knowest all, both customs and questions, that are among the Jews. Wherefore I beseech thee to hear me patiently.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 27</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/05-acts/chap027/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:24 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/05-acts/chap027/</guid>
      <description>1 And when it was determined that he should sail into Italy and that Paul, with the other prisoners, should be delivered to a centurion, named Julius, of the band Augusta,&#xA;2 Going on board a ship of Adrumetum, we launched, meaning to sail by the coasts of Asia, Aristarchus, the Macedonian of Thessalonica, continuing with us.&#xA;3 And the day following, we came to Sidon. And Julius, treating Paul courteously, permitted him to go to his friends and to take care of himself.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 28</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/05-acts/chap028/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:24 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/05-acts/chap028/</guid>
      <description>1 And when we had escaped, then we knew that the island was called Melita. But the barbarians shewed us no small courtesy.&#xA;2 For kindling a fire, they refreshed us all, because of the present rain and of the cold.&#xA;3 And when Paul had gathered together a bundle of sticks and had laid them on the fire, a viper, coming out of the heat, fastened on his hand.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 3</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/05-acts/chap003/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:24 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/05-acts/chap003/</guid>
      <description>1 Now Peter and John went up into the temple at the ninth hour of prayer.&#xA;2 And a certain man who was lame from his mother&amp;rsquo;s womb was carried: whom they laid every day at the gate of the temple, which is called Beautiful, that he might ask alms of them that went into the temple.&#xA;3 He, when he had seen Peter and John, about to go into the temple, asked to receive an alms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 4</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/05-acts/chap004/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:24 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/05-acts/chap004/</guid>
      <description>1 And as they were speaking to the people the priests and the officer of the temple and the Sadducees came upon them,&#xA;2 Being grieved that they taught the people and preached in Jesus the resurrection from the dead:&#xA;3 And they laid hands upon them and put them in hold till the next day: for it was now evening.&#xA;4 But many of them who had heard the word believed: and the number of the men was made five thousand.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 5</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/05-acts/chap005/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:24 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/05-acts/chap005/</guid>
      <description>1 But a certain man named Ananias, with Saphira his wife, sold a piece of land,&#xA;2 And by fraud kept back part of the price of the land, his wife being privy thereunto: and bringing a certain part of it, laid it at the feet of the apostles.&#xA;3 But Peter said: Ananias, why hath Satan tempted thy heart, that thou shouldst lie to the Holy Ghost and by fraud keep part of the price of the land?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 6</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/05-acts/chap006/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:24 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/05-acts/chap006/</guid>
      <description>1 And in those days, the number of the disciples increasing, there arose a murmuring of the Greeks against the Hebrews, for that their widows were neglected in the daily ministration.&#xA;2 Then the twelve, calling together the multitude of the disciples, said: It is not reason that we should leave the word of God and serve tables.&#xA;3 Wherefore, brethren, look ye out among you seven men of good reputation, full of the Holy Ghost and wisdom, whom we may appoint over this business.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 7</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/05-acts/chap007/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:24 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/05-acts/chap007/</guid>
      <description>1 Then the high priest said: Are these things so?&#xA;2 Who said: Ye men, brethren and fathers, hear. The God of glory appeared to our father Abraham, when he was in Mesopotamia, before he dwelt in Charan.&#xA;3 And said to him: Go forth out of thy country and from thy kindred: and come into the land which I shall shew thee.&#xA;4 Then he went out of the land of the Chaldeans and dwelt in Charan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 8</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/05-acts/chap008/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:24 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/05-acts/chap008/</guid>
      <description>1 And at that time, there was raised a great persecution against the church which was at Jerusalem. And they were all dispersed through the countries of Judea, and Samaria, except the apostles.&#xA;2 And devout men took order for Stephen&amp;rsquo;s funeral and made great mourning over him.&#xA;3 But Saul made havock of the church, entering in from house to house: and dragging away men and women, committed them to prison.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 9</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/05-acts/chap009/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:24 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/05-acts/chap009/</guid>
      <description>1 And Saul, as yet breathing out threatenings and slaughter against the disciples of the Lord, went to the high priest&#xA;2 And asked of him letters to Damascus, to the synagogues: that if he found any men and women of this way, he might bring them bound to Jerusalem.&#xA;3 And as he went on his journey, it came to pass that he drew nigh to Damascus. And suddenly a light from heaven shined round about him.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
