<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>1 Kings on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/38-1-kings/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 1 Kings on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:28 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/38-1-kings/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 10</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/38-1-kings/chap010/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:28 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/38-1-kings/chap010/</guid>
      <description>1 And the queen of Saba having heard of the fame of Solomon in the name of the Lord, came to try him with hard questions.&#xA;2 And entering into Jerusalem with a great train, and riches, and camels that carried spices, and an immense quantity of gold, and precious stones, she came to king Solomon, and spoke to him all that she had in her heart.&#xA;3 And Solomon informed her of all the things she proposed to him: there was not any word the king was ignorant of, and which he could not answer her.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 11</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/38-1-kings/chap011/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:28 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/38-1-kings/chap011/</guid>
      <description>1 And king Solomon loved many strange women, besides the daughter of Pharao, and women of Moab, and of Ammon, and of Edom, and of Sidon, and of the Hethites:&#xA;2 Of the nations concerning which the Lord said to the children of Israel: You shall not go in unto them, neither shall any of them come into yours: for they will most certainly turn away your hearts to follow their gods.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 12</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/38-1-kings/chap012/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:28 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/38-1-kings/chap012/</guid>
      <description>1 And Roboam went to Sichem: for thither were all Israel come together to make him king.&#xA;2 But Jeroboam, the son of Nabat, who was yet in Egypt, a fugitive from the face of king Solomon, hearing of his death, returned out of Egypt.&#xA;3 And they sent and called him: and Jeroboam came, and all the multitude of Israel, and they spoke to Roboam, saying:&#xA;4 Thy father laid a grievous yoke upon us: now, therefore, do thou take off a little of the grievous service of thy father, and of his most heavy yoke, which he put upon us, and we will serve thee.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 13</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/38-1-kings/chap013/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:28 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/38-1-kings/chap013/</guid>
      <description>1 And behold there came a man of God out of Juda, by the word of the Lord, to Bethel, when Jeroboam was standing upon the altar, and burning incense.&#xA;2 And he cried out against the altar in the word of the Lord, and said: O altar, altar, thus saith the Lord: Behold a child shall be born to the house of David, Josias by name, and he shall immolate upon thee the priests of the high places, who now burn incense upon thee, and he shall burn men&amp;rsquo;s bones upon thee.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 14</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/38-1-kings/chap014/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:28 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/38-1-kings/chap014/</guid>
      <description>1 At that time Abia, the son of Jeroboam, fell sick.&#xA;2 And Jeroboam said to his wife: Arise, and change thy dress, that thou be not known to be the wife of Jeroboam, and go to Silo, where Ahias, the prophet is, who told me that I should reign over this people.&#xA;3 Take also with thee ten loaves, and cracknels, and a pot of honey, and go to him: for he will tell thee what will become of this child.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 15</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/38-1-kings/chap015/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:28 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/38-1-kings/chap015/</guid>
      <description>1 Now in the eighteenth year of the reign of Jeroboam, the son of Nabat, Abiam reigned over Juda.&#xA;2 He reigned three years in Jerusalem: the name of his mother was Maacha, the daughter of Abessalom.&#xA;3 And he walked in all the sins of his father, which he had done before him: and his heart was not perfect with the Lord his God, as was the heart of David, his father.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 16</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/38-1-kings/chap016/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:28 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/38-1-kings/chap016/</guid>
      <description>1 Then the word of the Lord came to Jehu, the son of Hanani, against Baasa, saying:&#xA;2 For as much as I have exalted thee out of the dust and made thee prince over my people Israel, and thou hast walked in the way of Jeroboam, and hast made my people Israel to sin, to provoke me to anger with their sins:&#xA;3 Behold I will cut down the posterity of Baasa, and the posterity of his house, and I will make thy house as the house of Jeroboam, the son of Nabat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 17</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/38-1-kings/chap017/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:28 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/38-1-kings/chap017/</guid>
      <description>1 And Elias the Thesbite, of the inhabitants of Galaad, said to Achab: As the Lord liveth, the God of Israel, in whose sight I stand, there shall not be dew nor rain these years, but according to the words of my mouth.&#xA;2 And the word of the Lord came to him, saying:&#xA;3 Get thee hence, and go towards the east, and hide thyself by the torrent of Carith, which is over against the Jordan;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 18</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/38-1-kings/chap018/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:28 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/38-1-kings/chap018/</guid>
      <description>1 After many days, the word of the Lord came to Elias, in the third year, saying: Go, and shew thyself to Achab, that I may give rain upon the face of the earth.&#xA;2 And Elias went to shew himself to Achab, and there was a grievous famine in Samaria.&#xA;3 And Achab called Abdias the governor of his house: now Abdias feared the Lord very much.&#xA;4 For when Jezabel killed the prophets of the Lord, he took a hundred prophets, and hid them by fifty and fifty in caves, and fed them with bread and water.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 19</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/38-1-kings/chap019/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:28 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/38-1-kings/chap019/</guid>
      <description>1 And Achab told Jezabel all that Elias had done, and how he had slain all the prophets with the sword.&#xA;2 And Jezabel sent a messenger to Elias, saying: Such and such things may the gods do to me, and add still more, if by this hour to morrow I make not thy life as the life of one of them.&#xA;3 Then EIias was afraid, and rising up, he went whithersoever he had a mind: and he came to Bersabee of Juda, and left his servant there,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 20</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/38-1-kings/chap020/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:28 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/38-1-kings/chap020/</guid>
      <description>1 And Benadad, king of Syria, gathered together all his host, and there were two and thirty kings with him, and horses, and chariots: and going up, he fought against Samaria, and besieged it.&#xA;2 And sending messengers to Achab, king of Israel, into the city,&#xA;3 He said: Thus saith Benadad: Thy silver and thy gold is mine: and thy wives and thy goodliest children are mine.&#xA;4 And the king of Israel answered: According to thy word, my lord, O king, I am thine, and all that I have.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 21</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/38-1-kings/chap021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:28 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/38-1-kings/chap021/</guid>
      <description>1 And after these things, Naboth the Jezrahelite, who was in Jezrahel, had at that time a vineyard, near the palace of Achab, king of Samaria.&#xA;2 And Achab spoke to Naboth, saying: Give me thy vineyard, that I may make me a garden of herbs, because it is nigh, and adjoining to my house; and I will give thee for it a better vineyard: or if thou think it more convenient for thee, I will give thee the worth of it in money.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 22</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/38-1-kings/chap022/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:28 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/38-1-kings/chap022/</guid>
      <description>1 And there passed three years without war between Syria and Israel.&#xA;2 And in the third year, Josaphat, king of Juda, came down to the king of Israel.&#xA;3 (And the king of Israel said to his servants: Know ye not that Ramoth Galaad is ours, and we neglect to take it out of the hand of the king of Syria?)&#xA;4 And he said to Josaphat: Wilt thou come with me to battle to Ramoth Galaad?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 8</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/38-1-kings/chap008/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:28 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/38-1-kings/chap008/</guid>
      <description>1 Then all the ancients of Israel, with the princes of the tribes, and the heads of the families of the children of Israel, were assembled to king Solomon, in Jerusalem: that they might carry the ark of the covenant of the Lord, out of the city of David, that is, out of Sion.&#xA;2 And all Israel assembled themselves to king Solomon, on the festival day, in the month of Ethanim, the same is the seventh month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 9</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/38-1-kings/chap009/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:28 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/38-1-kings/chap009/</guid>
      <description>1 And it came to pass when Solomon had finished the building of the house of the Lord, and the king&amp;rsquo;s house, and all that he desired and was pleased to do,&#xA;2 That the Lord appeared to him the second time, as he had appeared to him in Gabaon.&#xA;3 And the Lord said to him: I have heard thy prayer and thy supplication, which thou hast made before me: I have sanctified this house, which thou hast built, to put my name there for ever; and my eyes, and my heart, shall be there always.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 1</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/38-1-kings/chap001/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:27 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/38-1-kings/chap001/</guid>
      <description>1 Now king David was old, and advanced in years: and when he was covered with clothes he was not warm.&#xA;2 His servants therefore, said to him: Let us seek for our Lord the king, a young virgin, and let her stand before the king, and cherish him, and sleep in his bosom and warm our lord the king.&#xA;3 So they sought a beautiful young woman, in all the coasts of Israel and they found Abisag, a Sunamitess, and brought her to the king.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 2</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/38-1-kings/chap002/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:27 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/38-1-kings/chap002/</guid>
      <description>1 And the days of David drew nigh that he should die, and he charged his son Solomon, saying:&#xA;2 I am going the way of all flesh: take thou courage and shew thyself a man.&#xA;3 And keep the charge of the Lord thy God, to walk in his ways, and observe his ceremonies, and his precepts, and judgments, and testimonies, as it is written in the law of Moses: that thou mayst understand all thou dost, and whithersoever thou shalt turn thyself:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 3</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/38-1-kings/chap003/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:27 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/38-1-kings/chap003/</guid>
      <description>1 And the kingdom was established in the hand of Solomon, and he made affinity with Pharao, the king of Egypt: for he took his daughter, and brought her into the city of David: until he had made an end of building his own house, and the house of the Lord, and the wall of Jerusalem round about.&#xA;2 But yet the people sacrificed in the high places: for there was no temple built to the name of the Lord until that day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 4</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/38-1-kings/chap004/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:27 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/38-1-kings/chap004/</guid>
      <description>1 And king Solomon reigned over all Israel:&#xA;2 And these were the princes which he had: Azarias, the son of Sadoc, the priest:&#xA;3 Elihoreph, and Ahia, the sons of Sisa, scribes: Josaphat, the son of Ahilud, recorder:&#xA;4 Banaias, the son of Joiada, over the army: and Sadoc, and Abiathar, priests.&#xA;5 Azarias, the son of Nathan, over them that were about the king: Zabud, the son of Nathan, the priest, the king&amp;rsquo;s friend:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 5</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/38-1-kings/chap005/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:27 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/38-1-kings/chap005/</guid>
      <description>1 And Hiram, king of Tyre, sent his servants to Solomon: for he heard that they had anointed him king in the room of his father: for Hiram had always been David&amp;rsquo;s friend.&#xA;2 Solomon sent to Hiram, saying:&#xA;3 Thou knowest the will of David, my father, and that he could not build a house to the name of the Lord his God, because of the wars that were round about him, until the Lord put them under the soles of his feet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 6</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/38-1-kings/chap006/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:27 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/38-1-kings/chap006/</guid>
      <description>1 And it came to pass in the four hundred and eightieth year after the children of Israel came out of the land of Egypt, in the fourth year of the reign of Solomon over Israel, in the month Zio, (the same is the second month) he began to build a house to the Lord.&#xA;2 And the house, which king Solomon built to the Lord, was threescore cubits in length, and twenty cubits in breadth, and thirty cubits in height.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 7</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/38-1-kings/chap007/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:27 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/38-1-kings/chap007/</guid>
      <description>1 And Solomon built his own house in thirteen years, and brought it to perfection.&#xA;2 He built also the house of the forest of Libanus; the length of it was a hundred cubits, and the breadth fifty cubits, and the height thirty cubits: and four galleries between pillars of cedar: for he had cut cedar trees into pillars.&#xA;3 And he covered the whole vault with boards of cedar, and it was held up with five and forty pillars.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
