<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>1 Peter on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/21-1-peter/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 1 Peter on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:25 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/21-1-peter/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 1</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/21-1-peter/chap001/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:25 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/21-1-peter/chap001/</guid>
      <description>1 Peter, an apostle of Jesus Christ, to the strangers dispersed through Pontus, Cappadocia, Asia and Bithynia, elect,&#xA;2 According to the foreknowledge of God the Father, unto the sanctification of the Spirit, unto obedience and sprinkling of the blood of Jesus Christ. Grace unto you and peace be multiplied.&#xA;3 Blessed be the God and Father of our Lord Jesus Christ, who according to his great mercy hath regenerated us unto a lively hope, by the resurrection of Jesus Christ from the dead:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 2</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/21-1-peter/chap002/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:25 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/21-1-peter/chap002/</guid>
      <description>1 Wherefore laying away all malice and all guile and dissimulations and envies and all detractions,&#xA;2 As newborn babes, desire the rational milk without guile, that thereby you may grow unto salvation:&#xA;3 If so be you have tasted that the Lord is sweet.&#xA;4 Unto whom coming, as to a living stone, rejected indeed by men but chosen and made honourable by God:&#xA;5 Be you also as living stones built up, a spiritual house, a holy priesthood, to offer up spiritual sacrifices, acceptable to God by Jesus Christ.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 3</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/21-1-peter/chap003/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:25 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/21-1-peter/chap003/</guid>
      <description>1 In like manner also, let wives be subject to their husbands: that, if any believe not the word, they may be won without the word, by the conversation of the wives,&#xA;2 Considering your chaste conversation with fear.&#xA;3 Whose adorning, let it not be the outward plaiting of the hair, or the wearing of gold, or the putting on of apparel:&#xA;4 But the hidden man of the heart, in the incorruptibility of a quiet and a meek spirit which is rich in the sight of God.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 4</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/21-1-peter/chap004/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:25 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/21-1-peter/chap004/</guid>
      <description>1 Christ therefore having suffered in the flesh, be you also armed with the same thought: for he that hath suffered in the flesh hath ceased from sins:&#xA;2 That now he may live the rest of his time in the flesh, not after the desires of men but according to the will of God.&#xA;3 For the time past is sufficient to have fulfilled the will of the Gentiles, for them who have walked in riotousness, lusts, excess of wine, revellings, banquetings and unlawful worshipping of idols.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 5</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/21-1-peter/chap005/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:25 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/bible/douay-rheims/new-testament/21-1-peter/chap005/</guid>
      <description>1 The ancients therefore that are among you, I beseech who am myself also an ancient and a witness of the sufferings of Christ, as also a partaker of that glory which is to be revealed in time to come:&#xA;2 Feed the flock of God which is among you, taking care of it, not by constraint but willingly, according to God: not for filthy lucre&amp;rsquo;s sake but voluntarily:&#xA;3 Neither as lording it over the clergy but being made a pattern of the flock from the heart.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
