<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Zephaniah on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/68-zephaniah/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Zephaniah on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/68-zephaniah/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 1</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/68-zephaniah/chap001/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/68-zephaniah/chap001/</guid>
      <description>1 The word of the Lord that came to Zephaniah the son of Chusi, the son of Godolias, the son of Amarias, the son of Ezechias, in the days of Josias, the son of Amon king of Juda.&#xA;2 Gathering, I will gather together all things from off the face of the land, saith the Lord:&#xA;3 I will gather man, and beast, I will gather the birds of the air, and the fishes of the sea: and the ungodly shall meet with ruin: and I will destroy men from off the face of the land, saith the Lord.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 2</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/68-zephaniah/chap002/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/68-zephaniah/chap002/</guid>
      <description>1Assemble yourselves together, be gathered together, O nation not worthy to be loved:&#xA;2 Before the decree bring forth the day as dust passing away, before the fierce anger of the Lord come upon you, before the day of the Lord&amp;rsquo;s indignation come upon you.&#xA;3 Seek the Lord, all ye meek of the earth, you that have wrought his judgment: seek the just, seek the meek: if by any means you may be hid in the day of the Lord&amp;rsquo;s indignation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 3</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/68-zephaniah/chap003/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/68-zephaniah/chap003/</guid>
      <description>1 Woe to the provoking and redeemed city, the dove.&#xA;2 She hath not hearkened to the voice, neither hath she received discipline: she hath not trusted in the Lord, she drew not near to her God.&#xA;3 Her princes are in the midst of her as roaring lions: her judges are evening wolves, they left nothing for the morning.&#xA;4 Her prophets are senseless, men without faith: her priests have polluted the sanctuary, they have acted unjustly against the law.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
