<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jonah on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/64-jonah/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Jonah on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/64-jonah/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 1</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/64-jonah/chap001/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/64-jonah/chap001/</guid>
      <description>1 Now the word of the Lord came to Jonah, the son of Amathi, saying:&#xA;2 Arise and go to Ninive, the great city, and preach in it: For the wickedness thereof is come up before me.&#xA;3 And Jonah rose up to flee into Tharsis from the face of the Lord, and he went down to Joppe, and found a ship going to Tharsis: and he paid the fare thereof, and went down into it, to go with them to Tharsis from the face of the Lord,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 2</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/64-jonah/chap002/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/64-jonah/chap002/</guid>
      <description>1 Now the Lord prepared a great fish to swallow up Jonah: and Jonah was in the belly of a fish for three days and three nights.&#xA;2 And Jonah prayed to the Lord, his God, out of the belly of the fish.&#xA;3 And he said: I cried out of my affliction to the Lord, and he heard me: I cried out of the belly of hell, and thou hast heard my voice.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 3</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/64-jonah/chap003/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/64-jonah/chap003/</guid>
      <description>1 And the word of the Lord came to Jonah the second time saying:&#xA;2 Arise, and go to Ninive, the great city: and preach in it the preaching that I bid thee.&#xA;3 And Jonah arose, and went to Ninive, according to the word of the Lord: now Ninive was a great city of three days&amp;rsquo; journey.&#xA;4 And Jonah began to enter into the city one day&amp;rsquo;s journey: and he cried and said: Yet forty days and Ninive shall be destroyed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 4</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/64-jonah/chap004/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/64-jonah/chap004/</guid>
      <description>1 And Jonah was exceedingly troubled, and was angry:&#xA;2 And he prayed to the Lord, and said: I beseech thee, O Lord, is not this what I said, when I was yet in my own country? therefore I went before to flee into Tharsis: for I know that thou art a gracious and merciful God, patient, and of much compassion, and easy to forgive evil.&#xA;3 And now, O Lord, I beseech thee take my life from me: for it is better for me to die than to live.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
