<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>1 Samuel on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</title>
    <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/36-1-samuel/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 1 Samuel on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:27 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/36-1-samuel/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 1</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/36-1-samuel/chap001/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:27 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/36-1-samuel/chap001/</guid>
      <description>1 There was a man of Ramathaimsophim, of Mount Ephraim, and his name was Elcana, the son of Jeroham, the son of Eliu, the son of Thohu, the son of Suph, an Ephraimite:&#xA;2 And he had two wives, the name of one was Anna, and the name of the other Phenenna. Phenenna had children: but Anna had no children.&#xA;3 And this man went up out of his city upon the appointed days, to adore and to offer sacrifice to the Lord of hosts in Silo.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 10</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/36-1-samuel/chap010/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:27 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/36-1-samuel/chap010/</guid>
      <description>1 And Samuel took a little vial of oil, and poured it upon his head, and kissed him, and said: Behold, the Lord hath anointed thee to be prince over his inheritance, and thou shalt deliver his people out of the hands of their enemies, that are round about them. And this shall be a sign unto thee, that God hath anointed thee to be prince.&#xA;2 When thou shalt depart from me this day, thou shalt find two men by the sepulchre of Rachel in the borders of Benjamin to the south, and they shall say to thee: The asses are found which thou wentest to seek: and thy father, thinking no more of the asses, is concerned for you, and saith: What shall I do for my son?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 11</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/36-1-samuel/chap011/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:27 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/36-1-samuel/chap011/</guid>
      <description>1 And it came to pass about a month after this, that Naas, the Ammonite, came up, and began to fight against Jabes Galaad. And all the men of Jabes said to Naas: Make a covenant with us, and we will serve thee.&#xA;2 And Naas, the Ammonite, answered them: On this condition will I make a covenant with you, that I may pluck out all your right eyes, and make you a reproach in all Israel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 12</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/36-1-samuel/chap012/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:27 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/36-1-samuel/chap012/</guid>
      <description>1 And Samuel said to all Israel: Behold I have hearkened to your voice in all that you said to me, and have made a king over you.&#xA;2 And now the king goeth before you: but I am old and greyheaded: and my sons are with you: having then conversed with you from my youth until this day, behold here I am.&#xA;3 Speak of me before the Lord, and before his anointed, whether I have taken any man&amp;rsquo;s ox, or ass: if I have wronged any man, if I have oppressed any man, if I have taken a bribe at any man&amp;rsquo;s hand: and I will despise it this day, and will restore it to you.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 13</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/36-1-samuel/chap013/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:27 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/36-1-samuel/chap013/</guid>
      <description>1 Saul was a child of one year when he began to reign, and he reigned two years over Israel.&#xA;2 And Saul chose him three thousand men of Israel: and two thousand were with Saul in Machmas, and in mount Bethel: and a thousand with Jonathan in Gabaa of Benjamin: and the rest of the people he sent back every man to their dwellings.&#xA;3 And Jonathan smote the garrison of the Philistines which was in Gabaa.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 14</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/36-1-samuel/chap014/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:27 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/36-1-samuel/chap014/</guid>
      <description>1 Now it came to pass one day that Jonathan, the son of Saul, said to the young man that bore his armour: Come, and let us go over to the garrison of the Philistines, which is on the other side of yonder place. But he told not this to his father.&#xA;2 And Saul abode in the uttermost part of Gabaa, under the pomegranate tree, which was in Magron: and the people with him were about six hundred men.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 15</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/36-1-samuel/chap015/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:27 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/36-1-samuel/chap015/</guid>
      <description>1 And Samuel said to Saul: The Lord sent me to anoint thee king over his people Israel: now therefore hearken thou unto the voice of the Lord:&#xA;2 Thus saith the Lord of hosts: I have reckoned up all that Amalec hath done to Israel: how he opposed them in the way when they came up out of Egypt.&#xA;3 Now therefore go, and smite Amalec, and utterly destroy all that he hath: spare him not, nor covet anything that is his: but slay both man and woman, child and suckling, ox and sheep, camel and ass.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 16</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/36-1-samuel/chap016/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:27 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/36-1-samuel/chap016/</guid>
      <description>1 And the Lord said to Samuel: How long wilt thou mourn for Saul, whom I have rejected from reigning over Israel? fill thy horn with oil, and come, that I may send thee to Isai, the Bethlehemite: for I have provided me a king among his sons.&#xA;2 And Samuel said: How shall I go? for Saul will hear of it, and he will kill me. And the Lord said: Thou shalt take with thee a calf of the herd, and thou shalt say: I am come to sacrifice to the Lord.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 17</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/36-1-samuel/chap017/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:27 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/36-1-samuel/chap017/</guid>
      <description>1 Now the Philistines gathering together their troops to battle, assembled at Socho of Juda: and camped between Socho and Azeca, in the borders of Dommim.&#xA;2 And Saul and the children of Israel being gathered together, came to the valley of Terebinth, and they set the army in array to fight against the Philistines.&#xA;3 And the Philistines stood on a mountain on the one side, and Israel stood on a mountain on the other side: and there was a valley between them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 18</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/36-1-samuel/chap018/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:27 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/36-1-samuel/chap018/</guid>
      <description>1 And it came to pass, when he had made an end of speaking to Saul, the son of Jonathan was knit with the soul of David, and Jonathan loved him as his own soul.&#xA;2 And Saul took him that day, and would not let him return to his father&amp;rsquo;s house.&#xA;3 And David and Jonathan made a covenant, for he loved him as his own soul.&#xA;4 And Jonathan stripped himself of the coat with which he was clothed, and gave it to David, and the rest of his garments, even to his sword, and to his bow, and to his girdle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 19</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/36-1-samuel/chap019/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:27 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/36-1-samuel/chap019/</guid>
      <description>1 And Saul spoke to Jonathan, his son, and to all his servants, that they should kill David. But Jonathan, the son of Saul, loved David exceedingly.&#xA;2 And Jonathan told David, saying: Saul, my father, seeketh to kill thee: wherefore look to thyself, I beseech thee, in the morning and thou shalt abide in a secret place, and shalt be hid.&#xA;3 And I will go out and stand beside my father in the field where thou art: and I will speak of thee to my father, and whatsoever I shall see, I will tell thee.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 2</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/36-1-samuel/chap002/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:27 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/36-1-samuel/chap002/</guid>
      <description>1 My heart hath rejoiced in the Lord, and my horn is exalted in my God: my mouth is enlarged over my enemies: because I have joyed in thy salvation.&#xA;2 There is none holy as the Lord is: for there is no other beside thee, and there is none strong like our God.&#xA;3 Do not multiply to speak lofty things, boasting: let old matters depart from your mouth: for the Lord is a God of all knowledge, and to him are thoughts prepared.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 20</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/36-1-samuel/chap020/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:27 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/36-1-samuel/chap020/</guid>
      <description>1 But David fled from Najoth, which is in Ramatha, and came and said to Jonathan: What have I done? what is my iniquity, and what is my sin against thy father, that he seeketh my life?&#xA;2 And he said to him: (God forbid, thou shalt not die: for my father will do nothing, great or little, without first telling me: hath then my father hid this word only from me?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 21</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/36-1-samuel/chap021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:27 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/36-1-samuel/chap021/</guid>
      <description>1 And David came to Nobe, to Achimelech, the priest and Achimelech was astonished at David&amp;rsquo;s coming. And he said to him: Why art thou alone, and no man with thee?&#xA;2 And David said to Achimelech, the priest: The king hath commanded me a business, and said: Let no man know the thing for which thou art sent by me, and what manner of commands I have given thee: and I have appointed my servants to such and such a place.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 22</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/36-1-samuel/chap022/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:27 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/36-1-samuel/chap022/</guid>
      <description>1 David therefore went from thence, and fled to the cave of Odollam. And when his brethren, and all his father&amp;rsquo;s house, had heard of it, they went down to him thither.&#xA;2 And all that were in distress, and oppressed with debt, and under affliction of mind, gathered themselves unto him: and he became their prince, and there were with him about four hundred men.&#xA;3 And David departed from thence into Maspha of Moab: and he said to the king of Moab: Let my father and my mother tarry with you, I beseech thee, till I know what God will do for me.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 23</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/36-1-samuel/chap023/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:27 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/36-1-samuel/chap023/</guid>
      <description>1 And they told David, saying: Behold the Philistines fight against Ceila, and they rob the barns.&#xA;2 Therefore David consulted the Lord, saying: Shall I go and smite these Philistines? And the Lord said to David: Go, and thou shalt smite the Philistines, and shalt save Ceila.&#xA;3 And the men that were with David, said to him: Behold we are in fear here in Judea, how much more if we go to Ceila against the bands of the Philistines?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 24</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/36-1-samuel/chap024/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:27 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/36-1-samuel/chap024/</guid>
      <description>1 Then David went up from thence, and dwelt in strong holds of Engaddi.&#xA;2 And when Saul was returned from following the Philistines, they told him, saying: Behold, David is in the desert of Engaddi.&#xA;3 Saul, therefore, took three thousand chosen men out of all Israel, and went out to seek after David and his men, even upon the most craggy rocks, which are accessible only to wild goats.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 25</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/36-1-samuel/chap025/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:27 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/36-1-samuel/chap025/</guid>
      <description>1 And Samuel died, and all Israel was gathered together, and they mourned for him, and buried him in his house in Ramatha. And David rose, and went down into the wilderness of Pharan.&#xA;2 Now there was a certain man in the wilderness of Maon, and his possessions were in Carmel, and the man was very great: and he had three thousand sheep, and a thousand goats: and it happened that he was shearing his sheep in Carmel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 26</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/36-1-samuel/chap026/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:27 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/36-1-samuel/chap026/</guid>
      <description>1 And the men of Ziph came to Saul in Gabaa, saying: Behold David is hid in the hill of Hachila, which is over against the wilderness.&#xA;2 And Saul arose, and went down to the wilderness of Ziph having with him three thousand chosen men of Israel, to seek David in the wilderness of Ziph.&#xA;3 And Saul encamped in Gabaa Hachila, which was over against the wilderness in the way: and David abode in the wilderness.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 27</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/36-1-samuel/chap027/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:27 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/36-1-samuel/chap027/</guid>
      <description>1 And David said in his heart: I shall one day or other fall into the hands of Saul: is it not better for me to flee, and to be saved in the land of the Philistines, that Saul may despair of me, and cease to seek me in all the coasts of Israel? I will flee then out of his hands.&#xA;2 And David arose, and went away, both he and the six hundred men that were with him, to Achis, the son of Maoch, king of Geth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 28</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/36-1-samuel/chap028/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:27 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/36-1-samuel/chap028/</guid>
      <description>1 And it came to pass in those days, that the Philistines gathered together their armies, to be prepared for war against Israel: And Achis said to David: Know thou now assuredly, that thou shalt go out with me to the war, thou, and thy men.&#xA;2 And David said to Achis: Now thou shalt know what thy servant will do. And Achis said to David: And I will appoint thee to guard my life for ever.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 29</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/36-1-samuel/chap029/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:27 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/36-1-samuel/chap029/</guid>
      <description>1 Now all the troops of the Philistines were gathered together to Aphec: and Israel also encamped by the fountain, which is in Jezrahel.&#xA;2 And the lords of the Philistines marched with their hundreds and their thousands: but David and his men were in the rear with Achis.&#xA;3 And the princes of the Philistines said to Achis: What mean these Hebrews? And Achis said to the princes of the Philistines: Do you not know David who was the servant of Saul, the king of Israel, and hath been with me many days, or years, and I have found no fault in him, since the day that he fled over to me until this day?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 3</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/36-1-samuel/chap003/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:27 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/36-1-samuel/chap003/</guid>
      <description>1 Now the child Samuel ministered to the Lord before Heli, and the word of the Lord was precious in those days, there was no manifest vision.&#xA;2 And it came to pass one day when Heli lay in his place, and his eyes were grown dim, that he could not see:&#xA;3 Before the lamp of God went out, Samuel slept in the temple of the Lord, where the ark of God was.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 30</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/36-1-samuel/chap030/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:27 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/36-1-samuel/chap030/</guid>
      <description>1 Now when David and his men were come to Siceleg on the third day, the Amalecites had made an invasion on the south side upon Siceleg, and had smitten Siceleg, and burnt it with fire,&#xA;2 And had taken the women captives that were in it, both little and great: and they had not killed any person, but had carried them with them, and went on their way.&#xA;3 So when David and his men came to the city, and found it burnt with fire, and that their wives, and their sons, and their daughters, were taken captives,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 31</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/36-1-samuel/chap031/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:27 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/36-1-samuel/chap031/</guid>
      <description>1 And the Philistines fought against Israel, and the men of Israel fled from before the Philistines, and fell down slain in mount Gelboe.&#xA;2 And the Philistines fell upon Saul, and upon his sons, and they slew Jonathan, and Abinadab, and Melchisua, the sons of Saul.&#xA;3 And the whole weight of the battle was turned upon Saul: and the archers overtook him, and he was grievously wounded by the archers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 4</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/36-1-samuel/chap004/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:27 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/36-1-samuel/chap004/</guid>
      <description>1 And it came to pass in those days, that the Philistines gathered themselves together to fight: and Israel went out to war against the Philistines, and camped by the Stone of help. And the Philistines came to Aphec,&#xA;2 And put their army in array against Israel. And when they had joined battle, Israel turned their backs to the Philistines: and there were slain in that fight, here and there in the fields, about four thousand men.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 5</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/36-1-samuel/chap005/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:27 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/36-1-samuel/chap005/</guid>
      <description>1 And the Philistines took the ark of God, and carried it from the Stone of help into Azotus.&#xA;2 And the Philistines took the ark of God, and brought it into the temple of Dagon, and set it by Dagon.&#xA;3 And when the Azotians arose early the next day, behold Dagon lay upon his face on the ground before the ark of the Lord: and they took Dagon, and set him again in his place.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 6</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/36-1-samuel/chap006/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:27 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/36-1-samuel/chap006/</guid>
      <description>1 Now the ark of God was in the land of the Philistines seven months.&#xA;2 And the Philistines called for the priests and the diviners, saying: What shall we do with the ark of the Lord? tell us how we are to send it back to its place. And they said:&#xA;3 If you send back the ark of the God of Israel, send it not away empty, but render unto him what you owe for sin, and then you shall be healed: and you shall know why his hand departeth not from you.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 7</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/36-1-samuel/chap007/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:27 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/36-1-samuel/chap007/</guid>
      <description>1 And the men of Cariathiarim came, and fetched up the ark of the Lord, and carried it into the house of Abinadab, in Gabaa: and they sanctified Eleazar, his son, to keep the ark of the Lord.&#xA;2 And it came to pass, that from the day the ark of the Lord abode in Cariathiarim, days were multiplied (for it was now the twentieth year) and all the house of Israel rested, following the Lord.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 8</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/36-1-samuel/chap008/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:27 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/36-1-samuel/chap008/</guid>
      <description>1 And it came to pass, when Samuel was old, that he appointed his sons to be judges over Israel.&#xA;2 Now the name of his firstborn son was Joel: and the name of the second was Abia, judges in Bersabee.&#xA;3 And his sons walked not in his ways: but they turned aside after lucre, and took bribes, and perverted judgment.&#xA;4 Then all the ancients of Israel being assembled came to Samuel to Ramatha.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 9</title>
      <link>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/36-1-samuel/chap009/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:27 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eens.netlify.app/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/36-1-samuel/chap009/</guid>
      <description>1 Now there was a man of Benjamin, whose name was Cis, the son of Abiel, the son of Seror, the son of Bechorath, the son of Aphia, the son of a man of Jemini, valiant and strong.&#xA;2 And he had a son whose name was Saul, a choice and goodly man, and there was not among the children of Israel a goodlier person than he: from his shoulders and upward he appeared above all the people.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
