<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>1 Chronicles on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/40-1-chronicles/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 1 Chronicles on Extra Ecclesia Nulla Salus</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:28 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/40-1-chronicles/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 1</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/40-1-chronicles/chap001/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:28 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/40-1-chronicles/chap001/</guid>
      <description>1 Adam, Seth, Enos,&#xA;2 Cainan, Malaleel, Jared,&#xA;3 Henoc, Mathusale, Lamech,&#xA;4 Noe, Sem, Cham, and Japheth.&#xA;5 The sons of Japheth: Gomer, and Magog, and Madai, and Javan, Thubal, Mosoch, Thiras.&#xA;6 And the sons of Gomer: Ascenez, and Riphath, and Thogorma.&#xA;7 And the sons of Javan: Elisa and Tharsis, Cethim and Dodanim.&#xA;8 The sons of Cham: Chus, and Mesrai, and Phut, and Chanaan.&#xA;9 And the sons of Chus: Saba, and Hevila, Sabatha, and Regma, and Sabathaca.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 10</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/40-1-chronicles/chap010/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:28 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/40-1-chronicles/chap010/</guid>
      <description>1 Now the Philistines fought against Israel, and the men of Israel fled from before the Philistines, and fell down wounded in mount Gelboe.&#xA;2 And the Philistines drew near pursuing after Saul, and his sons, and they killed Jonathan, and Abinadab, and Melchisua the sons of Saul.&#xA;3 And the battle grew hard against Saul and the archers reached him, and wounded him with arrows.&#xA;4 And Saul said to his armourbearer: Draw thy sword, and kill me: lest these uncircumcised come, and mock me.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 11</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/40-1-chronicles/chap011/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:28 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/40-1-chronicles/chap011/</guid>
      <description>1 Then all Israel gathered themselves to David in Hebron, saying: We are thy bone, and thy flesh.&#xA;2 Yesterday also, and the day before when Saul was king, thou wast he that leddest out and broughtest in Israel: for the Lord thy God said to thee: Thou shalt feed my people Israel, and thou shalt be ruler over them.&#xA;3 So all the ancients of Israel came to the king to Hebron, and David made a covenant with them before the Lord: and they anointed him king over Israel according to the word of the Lord which he spoke in the hand of Samuel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 12</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/40-1-chronicles/chap012/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:28 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/40-1-chronicles/chap012/</guid>
      <description>1 Now these are they that came to David to Siceleg, while he yet fled from Saul the son of Cis, and they were most valiant and excellent warriors,&#xA;2 Bending the bow, and using either hand in hurling stones with slings, and shooting arrows: of the brethren of Saul of Benjamin.&#xA;3 The chief was Ahiezer, and Joas, the sons of Samoa of Gabaath, and Jaziel, and Phallet the sons of Azmoth, and Beracha, and Jehu an Anathothite.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 13</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/40-1-chronicles/chap013/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:28 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/40-1-chronicles/chap013/</guid>
      <description>1 David consulted with the captains of thousands, and of hundreds, and with all the commanders.&#xA;2 And he said to all the assembly of Israel: If it please you; and if the words which I speak come from the Lord our God, let us send to the rest of our brethren into all the countries of Israel, and to the priests, and the Levites, that dwell in the suburbs of the cities, to gather themselves to us,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 14</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/40-1-chronicles/chap014/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:28 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/40-1-chronicles/chap014/</guid>
      <description>1 And Hiram king of Tyre sent messengers to David, and cedar trees, and masons, and carpenters, to build him a house.&#xA;2 And David perceived that the Lord had confirmed him king over Israel, and that his kingdom was exalted over his people Israel.&#xA;3 And David took other wives in Jerusalem: and he begot sons, and daughters.&#xA;4 Now these are the names of them that were born to him in Jerusalem: Samua, and Sobad, Nathan, and Solomon,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 15</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/40-1-chronicles/chap015/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:28 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/40-1-chronicles/chap015/</guid>
      <description>1 He made also houses for himself in the city of David: and built a place for the ark of God, and pitched a tabernacle for it.&#xA;2 Then David said: No one ought to carry the ark of God, but the Levites, whom the Lord hath chosen to carry it, and to minister unto himself for ever.&#xA;3 And he gathered all Israel together into Jerusalem, that the ark of God might be brought into its place, which he had prepared for it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 16</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/40-1-chronicles/chap016/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:28 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/40-1-chronicles/chap016/</guid>
      <description>1 So they brought the ark of God, and set it in the midst of the tent, which David had pitched for it: and they offered holocausts, and peace offerings before God.&#xA;2 And when David had made an end of offering holocausts, and peace offerings, he blessed the people in the name of the Lord.&#xA;3 And he divided to all and every one, both men and women, a loaf of bread, and a piece of roasted beef, and flour fried with oil.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 17</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/40-1-chronicles/chap017/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:28 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/40-1-chronicles/chap017/</guid>
      <description>1 Now when David was dwelling in his house, he said to Nathan the prophet: Behold I dwell in a house of cedar: and the ark of the covenant of the Lord is under skins.&#xA;2 And Nathan said to David: Do all that is in thy heart: for God is with thee.&#xA;3 Now that night the word of God came to Nathan, saying:&#xA;4 Go, and speak to David my servant: Thus saith the Lord: Thou shalt not build me a house to dwell in.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 18</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/40-1-chronicles/chap018/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:28 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/40-1-chronicles/chap018/</guid>
      <description>1 And it came to pass after this, that David defeated the Philistines, and humbled them, and took away Geth, and her daughters out of the hands of the Philistines,&#xA;2 And he defeated Moab, and the Moabites were made David&amp;rsquo;s servants, and brought him gifts.&#xA;3 At that time David defeated also Adarezer king of Soba of the land of Hemath, when he went to extend his dominions as far as the river Euphrates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 19</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/40-1-chronicles/chap019/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:28 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/40-1-chronicles/chap019/</guid>
      <description>1 Now it came to pass that Naas the king of the children of Ammon died, and his son reigned in his stead.&#xA;2 And David said: I will shew kindness to Hanon the son of Naas: for his father did a favour tome. And David sent messengers to comfort him upon the death of his father. But when they were come into the land of the children of Ammon, to comfort Hanon,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 2</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/40-1-chronicles/chap002/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:28 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/40-1-chronicles/chap002/</guid>
      <description>1 And these are the sons of Israel: Ruben, Simeon, Levi, Juda, Issachar, and Zabulon,&#xA;2 Dan, Joseph, Benjamin, Nephtali, Gad, and Aser.&#xA;3 The sons of Juda: Her, Onan and Sela. These three were born to him of the Chanaanitess the daughter of Sue. And Her the firstborn of Juda, was wicked in the sight of the Lord, and he slew him.&#xA;4 And Thamar his daughter in law bore him Phares and Zara.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 20</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/40-1-chronicles/chap020/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:28 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/40-1-chronicles/chap020/</guid>
      <description>1 And it came to pass after the course of a year, at the time that kings go out to battle, Joab gathered together an army and the strength of the troops, and wasted the land of the children of Ammon: and went and besieged Rabba. But David stayed at Jerusalem, when Joab smote Rabba, and destroyed it.&#xA;2 And David took the crown of Melchom from his head, and found in it a talent weight of gold, and most precious stones, and he made himself a diadem of it: he took also the spoils of the city which were very great.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 21</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/40-1-chronicles/chap021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:28 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/40-1-chronicles/chap021/</guid>
      <description>1 And Satan rose up against Israel: and moved David to number Israel.&#xA;2 And David said to Joab, and to the rulers of the people: Go, and number Israel from Bersabee even to Dan, and bring me the number of them that I may know it.&#xA;3 And Joab answered: The Lord make his people a hundred times more than they are: but, my lord the king, are they not all thy servants: why doth my lord seek this thing, which may be imputed as a sin to Israel?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 22</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/40-1-chronicles/chap022/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:28 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/40-1-chronicles/chap022/</guid>
      <description>1 Then David said: This is the house of God, And this is the altar for the holocaust of Israel.&#xA;2 And he commanded to gather together all the proselytes of the land of Israel, and out of them he appointed stonecutters to hew stones and polish them, to build the house of God.&#xA;3 And David prepared in abundance iron for the nails of the gates, and for the closures and joinings: and of brass an immense weight.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 23</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/40-1-chronicles/chap023/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:28 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/40-1-chronicles/chap023/</guid>
      <description>1 David being old and full of days, made Solomon his son king over Israel.&#xA;2 And he gathered together all the princes of Israel, and the priests and Levites.&#xA;3 And the Levites were numbered from the age of thirty years, and upwards: and there were found of them thirty-eight thousand men.&#xA;4 Of these twenty-four thousand were chosen, and distributed unto the ministry of the house of the Lord: and six thousand were the overseers and judges.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 24</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/40-1-chronicles/chap024/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:28 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/40-1-chronicles/chap024/</guid>
      <description>1 Now these were the divisions of the sons of Aaron: The sons of Aaron: Nadab, and Abiu, and Eleazar, and Ithamar.&#xA;2 But Nadab and Abiu died before their father, and had no children: so Eleazar, and Ithamar did the office of the priesthood.&#xA;3 And David distributed them, that is, Sadoc of the sons of Eleazar, and Ahimelech of the sons of Ithamar, according to their courses and ministry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 25</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/40-1-chronicles/chap025/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:28 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/40-1-chronicles/chap025/</guid>
      <description>1 Moreover David and the chief officers of the army separated for the ministry the sons of Asaph, and of Heman, and of Idithun: to prophesy with harps, and with psalteries, and with cymbals according to their number serving in their appointed office.&#xA;2 Of the sons of Asaph: Zacchur, and Joseph, and Nathania, and Asarela, sons of Asaph: under the hand of Asaph prophesying near the king.&#xA;3 And of Idithun: the sons of Idithun, Godolias, Sori, Jeseias, and Hasabias, and Mathathias, under the hand of their father Idithun, who prophesied with a harp to give thanks and to praise the Lord.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 26</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/40-1-chronicles/chap026/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:28 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/40-1-chronicles/chap026/</guid>
      <description>1 And the divisions of the porters: of the Corites Meselemia, the son of Core, of the sons of Asaph.&#xA;2 The sons of Meselemia: Zacharias the firstborn, Jadihel the second, Zabadias the third, Jathanael the fourth,&#xA;3 Elam the fifth, Johanan the sixth, Elioenai the seventh.&#xA;4 And the sons of Obededom, Semeias the firstborn, Jozabad the second, Joaha the third, Sachar the fourth, Nathanael the fifth,&#xA;5 Ammiel the sixth, Issachar the seventh, Phollathi the eighth: for the Lord had blessed him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 27</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/40-1-chronicles/chap027/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:28 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/40-1-chronicles/chap027/</guid>
      <description>1 Now the children of Israel according to their number, the heads of families, captains of thousands and of hundreds, and officers, that served the king according to their companies, who came in and went out every month in the year, under every chief were four and twenty thousand.&#xA;2 Over the first company the first month Jesboam, the son of Zabdiel was chief, and under him were four and twenty thousand.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 28</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/40-1-chronicles/chap028/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:28 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/40-1-chronicles/chap028/</guid>
      <description>1 And David assembled all the chief men of Israel, the princes of the tribes, and the captains of the companies, who waited on the king: and the captains over thousands, and over hundreds, and them who had the charge over the substance and possessions of the king, and his sons with the officers of the court, and the men of power, and all the bravest of the army at Jerusalem.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 29</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/40-1-chronicles/chap029/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:28 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/40-1-chronicles/chap029/</guid>
      <description>1 And king David said to all the assembly: Solomon my son, whom alone God hath chosen, is as yet young and tender: and the work is great, for a house is prepared not for man, but for God.&#xA;2 And I with all my ability have prepared the expenses for the house of my God. Gold for vessels of gold, and silver for vessels of silver, brass for things of brass, iron for things of iron, wood for things of wood: and onyx stones, and stones like alabaster, and of divers colours, and all manner of precious stones, and marble of Paros in great abundance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 3</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/40-1-chronicles/chap003/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:28 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/40-1-chronicles/chap003/</guid>
      <description>1 Now these were the sons of David that were born to him in Hebron: the firstborn Amnon of Achinoam the Jezrahelitess, the second Daniel of Abigail the Carmelitess.&#xA;2 The third Absalom the son of Maacha the daughter of Tolmai king of Gessur, the fourth Adonias the son of Aggith,&#xA;3 The fifth Saphatias of Abital, the sixth Jethrahem of Egla his wife.&#xA;4 So six sons were born to him in Hebron, where he reigned seven years and six months.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 4</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/40-1-chronicles/chap004/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:28 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/40-1-chronicles/chap004/</guid>
      <description>1 The sons of Juda: Phares, Hesron, and Charmi and Hur, and Sobal.&#xA;2 And Raia the son of Sobal begot Jahath, of whom were born Ahumai, and Laad. These are the families of Sarathi.&#xA;3 And this is the posterity of Etam: Jezrahel, and Jesema, And Jedebos: and the name of their sister was Asalelphuni.&#xA;4 And Phanuel the father of Gedor, and Ezar the father of Hosa, these are the sons of Hur the firstborn of Ephratha the father of Bethlehem.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 5</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/40-1-chronicles/chap005/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:28 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/40-1-chronicles/chap005/</guid>
      <description>1 Now the sons of Ruben the firstborn of Israel, (for he was his firstborn: but forasmuch as he defiled his father&amp;rsquo;s bed, his first birthright was given to the sons of Joseph the son of Israel, and he was not accounted for the firstborn.&#xA;2 But of the race of Juda, who was the strongest among his brethren, came the princes: but the first birthright was accounted to Joseph.)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 6</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/40-1-chronicles/chap006/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:28 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/40-1-chronicles/chap006/</guid>
      <description>1 The sons of Levi were Gerson, Caath, and Merari.&#xA;2 The Sons of Caath: Amram, Isaar, Hebron, and Oziel.&#xA;3 The children of Amram: Aaron, Moses, and Mary. The Sons of Aaron: Nadab and Abiu, Eleazar and Ithamar.&#xA;4 Eleazar begot Phinees, and Phinees begot Abisue,&#xA;5 And Abisue begot Bocci, and Bocci begot Ozi.&#xA;6 Ozi begot Zaraias, and Zaraias begot Maraioth.&#xA;7 And Maraioth begot Amarias, and Amarias begot Achitob.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 7</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/40-1-chronicles/chap007/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:28 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/40-1-chronicles/chap007/</guid>
      <description>1 Now the sons of Issachar were Thola, and Phua, Jasub and Simeron, four.&#xA;2 The sons of Thola: Ozi and Raphaia, and Jeriel, and Jemai, and Jebsem, and Samuel, chiefs of the houses of their kindreds. Of the posterity of Thola were numbered in the days of David, two and twenty thousand six hundred most valiant men.&#xA;3 The sons of Ozi: Izrahia, of whom were born Michael, and Obadia, and Joel, and Jesia, five all great men.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 8</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/40-1-chronicles/chap008/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:28 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/40-1-chronicles/chap008/</guid>
      <description>1 Now Benjamin begot Bale his firstborn, Asbel the second, Ahara the third,&#xA;2 Nohaa the fourth, and Rapha the fifth.&#xA;3 And the sons of Bale were Addar, and Gera, and Abiud,&#xA;4 And Abisue, and Naaman, and Ahoe,&#xA;5 And Gera, and Sephuphan, and Huram.&#xA;6 These are the sons of Abed, heads of families that dwelt in Gabaa, who were removed into Manahath.&#xA;7 And Naaman, and Achia, and Gera he removed them, and begot Oza, and Ahiud.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 9</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/40-1-chronicles/chap009/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:00:28 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/en/bible/douay-rheims/old-testament/40-1-chronicles/chap009/</guid>
      <description>1 And all Israel was numbered: and the sum of them was written in the book of the kings of Israel, and Juda: and they were carried away to Babylon for their transgression.&#xA;2 Now the first that dwelt in their possessions, and in their cities, were the Israelites, and the priests, and the Levites, and the Nathineans.&#xA;3 And in Jerusalem dwelt of the children of Juda, and of the children of Benjamin, and of the children of Ephraim, and of Manasses.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
